all results:
[   (67, u'2.7', 'NUMBER', 34, 36, False, True, 47),
    (67, u'160 km2', 'NUMBER', 28, 29, False, True, 48),
    (67, u'60 square', 'NUMBER', 24, 25, False, True, 53),
    (67, u'7.0 km2', 'NUMBER', 40, 43, False, True, 60),
    (62, u'1970', 'NUMBER', 1, 1, False, True, 13),
    (53, u'85,050', 'NUMBER', 15, 17, False, True, 3),
    (53, u'13 km2', 'NUMBER', 23, 24, False, True, 3),
    (109, u'1,536', 'NUMBER', 12, 14, False, True, 4),
    (157, u'575,000', 'NUMBER', 3, 5, False, True, 1),
    (157, u'53,400 m2', 'NUMBER', 9, 12, False, True, 3),
    (192, u'two', 'NUMBER', 7, 7, False, True, 14),
    (238, u'two', 'NUMBER', 30, 30, False, True, 23),
    (239, u'One', 'NUMBER', 0, 0, False, True, 8),
    (67, u'United States Census Bureau', 'OTHER', 3, 6, False, False, 131),
    (53, u'Southern United States', u'LOCATION', 35, 37, False, False, 15),
    (282, u'University of Richmond', 'OTHER', 18, 20, False, False, 93),
    (282, u'Virginia Union University', 'OTHER', 24, 26, False, False, 97),
    (   282,
        u'Virginia Commonwealth University',
        'OTHER',
        12,
        14,
        False,
        False,
        99),
    (282, u'Virginia College', 'OTHER', 30, 31, False, False, 105),
    (282, u'South University', 'OTHER', 35, 36, False, False, 110),
    (   282,
        u'Union Theological Seminary & Presbyterian School of Christian Education',
        'OTHER',
        46,
        54,
        False,
        False,
        131),
    (282, u'Baptist Theological Seminary', 'OTHER', 60, 62, False, False, 179),
    (185, u'America', u'LOCATION', 10, 10, False, False, 11),
    (185, u'Confederate States', 'OTHER', 7, 8, False, False, 17),
    (185, u'American Civil War', 'OTHER', 22, 24, False, False, 25),
    (185, u'Capital', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, False, 29),
    (222, u'University', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, False, 6),
    (222, u'Jeter Hall', u'PERSON', 10, 11, False, False, 14),
    (222, u'Ryland Hall', 'OTHER', 13, 14, False, False, 20),
    (222, u'Ralph Adams Cram', u'PERSON', 19, 21, False, False, 32),
    (222, u'Princeton University Chapel', 'OTHER', 27, 29, False, False, 48),
    (222, u'Cathedral', 'OTHER', 32, 32, False, False, 58),
    (222, u'John', u'PERSON', 35, 35, False, False, 64),
    (222, u'Divine', 'OTHER', 37, 37, False, False, 68),
    (77, u'Victorian', 'OTHER', 31, 31, False, False, 14),
    (77, u'Fan', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, False, 18),
    (77, u'VCU', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, False, 28),
    (77, u'Broad Street', 'OTHER', 10, 11, False, False, 34),
    (77, u'Main Street', u'LOCATION', 7, 8, False, False, 40),
    (77, u'Boulevard', u'LOCATION', 5, 5, False, False, 46),
    (190, u'Edgar Allan Poe Museum', u'PERSON', 34, 37, False, False, 3),
    (190, u'Give', 'OTHER', 22, 22, False, False, 18),
    (190, u'Patrick Henry', u'PERSON', 16, 17, False, False, 23),
    (190, u'John', u'PERSON', 8, 8, False, False, 32),
    (191, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 14, 15, False, False, 10),
    (191, u'Chief Justice', 'OTHER', 10, 11, False, False, 18),
    (191, u'John Marshall House', u'PERSON', 1, 3, False, False, 34),
    (192, u'U', 'OTHER', 8, 8, False, False, 14),
    (192, u'S', 'OTHER', 10, 10, False, False, 14),
    (192, u'Presidents', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, False, 14),
    (192, u'Cemetery', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, 16),
    (192, u'Civil War', 'OTHER', 17, 18, False, False, 16),
    (193, u'Monument Avenue', 'OTHER', 14, 15, False, False, 21),
    (206, u'Richmonders', u'PERSON', 5, 5, False, False, 7),
    (238, u'Civil War', 'OTHER', 20, 21, False, False, 40),
    (238, u'Powhatan', 'OTHER', 8, 8, False, False, 79),
    (238, u'Belle Isle', u'LOCATION', 0, 1, False, False, 100),
    (239, u'Civil War', 'OTHER', 14, 15, False, False, 6),
    (62, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 3, 3, True, False, 9),
    (282, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 38, 38, True, False, 115),
    (282, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 1, 1, True, False, 122),
    (282, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 64, 64, True, False, 193),
    (185, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 12, 12, True, False, 5),
    (211, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 5, 5, True, False, 2),
    (222, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 6, 6, True, False, 6),
    (261, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 1, 1, True, False, 9),
    (265, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 11, 11, True, False, 5)]
question: How many square kilometers is Richmond?
expected: 160
question open class words: ['square', 'many', 'is', 'richmond', 'how', 'kilometers']



all results:
[   (85, u'K\xf6ppen Cfa', 'OTHER', 7, 8, False, True, 9),
    (282, u'Virginia Union University', 'OTHER', 24, 26, False, True, 77),
    (282, u'University of Richmond', 'OTHER', 18, 20, False, True, 79),
    (282, u'Virginia College', 'OTHER', 30, 31, False, True, 79),
    (282, u'South University', 'OTHER', 35, 36, False, True, 79),
    (   282,
        u'Union Theological Seminary & Presbyterian School of Christian Education',
        'OTHER',
        46,
        54,
        False,
        True,
        89),
    (   282,
        u'Virginia Commonwealth University',
        'OTHER',
        12,
        14,
        False,
        True,
        91),
    (282, u'Baptist Theological Seminary', 'OTHER', 60, 62, False, True, 123),
    (282, u'BTSR', 'OTHER', 66, 66, False, True, 141),
    (146, u'Islamic Center', 'OTHER', 12, 13, False, True, 28),
    (146, u'ICR', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, True, 29),
    (   146,
        u'Islamic Society of Greater Richmond',
        'OTHER',
        32,
        36,
        False,
        True,
        40),
    (146, u'ISGR', 'OTHER', 38, 38, False, True, 54),
    (146, u'Masjid Ar', 'OTHER', 52, 53, False, True, 96),
    (272, u'Voters', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, True, 22),
    (272, u'Crusade', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, True, 24),
    (272, u'Reverend A', 'OTHER', 24, 25, False, True, 24),
    (272, u'Richmond City Council', 'OTHER', 31, 33, False, True, 32),
    (286, u'Richmond International Airport', 'OTHER', 8, 10, False, True, 33),
    (286, u'Greater', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 43),
    (286, u'IATA', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, True, 43),
    (286, u'ICAO', 'OTHER', 16, 16, False, True, 51),
    (286, u'KRIC', 'OTHER', 18, 18, False, True, 55),
    (   49,
        u'Richmond Union Passenger Railway',
        'OTHER',
        20,
        23,
        False,
        True,
        34),
    (121, u'Gothic', 'OTHER', 27, 27, False, True, 30),
    (121, u'Second Presbyterian Church', 'OTHER', 6, 8, False, True, 34),
    (121, u'February', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 48),
    (133, u'Jewish Foundation', 'OTHER', 19, 20, False, True, 4),
    (133, u'Jewish Community Federation', 'OTHER', 12, 14, False, True, 6),
    (133, u'Jewish Family Services', 'OTHER', 8, 10, False, True, 14),
    (   133,
        u'Weinstein Jewish Community Center',
        'OTHER',
        3,
        6,
        False,
        True,
        22),
    (154, u'Mays & Valentine LLP', 'OTHER', 18, 21, False, True, 25),
    (173, u'Greater Richmond Partnership', 'OTHER', 24, 26, False, True, 9),
    (173, u'MeadWestvaco', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, True, 33),
    (173, u'February', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 39),
    (173, u'Honeywell International', 'OTHER', 46, 47, False, True, 51),
    (175, u'McKesson', 'OTHER', 43, 43, False, True, 28),
    (   175,
        u'Capital One Financial Corporation',
        'OTHER',
        9,
        12,
        False,
        True,
        34),
    (175, u'SunTrust Bank', 'OTHER', 2, 3, False, True, 52),
    (212, u'Schutte House', 'OTHER', 14, 15, False, True, 28),
    (247, u'USL Professional Division', 'OTHER', 17, 19, False, True, 14),
    (247, u'American', 'OTHER', 24, 24, False, True, 16),
    (247, u'Richmond Flying Squirrels', 'OTHER', 29, 31, False, True, 16),
    (247, u'Class', 'OTHER', 34, 34, False, True, 26),
    (   247,
        u'AA Eastern League of Minor League Baseball',
        'OTHER',
        35,
        41,
        False,
        True,
        28),
    (247, u'San Francisco Giants', 'OTHER', 47, 49, False, True, 52),
    (257, u'Sunday', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, True, 42),
    (257, u'BH Media', 'OTHER', 24, 25, False, True, 47),
    (257, u'Dispatch', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, True, 56),
    (257, u'Richmond Times', 'OTHER', 1, 2, False, True, 59),
    (257, u'Berkshire Hathaway', 'OTHER', 34, 35, False, True, 70),
    (277, u'Virginia House of Delegates', 'OTHER', 23, 26, False, True, 15),
    (277, u'Member', 'OTHER', 20, 20, False, True, 18),
    (277, u'Mayor', 'OTHER', 29, 29, False, True, 18),
    (277, u'City', 'OTHER', 32, 32, False, True, 18),
    (277, u'Chairman', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, True, 24),
    (277, u'Baptist', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, True, 32),
    (277, u'Honorable Dwight C', 'OTHER', 1, 3, False, True, 44),
    (   296,
        u'Greater Richmond Transit Company',
        'OTHER',
        18,
        21,
        False,
        True,
        16),
    (296, u'GRTC', 'OTHER', 23, 23, False, True, 29),
    (0, u'D', 'OTHER', 43, 43, False, True, 98),
    (0, u'C', 'OTHER', 45, 45, False, True, 100),
    (0, u'Surrounded', 'OTHER', 47, 47, False, True, 102),
    (0, u'Interstate 95', 'OTHER', 62, 63, False, True, 129),
    (0, u'Interstate', 'OTHER', 65, 65, False, True, 138),
    (0, u'Interstate', 'OTHER', 71, 71, False, True, 156),
    (0, u'State Route', 'OTHER', 75, 76, False, True, 168),
    (2, u'English', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, True, 16),
    (6, u'American Civil War', 'OTHER', 2, 4, False, True, 2),
    (6, u'Confederate States of America', 'OTHER', 13, 16, False, True, 7),
    (146, u'Masjid Umm Barakah', u'LOCATION', 24, 26, False, False, 34),
    (146, u'2nd street', 'NUMBER', 28, 29, False, False, 39),
    (146, u'five', 'NUMBER', 4, 4, False, False, 48),
    (146, u'Masjidullah', u'LOCATION', 45, 45, False, False, 75),
    (146, u'Rahman', u'PERSON', 55, 55, False, False, 105),
    (272, u'South Richmond', u'LOCATION', 17, 18, False, False, 18),
    (272, u'Carl Prince', u'PERSON', 27, 28, False, False, 27),
    (286, u'RIC', u'PERSON', 14, 14, False, False, 47),
    (286, u'Sandston', u'LOCATION', 23, 23, False, False, 65),
    (286, u'seven miles', 'NUMBER', 25, 26, False, False, 68),
    (286, u'11 km', 'NUMBER', 28, 29, False, False, 74),
    (49, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 16, 17, False, False, 29),
    (121, u'5,1845', 'NUMBER', 2, 4, False, False, 42),
    (154, u'Troutman Sanders', u'PERSON', 9, 10, False, False, 9),
    (173, u'2008', 'NUMBER', 18, 18, False, False, 9),
    (173, u'Connecticut', u'LOCATION', 13, 13, False, False, 15),
    (173, u'2006', 'NUMBER', 2, 2, False, False, 37),
    (175, u'Virginia', u'LOCATION', 19, 19, False, False, 20),
    (175, u'McLean', u'LOCATION', 17, 17, False, False, 24),
    (175, u'San Francisco', u'LOCATION', 47, 48, False, False, 36),
    (175, u'Atlanta', u'LOCATION', 7, 7, False, False, 44),
    (212, u'Patteson', u'PERSON', 12, 12, False, False, 27),
    (212, u'Edgar Allan Poe Museum', u'PERSON', 18, 21, False, False, 30),
    (257, u'120,000', 'NUMBER', 17, 19, False, False, 38),
    (257, u'Warren Buffett', u'PERSON', 30, 31, False, False, 59),
    (277, u'Jones', u'PERSON', 5, 5, False, False, 40),
    (296, u'Chesterfield', u'LOCATION', 12, 12, False, False, 14),
    (296, u'Henrico', u'LOCATION', 9, 9, False, False, 17),
    (0, u'James River', u'LOCATION', 9, 10, False, False, 63),
    (0, u'44 miles', 'NUMBER', 12, 13, False, False, 66),
    (0, u'71 km', 'NUMBER', 15, 16, False, False, 69),
    (0, u'Williamsburg', u'LOCATION', 20, 20, False, False, 75),
    (0, u'66 miles', 'NUMBER', 22, 23, False, False, 76),
    (0, u'106 km', 'NUMBER', 25, 26, False, False, 79),
    (0, u'Charlottesville', u'LOCATION', 30, 30, False, False, 85),
    (0, u'98 miles', 'NUMBER', 33, 34, False, False, 87),
    (0, u'158 km', 'NUMBER', 36, 37, False, False, 90),
    (0, u'Washington', u'LOCATION', 41, 41, False, False, 96),
    (0, u'Henrico', u'LOCATION', 49, 49, False, False, 104),
    (0, u'Chesterfield', u'LOCATION', 51, 51, False, False, 106),
    (0, u'288', 'NUMBER', 77, 77, False, False, 174),
    (3, u'1737', 'NUMBER', 8, 8, False, False, 4),
    (85, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 0, 0, True, False, 12),
    (282, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 38, 38, True, False, 81),
    (282, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 1, 1, True, False, 119),
    (282, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 64, 64, True, False, 133),
    (146, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 15, 15, True, False, 27),
    (146, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 9, 9, True, False, 33),
    (272, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 12, 12, True, False, 25),
    (286, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 2, 2, True, False, 39),
    (286, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 33, 33, True, False, 85),
    (49, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 2, 2, True, False, 20),
    (121, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 10, 10, True, False, 30),
    (121, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 40, 40, True, False, 30),
    (133, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 16, 16, True, False, 2),
    (133, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 18, 18, True, False, 2),
    (154, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 6, 6, True, False, 11),
    (154, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 15, 15, True, False, 16),
    (173, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 16, 16, True, False, 9),
    (175, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 24, 24, True, False, 10),
    (175, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 34, 34, True, False, 10),
    (212, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 3, 3, True, False, 22),
    (212, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 23, 23, True, False, 38),
    (247, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 13, 13, True, False, 16),
    (257, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 11, 11, True, False, 42),
    (277, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 34, 34, True, False, 18),
    (296, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 7, 7, True, False, 19),
    (0, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 0, 0, True, False, 57),
    (2, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 3, 3, True, False, 0),
    (3, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 4, 4, True, False, 0),
    (6, u'Richmond', u'LOCATION', 6, 6, True, False, 0)]
question: What is Richmond's Köppen climate classification?
expected: Cfa
expected sentence: Richmond has a humid subtropical climate (Köppen Cfa), with hot and humid summers and generally cool winters.
question open class words: ['k\xc3\xb6ppen', 'classification', 'is', 'climate', 'richmond', 's']



all results:
[   (84, u'Talmud', 'OTHER', 53, 53, False, True, 105),
    (84, u'Passover', 'OTHER', 36, 36, False, True, 207),
    (84, u'Orthodox', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, True, 441),
    (80, u'Zionist', 'OTHER', 55, 55, False, True, 2),
    (80, u'State', 'OTHER', 44, 44, False, True, 9),
    (80, u'Zionist', 'OTHER', 28, 28, False, True, 25),
    (   80,
        u'National Council for Young Israel',
        19,
        23,
        30),
    (80, u'S', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, True, 36),
    (80, u'U', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, True, 38),
    (80, u'Orthodox Judaism', 'OTHER', 7, 8, False, True, 45),
    (80, u'Orthodoxy', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 52),
    (32, u'Ashkenazi Orthodox Jews', 'OTHER', 57, 59, False, True, 15),
    (32, u'Passover', 'OTHER', 22, 22, False, True, 20),
    (32, u'ReMA', 'OTHER', 67, 67, False, True, 25),
    (32, u'Shulchan Aruch', 'OTHER', 73, 74, False, True, 31),
    (30, u'Orthodox', 'OTHER', 11, 11, False, True, 19),
    (64, u'Haredi Judaism', 'OTHER', 7, 8, False, True, 13),
    (64, u'Chasidic Judaism', 'OTHER', 2, 3, False, True, 18),
    (37, u'Haredi', 'OTHER', 23, 23, False, True, 17),
    (84, u'Kashrut', u'LOCATION', 34, 34, False, False, 219),
    (80, u'Israel', u'LOCATION', 46, 46, False, False, 7),
    (32, u'Talmud', u'LOCATION', 28, 28, False, False, 14),
    (37, u'one', 'NUMBER', 13, 13, False, False, 7)]
question: previous generations typically praciced a more lenient position in regard to what?
expected: dietary laws
expected sentence: Rather, the Orthodox community, as a counterreaction to the liberalism of the Haskalah movement, began to embrace far more stringent halachic practices than their predecessors, most notably in matters of Kashrut and Passover dietary laws, where the strictest possible interpretation becomes a religious requirement, even where the Talmud explicitly prefers a more lenient position, and even where a more lenient position was practiced by prior generations.
question open class words: ['praciced', 'regard', 'position', 'lenient', 'previous', 'typically', 'generations', 'more']



    (80, u'4,2014', 'NUMBER', 2, 4, False, True, 22),
    (81, u'five', 'NUMBER', 9, 9, False, True, 26),
    (81, u'1.5 million', 'NUMBER', 5, 8, False, True, 29),
    (100, u'16,2011', 'NUMBER', 9, 11, False, True, 48),
    (50, u'Speech', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, False, 75),
    (50, u'Canadian', 'OTHER', 29, 29, False, False, 149),
    (   70,
        u'Canadian Cyber Incident Response Centre',
        'OTHER',
        5,
        9,
        False,
        False,
        61),
    (70, u'Public Safety Canada ’', 'OTHER', 0, 3, False, False, 71),
    (70, u'CCIRC', 'OTHER', 11, 11, False, False, 83),
    (79, u'STOP', 'OTHER', 11, 11, False, False, 36),
    (79, u'THINK', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, False, 40),
    (79, u'September', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, 52),
    (72, u'CCIRC', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, 34),
    (83, u'Canadian', 'OTHER', 11, 11, False, False, 43),
    (83, u'Cyber Security Awareness Month', 'OTHER', 17, 20, False, False, 49),
    (83, u'October', 'OTHER', 22, 22, False, False, 72),
    (55, u'Action Plan', 'OTHER', 1, 2, False, False, 56),
    (74, u'National Strategy', 'OTHER', 27, 28, False, False, 121),
    (74, u'Action Plan', 'OTHER', 30, 31, False, False, 138),
    (74, u'Critical Infrastructure', 'OTHER', 33, 34, False, False, 156),
    (53, u'Government', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, False, 10),
    (   54,
        u'Cyber Incident Management Framework',
        'OTHER',
        1,
        4,
        False,
        False,
        26),
    (71, u'CCIRC', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, 75),
    (   80,
        u'Cyber Security Cooperation Program',
        12,
        15,
        False,
        4),
    (80, u'February', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, 31),
    (52, u'Canadians', 'OTHER', 24, 24, False, False, 28),
    (   100,
        u'National Center for Cyber Defense',
        'OTHER',
        27,
        31,
        False,
        False,
        28),
    (100, u'Nationales Cyber', 'OTHER', 33, 34, False, False, 33),
    (100, u'German NCAZ', 'OTHER', 24, 25, False, False, 35),
    (100, u'Abwehrzentrum', 'OTHER', 36, 36, False, False, 41),
    (100, u'Home Affairs', 'OTHER', 17, 18, False, False, 42),
    (100, u'German Minister', 'OTHER', 14, 15, False, False, 45),
    (100, u'Bonn', u'LOCATION', 39, 39, False, False, 50),
    (100, u'On June', 'OTHER', 7, 8, False, False, 52),
    (   100,
        u'National Cyber Defense Initiative',
        'OTHER',
        2,
        5,
        False,
        False,
        55),
    (100, u'Berlin', u'LOCATION', 0, 0, False, False, 67),
    (0, u'IT', 'OTHER', 8, 8, False, False, 8),
    (50, u'Cyber Security Strategy', 'OTHER', 13, 15, True, False, 35),
    (50, u'Canada', u'LOCATION', 10, 10, True, False, 40),
    (50, u'Public Safety Canada', 'OTHER', 6, 8, True, False, 44),
    (82, u'Canada', u'LOCATION', 9, 9, True, False, 38),
    (82, u'Cyber Security Strategy', 'OTHER', 12, 14, True, False, 38),
    (82, u'Public Safety Canada', 'OTHER', 0, 2, True, False, 50),
    (70, u'Canada', u'LOCATION', 22, 22, True, False, 105),
    (79, u'Public Safety Canada', 'OTHER', 6, 8, True, False, 28),
    (72, u'Public Safety', 'OTHER', 9, 10, True, False, 10),
    (72, u'Canada', u'LOCATION', 11, 11, True, False, 16),
    (83, u'Public Safety Canada', 'OTHER', 0, 2, True, False, 32),
    (55, u'Cyber Security Strategy', 'OTHER', 10, 12, True, False, 12),
    (55, u'Canada', u'LOCATION', 7, 7, True, False, 26),
    (74, u'Cyber Security Strategy', 'OTHER', 3, 5, True, False, 28),
    (74, u'Canada', u'LOCATION', 0, 0, True, False, 42),
    (51, u'Canada', u'LOCATION', 8, 8, True, False, 10),
    (53, u'Canada', u'LOCATION', 11, 11, True, False, 10),
    (54, u'Canada', u'LOCATION', 6, 6, True, False, 27),
    (71, u'Canada', u'LOCATION', 27, 27, True, False, 33),
    (80, u'Canada', u'LOCATION', 9, 9, True, False, 7),
    (81, u'Canada', u'LOCATION', 16, 16, True, False, 5)]
question: When did Public Safety Canada unveil Canada's Cyber Security Strategy?
expected: October 3, 2010
expected sentence: On October 3, 2010, Public Safety Canada unveiled Canada’s Cyber Security Strategy, following a Speech from the Throne commitment to boost the security of Canadian cyberspace.
question open class words: ['canada', 'did', 'when', 'cyber', 'unveil', 's', 'safety', 'security', 'strategy', 'public']



all results:
[   (66, u'Walter Schlech', u'PERSON', 64, 65, False, True, 189),
    (132, u'Kennedy', u'PERSON', 26, 26, False, True, 27),
    (132, u'Dun Gifford', u'PERSON', 30, 31, False, True, 33),
    (112, u'Nixon', u'PERSON', 28, 28, False, True, 15),
    (74, u'Stephen Gardner', u'PERSON', 28, 29, False, True, 32),
    (74, u'Larry Thurlow', u'PERSON', 13, 14, False, True, 36),
    (53, u'George Elliott', u'PERSON', 8, 9, False, True, 26),
    (53, u'Douglas Brinkley', u'PERSON', 13, 14, False, True, 26),
    (54, u'Zumwalt', u'PERSON', 9, 9, False, True, 17),
    (54, u'Elliott', u'PERSON', 0, 0, False, True, 21),
    (71, u'John Kerry', u'PERSON', 63, 64, False, True, 70),
    (71, u'Bush', u'PERSON', 79, 79, False, True, 86),
    (71, u'Bush', u'PERSON', 14, 14, False, True, 139),
    (71, u'George W', u'PERSON', 11, 12, False, True, 145),
    (95, u'Harold Donohue', u'PERSON', 32, 33, False, True, 45),
    (105, u'Cameron Kerry', u'PERSON', 2, 3, False, True, 21),
    (105, u'Vallely', u'PERSON', 0, 0, False, True, 27),
    (116, u'Cronin', u'PERSON', 18, 18, False, True, 30),
    (157, u'Weld', u'PERSON', 2, 2, False, True, 19),
    (193, u'Bob Shrum', u'PERSON', 2, 3, False, True, 30),
    (193, u'Edwards', u'PERSON', 37, 37, False, True, 72),
    (231, u'Frederick', u'PERSON', 8, 8, False, True, 14),
    (231, u'Ida Lowe', u'PERSON', 17, 18, False, True, 20),
    (   246,
        u'Maria Teresa Thierstein Sim\xf5es Ferreira',
        u'PERSON',
        12,
        16,
        False,
        True,
        21),
    (246, u'Teresa', u'PERSON', 20, 20, False, True, 25),
    (246, u'Henry John Heinz III', u'PERSON', 33, 36, False, True, 41),
    (246, u'Heinz', u'PERSON', 44, 44, False, True, 63),
    (253, u'Rosemary Forbes Kerry', u'PERSON', 31, 33, False, True, 27),
    (253, u'Forbes', u'PERSON', 23, 23, False, True, 29),
    (253, u'Heinz', u'PERSON', 2, 2, False, True, 33),
    (66, u'New York', u'LOCATION', 15, 16, False, False, 108),
    (66, u'Washington', u'LOCATION', 18, 18, False, False, 113),
    (66, u'D', 'OTHER', 20, 20, False, False, 115),
    (66, u'C', 'OTHER', 22, 22, False, False, 117),
    (66, u'11,1969', 'NUMBER', 26, 28, False, False, 117),
    (   66,
        u'Atlantic Military Sea Transportation Service',
        37,
        41,
        124),
    (66, u'Brooklyn', u'LOCATION', 34, 34, False, False, 129),
    (66, u'Rear Admiral', 'OTHER', 62, 63, False, False, 179),
    (132, u'Kilvert & Forbes Ltd', 'OTHER', 17, 20, False, False, 24),
    (132, u'TV', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, False, 27),
    (112, u'President', 'OTHER', 27, 27, False, False, 13),
    (112, u'Nixon White House', 'OTHER', 11, 13, False, False, 15),
    (112, u'Oval Office', 'OTHER', 5, 6, False, False, 29),
    (256, u'000', 'NUMBER', 28, 28, False, False, 46),
    (43, u'B', 'OTHER', 18, 18, False, False, 28),
    (43, u'40 rocket', 'NUMBER', 20, 21, False, False, 29),
    (43, u'Cửa Lớn River', u'LOCATION', 6, 8, False, False, 34),
    (43, u'Swift', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, False, 52),
    (51, u'B', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, False, 20),
    (51, u'40 rocket', 'NUMBER', 17, 18, False, False, 21),
    (51, u'Viet Cong', 'OTHER', 36, 37, False, False, 71),
    (51, u'VC', 'OTHER', 39, 39, False, False, 80),
    (53, u'2003', 'NUMBER', 16, 16, False, False, 27),
    (54, u'Silver Star', 'OTHER', 5, 6, False, False, 16),
    (54, u'An Thoi', 'OTHER', 12, 13, False, False, 16),
    (71, u'Vietnam War', 'OTHER', 60, 61, False, False, 73),
    (71, u'Vietnam War', 'OTHER', 72, 73, False, False, 78),
    (71, u'United States Army', 'OTHER', 51, 53, False, False, 80),
    (71, u'Texas Air National Guard', 'OTHER', 39, 42, False, False, 90),
    (71, u'Republicans', 'OTHER', 88, 88, False, False, 95),
    (71, u'Presidential', 'OTHER', 18, 18, False, False, 127),
    (71, u'2000', 'NUMBER', 17, 17, False, False, 130),
    (95, u'February', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, 17),
    (95, u'Democrat', 'OTHER', 30, 30, False, False, 41),
    (116, u'44.72 %).', 'NUMBER', 39, 42, False, False, 65),
    (157, u'6.9 million', 'NUMBER', 14, 17, False, False, 16),
    (157, u'Beacon Hill', u'LOCATION', 22, 23, False, False, 25),
    (165, u'Washington Post', 'OTHER', 23, 24, False, False, 31),
    (165, u'Pakistan', u'LOCATION', 16, 16, False, False, 32),
    (165, u'2011', 'NUMBER', 29, 29, False, False, 32),
    (165, u'two countries', 'NUMBER', 38, 39, False, False, 44),
    (193, u'2004 campaign', 'NUMBER', 10, 11, False, False, 22),
    (193, u'Time', 'OTHER', 18, 18, False, False, 31),
    (193, u'two', 'NUMBER', 42, 42, False, False, 87),
    (208, u'one', 'NUMBER', 26, 26, False, False, 16),
    (208, u'Career State Department', 'OTHER', 0, 2, False, False, 32),
    (231, u'Fred', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, False, 14),
    (231, u'Austro', u'LOCATION', 24, 24, False, False, 34),
    (231, u'Hungarian Empire', 'OTHER', 26, 27, False, False, 38),
    (246, u'Mozambican', u'LOCATION', 6, 6, False, False, 25),
    (246, u'Republican', 'OTHER', 30, 30, False, False, 35),
    (246, u'Senate', 'OTHER', 31, 31, False, False, 37),
    (246, u'Earth Day', 'OTHER', 47, 48, False, False, 69),
    (246, u'1990', 'NUMBER', 51, 51, False, False, 77),
    (253, u'2002', 'NUMBER', 38, 38, False, False, 39),
    (66, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 0, 0, True, True, 131),
    (132, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 0, 0, True, True, 27),
    (112, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 17, 17, True, True, 7),
    (256, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 0, 0, True, True, 10),
    (74, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 23, 23, True, True, 28),
    (74, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 34, 34, True, True, 39),
    (74, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 6, 6, True, True, 45),
    (43, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 10, 10, True, True, 28),
    (43, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 34, 34, True, True, 44),
    (51, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 6, 6, True, True, 19),
    (51, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 21, 21, True, True, 26),
    (53, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 0, 0, True, True, 27),
    (53, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 27, 27, True, True, 27),
    (54, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 2, 2, True, True, 17),
    (54, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 19, 19, True, True, 17),
    (71, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 94, 94, True, True, 101),
    (95, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 4, 4, True, True, 11),
    (95, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 15, 15, True, True, 11),
    (105, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 24, 24, True, True, 21),
    (116, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 8, 8, True, True, 28),
    (116, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 32, 32, True, True, 44),
    (157, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 0, 0, True, True, 19),
    (157, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 19, 19, True, True, 19),
    (165, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 0, 0, True, True, 32),
    (165, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 32, 32, True, True, 32),
    (193, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 7, 7, True, True, 20),
    (193, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 26, 26, True, True, 39),
    (208, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 13, 13, True, True, 10),
    (208, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 23, 23, True, True, 10),
    (231, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 0, 0, True, True, 14),
    (231, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 14, 14, True, True, 14),
    (246, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 0, 0, True, True, 25),
    (246, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 25, 25, True, True, 25),
    (253, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 4, 4, True, True, 29),
    (231, u'A', 'OTHER', 9, 9, True, False, 14)]
question: Who was Kerry a personal aide for?
expected: Rear Admiral Walter Schlech
expected sentence: Kerry's preferred choice for reassignment was as a military aide in Boston, New York or Washington, D.C. On April 11, 1969, he reported to the Brooklyn-based Atlantic Military Sea Transportation Service, where he would remain on active duty for the following year as a personal aide to an officer, Rear Admiral Walter Schlech.
actual: (66, u'Walter Schlech', u'PERSON', 64, 65, False, True, 189)
question open class words: ['kerry', 'personal', 'aide', 'was']



all results:
[   (74, u'Stephen Gardner', u'PERSON', 28, 29, False, True, 32),
    (74, u'Larry Thurlow', u'PERSON', 13, 14, False, True, 36),
    (53, u'George Elliott', u'PERSON', 8, 9, False, True, 26),
    (53, u'Douglas Brinkley', u'PERSON', 13, 14, False, True, 26),
    (54, u'Zumwalt', u'PERSON', 9, 9, False, True, 17),
    (54, u'Elliott', u'PERSON', 0, 0, False, True, 21),
    (71, u'John Kerry', u'PERSON', 63, 64, False, True, 70),
    (71, u'Bush', u'PERSON', 79, 79, False, True, 86),
    (71, u'Bush', u'PERSON', 14, 14, False, True, 139),
    (71, u'George W', u'PERSON', 11, 12, False, True, 145),
    (95, u'Harold Donohue', u'PERSON', 32, 33, False, True, 45),
    (105, u'Cameron Kerry', u'PERSON', 2, 3, False, True, 21),
    (105, u'Vallely', u'PERSON', 0, 0, False, True, 27),
    (116, u'Cronin', u'PERSON', 18, 18, False, True, 30),
    (157, u'Weld', u'PERSON', 2, 2, False, True, 19),
    (193, u'Bob Shrum', u'PERSON', 2, 3, False, True, 30),
    (193, u'Edwards', u'PERSON', 37, 37, False, True, 72),
    (231, u'Frederick', u'PERSON', 8, 8, False, True, 14),
    (231, u'Ida Lowe', u'PERSON', 17, 18, False, True, 20),
    (   246,
        u'Maria Teresa Thierstein Sim\xf5es Ferreira',
        u'PERSON',
        12,
        16,
        False,
        True,
        21),
    (246, u'Teresa', u'PERSON', 20, 20, False, True, 25),
    (246, u'Henry John Heinz III', u'PERSON', 33, 36, False, True, 41),
    (246, u'Heinz', u'PERSON', 44, 44, False, True, 63),
    (253, u'Rosemary Forbes Kerry', u'PERSON', 31, 33, False, True, 27),
    (253, u'Forbes', u'PERSON', 23, 23, False, True, 29),
    (253, u'Heinz', u'PERSON', 2, 2, False, True, 33),
    (254, u'Heinz', u'PERSON', 22, 22, False, True, 15),
    (254, u'Forbes', u'PERSON', 6, 6, False, True, 29),
    (43, u'B', 'OTHER', 18, 18, False, False, 28),
    (43, u'40 rocket', 'NUMBER', 20, 21, False, False, 29),
    (43, u'Cửa Lớn River', u'LOCATION', 6, 8, False, False, 34),
    (43, u'Swift', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, False, 52),
    (51, u'B', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, False, 20),
    (51, u'40 rocket', 'NUMBER', 17, 18, False, False, 21),
    (51, u'Viet Cong', 'OTHER', 36, 37, False, False, 71),
    (51, u'VC', 'OTHER', 39, 39, False, False, 80),
    (53, u'2003', 'NUMBER', 16, 16, False, False, 27),
    (54, u'Silver Star', 'OTHER', 5, 6, False, False, 16),
    (54, u'An Thoi', 'OTHER', 12, 13, False, False, 16),
    (71, u'Vietnam War', 'OTHER', 60, 61, False, False, 73),
    (71, u'Vietnam War', 'OTHER', 72, 73, False, False, 78),
    (71, u'United States Army', 'OTHER', 51, 53, False, False, 80),
    (71, u'Texas Air National Guard', 'OTHER', 39, 42, False, False, 90),
    (71, u'Republicans', 'OTHER', 88, 88, False, False, 95),
    (71, u'Presidential', 'OTHER', 18, 18, False, False, 127),
    (71, u'2000', 'NUMBER', 17, 17, False, False, 130),
    (95, u'February', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, 17),
    (95, u'Democrat', 'OTHER', 30, 30, False, False, 41),
    (116, u'44.72 %).', 'NUMBER', 39, 42, False, False, 65),
    (157, u'6.9 million', 'NUMBER', 14, 17, False, False, 16),
    (157, u'Beacon Hill', u'LOCATION', 22, 23, False, False, 25),
    (165, u'Washington Post', 'OTHER', 23, 24, False, False, 31),
    (165, u'Pakistan', u'LOCATION', 16, 16, False, False, 32),
    (165, u'2011', 'NUMBER', 29, 29, False, False, 32),
    (165, u'two countries', 'NUMBER', 38, 39, False, False, 44),
    (193, u'2004 campaign', 'NUMBER', 10, 11, False, False, 22),
    (193, u'Time', 'OTHER', 18, 18, False, False, 31),
    (193, u'two', 'NUMBER', 42, 42, False, False, 87),
    (208, u'one', 'NUMBER', 26, 26, False, False, 16),
    (208, u'Career State Department', 'OTHER', 0, 2, False, False, 32),
    (231, u'A', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, False, 14),
    (231, u'Fred', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, False, 14),
    (231, u'Austro', u'LOCATION', 24, 24, False, False, 34),
    (231, u'Hungarian Empire', 'OTHER', 26, 27, False, False, 38),
    (246, u'Mozambican', u'LOCATION', 6, 6, False, False, 25),
    (246, u'Republican', 'OTHER', 30, 30, False, False, 35),
    (246, u'Senate', 'OTHER', 31, 31, False, False, 37),
    (246, u'Earth Day', 'OTHER', 47, 48, False, False, 69),
    (246, u'1990', 'NUMBER', 51, 51, False, False, 77),
    (253, u'2002', 'NUMBER', 38, 38, False, False, 39),
    (254, u'U', 'OTHER', 36, 36, False, False, 31),
    (254, u'President', 'OTHER', 40, 40, False, False, 39),
    (0, u'Aurora', u'LOCATION', 4, 4, False, False, 7),
    (0, u'Massachusetts', u'LOCATION', 12, 12, False, False, 23),
    (0, u'New Hampshire', u'LOCATION', 14, 15, False, False, 27),
    (2, u'1969', 'NUMBER', 13, 13, False, False, 13),
    (2, u'four', 'NUMBER', 17, 17, False, False, 17),
    (2, u'South Vietnam', u'LOCATION', 24, 25, False, False, 24),
    (2, u'OIC', 'OTHER', 33, 33, False, False, 33),
    (4, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 6, 7, False, False, 2),
    (4, u'Vietnam', u'LOCATION', 12, 12, False, False, 3),
    (4, u'Veterans Against', 'OTHER', 13, 14, False, False, 4),
    (4, u'War', 'OTHER', 16, 16, False, False, 7),
    (4, u'Vietnam War', 'OTHER', 34, 35, False, False, 25),
    (74, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 23, 23, True, True, 28),
    (74, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 34, 34, True, True, 39),
    (74, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 6, 6, True, True, 45),
    (43, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 10, 10, True, True, 28),
    (43, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 34, 34, True, True, 44),
    (51, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 6, 6, True, True, 19),
    (51, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 21, 21, True, True, 26),
    (53, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 0, 0, True, True, 27),
    (53, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 27, 27, True, True, 27),
    (54, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 2, 2, True, True, 17),
    (54, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 19, 19, True, True, 17),
    (71, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 94, 94, True, True, 101),
    (95, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 4, 4, True, True, 11),
    (95, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 15, 15, True, True, 11),
    (105, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 24, 24, True, True, 21),
    (116, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 8, 8, True, True, 28),
    (116, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 32, 32, True, True, 44),
    (157, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 0, 0, True, True, 19),
    (157, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 19, 19, True, True, 19),
    (165, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 0, 0, True, True, 32),
    (165, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 32, 32, True, True, 32),
    (193, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 7, 7, True, True, 20),
    (193, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 26, 26, True, True, 39),
    (208, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 13, 13, True, True, 10),
    (208, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 23, 23, True, True, 10),
    (231, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 0, 0, True, True, 14),
    (231, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 14, 14, True, True, 14),
    (246, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 0, 0, True, True, 25),
    (246, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 25, 25, True, True, 25),
    (253, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 4, 4, True, True, 29),
    (254, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 13, 13, True, True, 15),
    (254, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 28, 28, True, True, 15),
    (0, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 0, 0, True, True, 1),
    (2, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 0, 0, True, True, 0),
    (4, u'Kerry', u'PERSON', 9, 9, True, True, 0)]
question: Who was Kerry an Lt. Gov. for?
expected: Michael Dukakis
expected sentence: He served as Lieutenant Governor of Massachusetts under Michael Dukakis from 1983 to 1985 and was elected to the U.S. Senate in 1984 and was sworn in the following January.
actual: (74, u'Stephen Gardner', u'PERSON', 28, 29, False, True, 32)
question open class words: ['gov', 'kerry', 'lt', 'was']



all results:
[   (112, u'Stonehenge', 'OTHER', 20, 20, False, True, 95),
    (113, u'Neolithic', 'OTHER', 32, 32, False, True, 54),
    (113, u'Old Kingdom', 'OTHER', 38, 39, False, True, 66),
    (134, u'Greeks', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, True, None),
    (134, u'Romans', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, True, None),
    (134, u'Garamantes', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, True, None),
    (53, u'F', 'OTHER', 39, 39, False, True, 36),
    (53, u'F', 'OTHER', 49, 49, False, True, 46),
    (68, u'C', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, True, 63),
    (68, u'F', 'OTHER', 25, 25, False, True, 67),
    (3, u'Atlas Mountains', 'OTHER', 24, 25, False, True, 17),
    (3, u'Maghreb', 'OTHER', 28, 28, False, True, 21),
    (3, u'Nile Valley', 'OTHER', 32, 33, False, True, 25),
    (135, u'Roman', 'OTHER', 10, 10, False, True, 4),
    (135, u'Garamantes', 'OTHER', 6, 6, False, True, 8),
    (105, u'Ouranosaurus', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, True, 5),
    (105, u'Afrovenator', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, True, 9),
    (136, u'Garamantes', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, True, 11),
    (104, u'Ajjer', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, True, 6),
    (106, u'Mediterranean', 'OTHER', 30, 30, False, True, 15),
    (113, u'Egypt', u'LOCATION', 41, 41, False, False, 75),
    (72, u'Morocco', u'LOCATION', 9, 9, False, False, 3),
    (72, u'Ouarzazate', u'LOCATION', 7, 7, False, False, 7),
    (72, u'Algeria', u'LOCATION', 5, 5, False, False, 11),
    (72, u'Biskra', u'LOCATION', 3, 3, False, False, 15),
    (74, u'Niger', u'LOCATION', 9, 9, False, False, 3),
    (74, u'Agadez', u'LOCATION', 7, 7, False, False, 7),
    (74, u'Mali', u'LOCATION', 5, 5, False, False, 11),
    (74, u'Timbuktu', u'LOCATION', 3, 3, False, False, 15),
    (53, u'Algeria', u'LOCATION', 5, 5, False, False, 2),
    (53, u'113.9', 'NUMBER', 45, 47, False, False, 42),
    (58, u'Bilma', u'LOCATION', 5, 5, False, False, 5),
    (58, u'Niger', u'LOCATION', 7, 7, False, False, 9),
    (58, u'Faya', u'PERSON', 9, 9, False, False, 13),
    (58, u'Largeau', u'PERSON', 11, 11, False, False, 17),
    (68, u'50', 'NUMBER', 23, 23, False, False, 65),
    (3, u'North Africa', u'LOCATION', 9, 10, False, False, 2),
    (3, u'Egypt', u'LOCATION', 35, 35, False, False, 28),
    (3, u'Sudan', u'LOCATION', 37, 37, False, False, 30),
    (37, u'Atlas Mountains', u'LOCATION', 1, 2, False, False, 2),
    (37, u'Algeria', u'LOCATION', 6, 6, False, False, 2),
    (37, u'Morocco', u'LOCATION', 8, 8, False, False, 4),
    (37, u'Tunisia', u'LOCATION', 10, 10, False, False, 6),
    (135, u'Garama', u'LOCATION', 20, 20, False, False, 6),
    (105, u'Jobaria', u'PERSON', 7, 7, False, False, 7),
    (111, u'Africa', u'LOCATION', 24, 24, False, False, 8),
    (81, u'Earth', u'LOCATION', 3, 3, False, False, 4),
    (81, u'Sahara', u'LOCATION', 15, 15, False, False, 8),
    (136, u'eight', 'NUMBER', 3, 3, False, False, 1),
    (104, u'Tassili', u'LOCATION', 18, 18, False, False, 3),
    (104, u'Algeria', u'LOCATION', 24, 24, False, False, 9),
    (104, u'30,000 petroglyphs', 'NUMBER', 1, 4, False, False, 11),
    (106, u'Nile Valley', u'LOCATION', 15, 16, False, False, 43),
    (106, u'Sahara', u'LOCATION', 2, 2, False, False, 71),
    (112, u'Nabta Playa', u'LOCATION', 3, 4, True, False, 39),
    (113, u'Nabta Playa', u'LOCATION', 6, 7, True, False, 28),
    (113, u'Nabta', u'LOCATION', 35, 35, True, False, 57)]
question: What are examples of the first known archaeoastronomy   found in Nabta Playa?
expected: Megaliths
expected sentence: Megaliths found at Nabta Playa are overt examples of probably the world's first known archaeoastronomy devices, predating Stonehenge by some 2,000 years.
question open class words: ['archaeoastronomy', 'examples', 'nabta', 'are', 'playa', 'known', 'found', 'first']



all results:
[   (26, u'K\xf6ppen', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, True, 3),
    (26, u'BWh', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, True, 7),
    (38, u'Mediterranean', 'OTHER', 36, 36, False, True, None),
    (12, u'Mediterranean', 'OTHER', 45, 45, False, True, 3),
    (12, u'Maghreb', 'OTHER', 22, 22, False, True, 45),
    (13, u'Mediterranean', 'OTHER', 45, 45, False, True, 1),
    (13, u'Maghreb', 'OTHER', 50, 50, False, True, 4),
    (13, u'Iberia', 'OTHER', 52, 52, False, True, 6),
    (13, u'Rey', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, True, 33),
    (5, u'Region', 'OTHER', 26, 26, False, True, 17),
    (5, u'Sub', 'OTHER', 28, 28, False, True, 19),
    (73, u'Intertropical Convergence Zone', 'OTHER', 23, 25, False, True, 12),
    (16, u'Cenchrus', 'OTHER', 30, 30, False, True, 8),
    (16, u'Chenopodiaceae', 'OTHER', 24, 24, False, True, 14),
    (83, u'South Saharan', 'OTHER', 1, 2, False, True, 21),
    (149, u'Tuareg', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, True, 14),
    (12, u'Africa', u'LOCATION', 38, 38, False, False, 13),
    (12, u'Mediterranean', u'LOCATION', 28, 28, False, False, 33),
    (12, u'Sahara', u'LOCATION', 25, 25, False, False, 39),
    (12, u'Cyrenaica', u'LOCATION', 19, 19, False, False, 51),
    (12, u'Egypt', u'LOCATION', 11, 11, False, False, 67),
    (12, u'Mediterranean Sea', u'LOCATION', 8, 9, False, False, 71),
    (12, u'Sahara', u'LOCATION', 5, 5, False, False, 79),
    (13, u'Sahara', u'LOCATION', 20, 20, False, False, 26),
    (13, u'Robert Capot', u'PERSON', 10, 11, False, False, 35),
    (13, u'Frank White', u'PERSON', 6, 7, False, False, 39),
    (5, u'Niger River valley', u'LOCATION', 21, 23, False, False, 12),
    (5, u'Sudan', u'LOCATION', 25, 25, False, False, 16),
    (5, u'Saharan Africa', u'LOCATION', 30, 31, False, False, 21),
    (39, u'Sahara', u'LOCATION', 39, 39, False, False, 4),
    (39, u'Sahara', u'LOCATION', 7, 7, False, False, 28),
    (73, u'3,93', 'NUMBER', 39, 41, False, False, 28),
    (73, u'9,84', 'NUMBER', 48, 50, False, False, 37),
    (15, u'Africa', u'LOCATION', 26, 26, False, False, 16),
    (16, u'Cornulaca', u'LOCATION', 14, 14, False, False, 24),
    (16, u'Sahara', u'LOCATION', 5, 5, False, False, 33),
    (83, u'Sahara', u'LOCATION', 20, 20, False, False, 3),
    (149, u'Sahara', u'LOCATION', 4, 4, False, False, 3),
    (5, u'Sahel', 'OTHER', 9, 9, True, True, 0),
    (39, u'Sahel', 'OTHER', 35, 35, True, True, 0),
    (15, u'Sahel', 'OTHER', 10, 10, True, True, 0),
    (16, u'Sahel', 'OTHER', 38, 38, True, True, 0),
    (83, u'Sahel', 'OTHER', 23, 23, True, True, 0),
    (149, u'Sahel', 'OTHER', 1, 1, True, True, 0),
    (73, u'Sahel', u'LOCATION', 11, 11, True, False, 0)]
question: What kind of climate does the Sahel have?
expected: dry tropical
expected sentence: To the south, the Sahara is bounded by the Sahel, a belt of dry tropical savanna with a summer rainy season that extends across Africa from east to west.
question open class words: ['sahel', 'kind', 'does', 'have', 'climate']



all results:
[   (57, u'Americans', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, True, 53),
    (57, u'American', 'OTHER', 45, 45, False, True, 205),
    (130, u'Atlas', 'OTHER', 25, 25, False, True, None),
    (142, u'Moon', 'OTHER', 27, 27, False, True, 16),
    (82, u'Vanguard', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, True, 31),
    (101, u'Military Liaison Committee', 'OTHER', 6, 8, False, True, 16),
    (101, u'President', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, True, 18),
    (101, u'Civilian', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, True, 22),
    (296, u'Almaz', 'OTHER', 26, 26, False, True, 14),
    (5, u'October', 'OTHER', 11, 11, False, True, 19),
    (5, u'April', 'OTHER', 36, 36, False, True, 69),
    (88, u'Soviets', 'OTHER', 27, 27, False, True, 13),
    (170, u'President', 'OTHER', 16, 16, False, True, 19),
    (170, u'Moon', 'OTHER', 35, 35, False, True, 19),
    (   170,
        u'United Nations General Assembly',
        11,
        14,
        True,
        23),
    (170, u'September', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 49),
    (14, u'General', 'OTHER', 6, 6, False, True, 4),
    (14, u'Second World War', 'OTHER', 2, 4, False, True, 6),
    (14, u'Peenem\xfcnde', 'OTHER', 26, 26, False, True, 16),
    (80, u'C', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, True, 11),
    (80, u'Jupiter', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, True, 13),
    (83, u'Cape Canaveral Air Force Station', 'OTHER', 11, 15, False, True, 1),
    (83, u'December', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 13),
    (129, u'US Air Force', 'OTHER', 1, 3, False, True, 0),
    (129, u'Man', 'OTHER', 18, 18, False, True, 15),
    (129, u'Space Soonest', 'OTHER', 20, 21, False, True, 17),
    (0, u'USSR', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, True, 5),
    (0, u'Cold War', 'OTHER', 11, 12, False, True, 9),
    (4, u'August', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, True, 15),
    (4, u'International Geophysical Year', 'OTHER', 29, 31, False, True, 35),
    (52, u'American', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, True, 19),
    (52, u'Strategic Air Command', 'OTHER', 25, 27, False, True, 25),
    (57, u'1947', 'NUMBER', 27, 27, False, False, 97),
    (57, u'Stalin', u'PERSON', 28, 28, False, False, 103),
    (130, u'one', 'NUMBER', 7, 7, False, False, None),
    (130, u'nine candidate', 'NUMBER', 33, 34, False, False, None),
    (142, u'Kennedy', u'PERSON', 7, 7, False, False, 4),
    (82, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 8, 9, False, False, 30),
    (56, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 1, 2, False, False, 66),
    (5, u'1', 'NUMBER', 18, 18, False, False, 33),
    (5, u'12,1961', 'NUMBER', 37, 39, False, False, 71),
    (170, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 21, 22, False, False, 7),
    (170, u'20,1963', 'NUMBER', 2, 4, False, False, 43),
    (13, u'Von Braun', u'PERSON', 0, 1, False, False, 27),
    (14, u'Dornberger', u'PERSON', 7, 7, False, False, 3),
    (14, u'Zanssen', u'PERSON', 20, 20, False, False, 10),
    (14, u'von Braun', u'PERSON', 32, 33, False, False, 22),
    (78, u'Eisenhower', u'PERSON', 0, 0, False, False, 22),
    (83, u'6,1957', 'NUMBER', 2, 4, False, False, 10),
    (4, u'2,1955', 'NUMBER', 5, 7, False, False, 9),
    (4, u'four days', 'NUMBER', 18, 19, False, False, 13),
    (82, u'Soviet', 'OTHER', 1, 1, True, True, 31),
    (52, u'Soviet', 'OTHER', 7, 7, True, True, 11),
    (57, u'Soviet Union', u'LOCATION', 11, 12, True, False, 25),
    (57, u'Soviet', u'LOCATION', 23, 23, True, False, 73),
    (142, u'US', u'LOCATION', 37, 37, True, False, 26),
    (56, u'Soviet Union', u'LOCATION', 21, 22, True, False, 7),
    (5, u'Soviet Union', u'LOCATION', 1, 2, True, False, 0),
    (5, u'US', u'LOCATION', 5, 5, True, False, 7),
    (5, u'US', u'LOCATION', 24, 24, True, False, 45),
    (170, u'Soviet Union', u'LOCATION', 25, 26, True, False, 0),
    (83, u'US', u'LOCATION', 25, 25, True, False, 11),
    (0, u'Soviet Union', u'LOCATION', 16, 17, True, False, 0),
    (0, u'US', u'LOCATION', 26, 26, True, False, 19),
question open class words: ['force', 'did', 'larger', 'soviet', 'union', 'much', 'fleet', 'military', 'type', 'possess']



all results:
[   (205, u'Moon', 'OTHER', 24, 24, False, True, 130),
    (205, u'Other Celestial Bodies', 'OTHER', 26, 28, False, True, 136),
    (205, u'UN', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 200),
    (205, u'October', 'OTHER', 55, 55, False, True, 448),
    (209, u'USSR', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, True, 13),
    (209, u'Apollo', 'OTHER', 25, 25, False, True, 39),
    (209, u'January', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 57),
    (209, u'Gus', 'OTHER', 32, 32, False, True, 67),
    (209, u'White', 'OTHER', 41, 41, False, True, 103),
    (209, u'February', 'OTHER', 71, 71, False, True, 223),
    (77, u'International Geophysical Year', 'OTHER', 32, 34, False, True, 31),
    (203, u'December', 'OTHER', 43, 43, False, True, 107),
    (203, u'Political Committee', 'OTHER', 35, 36, False, True, 112),
    (203, u'USSR', 'OTHER', 27, 27, False, True, 123),
    (203, u'Peaceful Uses', 'OTHER', 16, 17, False, True, 151),
    (203, u'Second National Conference', 'OTHER', 11, 13, False, True, 171),
    (203, u'Vice President', 'OTHER', 6, 7, False, True, 201),
    (203, u'May', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 231),
    (314, u'Eastern European', 'OTHER', 18, 19, False, True, 7),
    (314, u'USSR', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, True, 26),
    (   72,
        'OTHER',
        6,
        11,
        False,
        True,
        None),
    (72, u'Leonid I', 'OTHER', 16, 17, False, True, None),
    (72, u'Soviet', 'OTHER', 26, 26, False, True, None),
    (11, u'Lieutenant Colonel', 'OTHER', 13, 14, False, True, 61),
    (11, u'Munitions Branch', 'OTHER', 10, 11, False, True, 67),
    (11, u'Ballistics', 'OTHER', 8, 8, False, True, 73),
    (21, u'American', 'OTHER', 43, 43, False, True, 30),
    (21, u'German', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, True, 74),
    (21, u'Allies', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, True, 104),
    (139, u'NASA', 'OTHER', 38, 38, False, True, 9),
    (139, u'April', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, True, 24),
    (73, u'Space Race', 'OTHER', 39, 40, False, True, 29),
    (73, u'Earth', 'OTHER', 27, 27, False, True, 31),
    (73, u'Americans', 'OTHER', 25, 25, False, True, 35),
    (73, u'Soviet Academy of Sciences', 'OTHER', 11, 14, False, True, 71),
    (73, u'August', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 123),
    (127, u'Cosmonautics Day', 'OTHER', 4, 5, False, True, 2),
    (127, u'USSR', 'OTHER', 8, 8, False, True, 6),
    (127, u'Commemorative Dates', 'OTHER', 22, 23, False, True, 20),
    (176, u'Apollo', 'OTHER', 31, 31, False, True, 8),
    (176, u'January', 'OTHER', 10, 10, False, True, 29),
    (176, u'Moon', 'OTHER', 6, 6, False, True, 33),
    (99, u'Space Act', 'OTHER', 19, 20, False, True, 4),
    (99, u'National Aeronautics', 'OTHER', 16, 17, False, True, 9),
    (99, u'July', 'OTHER', 28, 28, False, True, 13),
    (99, u'Majority Leader', 'OTHER', 5, 6, False, True, 31),
    (99, u'Congress', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, True, 43),
    (202, u'Peaceful Uses', 'OTHER', 32, 33, False, True, 26),
    (202, u'United Nations', 'OTHER', 23, 24, False, True, 35),
    (202, u'USSR', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, True, 73),
    (36, u'WW II', 'OTHER', 80, 81, False, True, 12),
    (36, u'He', 'OTHER', 45, 45, False, True, 23),
    (36, u'World War I', 'OTHER', 41, 43, False, True, 25),
    (36, u'American', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 67),
    (98, u'US Congress', 'OTHER', 24, 25, False, True, 33),
    (98, u'April', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 80),
    (102, u'NASA', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, True, 7),
    (102, u'October', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 33),
    (189, u'EVA', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, True, None),
    (153, u'Mercury', 'OTHER', 6, 6, False, True, 4),
    (153, u'Aurora', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, True, 11),
    (153, u'May', 'OTHER', 16, 16, False, True, 14),
    (153, u'October', 'OTHER', 30, 30, False, True, 28),
    (153, u'Faith', 'OTHER', 39, 39, False, True, 37),
    (209, u'27,1967', 'NUMBER', 2, 4, False, False, 45),
    (209, u'Virgil', u'PERSON', 30, 30, False, False, 59),
    (209, u'Grissom', u'PERSON', 34, 34, False, False, 75),
    (209, u'Roger Chaffee', u'PERSON', 45, 46, False, False, 119),
    (209, u'21 launch', 'NUMBER', 72, 73, False, False, 227),
    (77, u'58', 'NUMBER', 31, 31, False, False, 29),
    (203, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 23, 24, False, False, 125),
    (314, u'1991', 'NUMBER', 6, 6, False, False, 20),
    (72, u'Four days', 'NUMBER', 0, 1, False, False, None),
    (72, u'Copenhagen', u'LOCATION', 13, 13, False, False, None),
    (72, u'Sedov', u'PERSON', 19, 19, False, False, None),
    (11, u'Versailles', u'LOCATION', 53, 53, False, False, 17),
    (11, u'Leo Zanssen', u'PERSON', 30, 31, False, False, 27),
    (11, u'Walter Dornberger', u'PERSON', 27, 28, False, False, 33),
    (11, u'Karl Emil Becker', u'PERSON', 15, 17, False, False, 55),
    (139, u'America', u'LOCATION', 26, 26, False, False, 3),
    (139, u'Johnson', u'PERSON', 16, 16, False, False, 13),
    (139, u'20,1961', 'NUMBER', 6, 8, False, False, 21),
    (127, u'Russia', u'LOCATION', 15, 15, False, False, 13),
    (127, u'Russia', u'LOCATION', 25, 25, False, False, 23),
    (176, u'two craft', 'NUMBER', 44, 45, False, False, 5),
    (176, u'Moon', u'PERSON', 57, 57, False, False, 18),
    (176, u'1962', 'NUMBER', 11, 11, False, False, 28),
    (99, u'29,1958', 'NUMBER', 29, 31, False, False, 15),
    (99, u'Johnson', u'PERSON', 10, 10, False, False, 23),
    (36, u'1921', 'NUMBER', 54, 54, False, False, 14),
    (36, u'1914', 'NUMBER', 16, 16, False, False, 52),
    (36, u'Goddard', u'PERSON', 6, 6, False, False, 62),
    (36, u'Robert H', u'PERSON', 3, 4, False, False, 64),
    (98, u'2,1958', 'NUMBER', 2, 4, False, False, 71),
    (153, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 1, 2, False, False, 0),
    (153, u'24,1962', 'NUMBER', 17, 19, False, False, 15),
    (153, u'Glenn', u'PERSON', 21, 21, False, False, 19),
    (153, u'3,1962', 'NUMBER', 31, 33, False, False, 29),
    (153, u'15,1963', 'NUMBER', 43, 45, False, False, 41),
    (153, u'22 orbits', 'NUMBER', 47, 48, False, False, 45),
    (153, u'32.4 hours', 'NUMBER', 50, 53, False, False, 48),
    (13, u'Von Braun', u'PERSON', 0, 1, False, False, 11),
    (205, u'Exploration', 'OTHER', 15, 15, True, True, 98),
    (205, u'Use', 'OTHER', 17, 17, True, True, 98),
    (205, u'Outer Space', 'OTHER', 19, 20, True, True, 98),
    (205, u'States', 'OTHER', 12, 12, True, True, 104),
    (205, u'Activities', 'OTHER', 10, 10, True, True, 112),
    (205, u'Principles Governing', 'OTHER', 7, 8, True, True, 122),
    (205, u'Treaty', 'OTHER', 5, 5, True, True, 152),
    (209, u'Outer Space Treaty', 'OTHER', 15, 17, True, True, 3),
    (203, u'Space', 'OTHER', 19, 19, True, True, 141),
    (11, u'Treaty', 'OTHER', 51, 51, True, True, 13),
    (202, u'Outer Space', 'OTHER', 35, 36, True, True, 24),
    (176, u'three', 'NUMBER', 28, 28, True, False, 11),
    (153, u'three', 'NUMBER', 4, 4, True, False, 2)]
question open class words: ['principles', 'states', 'use', 'outer', 'space', 'was', 'activities', 'governing', 'date', 'countries', 'signed', 'treaty', 'exploration']



all results:
[   (121, u'Windows Media Center', 'OTHER', 18, 20, False, True, 71),
    (121, u'DVD', 'OTHER', 22, 22, False, True, 79),
    (121, u'Pro Pack', 'OTHER', 31, 32, False, True, 86),
    (121, u'Windows Media Center', 'OTHER', 5, 7, False, True, 98),
    (121, u'Media Center Pack', 'OTHER', 46, 48, False, True, 113),
    (136, u'Add', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, True, 26),
    (141, u'January', 'OTHER', 37, 37, False, True, 35),
    (141, u'Microsoft', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, True, 39),
    (95, u'Enterprise', 'OTHER', 16, 16, False, True, 29),
    (95, u'Windows RT', 'OTHER', 27, 28, False, True, 37),
    (95, u'Windows Store', 'OTHER', 7, 8, False, True, 40),
    (42, u'European', 'OTHER', 26, 26, False, True, 32),
    (42, u'Enterprise', 'OTHER', 54, 54, False, True, 40),
    (142, u'Home Basic', 'OTHER', 11, 12, False, True, 25),
    (142, u'Home Premium', 'OTHER', 14, 15, False, True, 25),
    (142, u'Professional', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, True, 26),
    (142, u'January', 'OTHER', 27, 27, False, True, 26),
    (142, u'PCs', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, True, 36),
    (144, u'Windows Media Center', 'OTHER', 5, 7, False, True, 5),
    (135, u'Windows Media Center', 'OTHER', 23, 25, False, True, 0),
    (135, u'V', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, True, 14),
    (135, u'Hyper', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, True, 16),
    (135, u'BitLocker', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, True, 18),
    (54, u'Windows Phone', 'OTHER', 33, 34, False, True, 13),
    (54, u'Windows Everywhere', 'OTHER', 23, 24, False, True, 15),
    (54, u'Microsoft', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, True, 41),
    (54, u'June', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 83),
    (94, u'Windows Store', 'OTHER', 13, 14, False, True, 30),
    (139, u'Windows RT', 'OTHER', 9, 10, False, True, 14),
    (139, u'ARM', 'OTHER', 6, 6, False, True, 18),
    (154, u'DVDs', 'OTHER', 24, 24, False, True, 46),
    (203, u'SKU', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, True, 71),
    (55, u'USB', 'OTHER', 56, 56, False, True, 91),
    (55, u'Windows To Go', 'OTHER', 63, 65, False, True, 99),
    (55, u'Hybrid Boot', 'OTHER', 18, 19, False, True, 104),
    (55, u'UEFI', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, True, 119),
    (158, u'Windows Update', 'OTHER', 34, 35, False, True, 64),
    (158, u'ARM', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, True, 65),
    (158, u'Office', 'OTHER', 29, 29, False, True, 65),
    (158, u'Windows Store', 'OTHER', 38, 39, False, True, 73),
    (158, u'RT', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 77),
    (30, u'Consumer Preview', 'OTHER', 10, 11, False, True, 8),
    (30, u'February', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 23),
    (52, u'English', 'OTHER', 22, 22, False, True, 43),
    (53, u'Microsoft', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, True, 22),
    (53, u'May', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 28),
    (53, u'Apple', 'OTHER', 45, 45, False, True, 60),
    (53, u'Get', 'OTHER', 49, 49, False, True, 68),
    (53, u'Mac', 'OTHER', 51, 51, False, True, 72),
    (141, u'US', u'LOCATION', 18, 18, False, False, 35),
    (141, u'199.99', 'NUMBER', 58, 60, False, False, 63),
    (154, u'64', 'NUMBER', 12, 12, False, False, 50),
    (154, u'32', 'NUMBER', 8, 8, False, False, 54),
    (203, u'8.1', 'NUMBER', 15, 17, False, False, 45),
    (30, u'8250', 'NUMBER', 21, 21, False, False, 17),
    (52, u'8 devices', 'NUMBER', 9, 10, False, False, 42),
    (52, u'Allison Brown', u'PERSON', 28, 29, False, False, 42),
    (52, u'8 devices', 'NUMBER', 52, 53, False, False, 45),
    (53, u'2013', 'NUMBER', 2, 2, False, False, 26),
    (149, u'8.1', 'NUMBER', 13, 15, False, False, 11),
    (121, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 14, 14, True, True, 79),
    (121, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 40, 40, True, True, 97),
    (121, u'Pro', 'OTHER', 42, 42, True, True, 103),
    (121, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 54, 54, True, True, 139),
    (121, u'Pro', 'OTHER', 56, 56, True, True, 149),
    (136, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 17, 17, True, True, 22),
    (136, u'Pro', 'OTHER', 19, 19, True, True, 24),
    (136, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 24, 24, True, True, 29),
    (136, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 2, 2, True, True, 37),
    (141, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 9, 9, True, True, 35),
    (141, u'Pro', 'OTHER', 11, 11, True, True, 35),
    (141, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 44, 44, True, True, 35),
    (141, u'Pro', 'OTHER', 55, 55, True, True, 57),
    (133, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 18, 18, True, True, 22),
    (133, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 22, 22, True, True, 26),
    (133, u'Pro', 'OTHER', 24, 24, True, True, 32),
    (95, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 14, 14, True, True, 29),
    (95, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 23, 23, True, True, 29),
    (95, u'Pro', 'OTHER', 25, 25, True, True, 33),
    (42, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 18, 18, True, True, 32),
    (42, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 50, 50, True, True, 32),
    (42, u'Pro', 'OTHER', 52, 52, True, True, 36),
    (142, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 9, 9, True, True, 26),
    (142, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 35, 35, True, True, 26),
    (142, u'Pro', 'OTHER', 37, 37, True, True, 30),
    (144, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 12, 12, True, True, 7),
    (144, u'Pro', 'OTHER', 14, 14, True, True, 11),
    (135, u'Pro', 'OTHER', 3, 3, True, True, 20),
    (54, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 30, 30, True, True, 10),
    (94, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 3, 3, True, True, 41),
    (94, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 34, 34, True, True, 52),
    (139, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 3, 3, True, True, 21),
    (139, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 18, 18, True, True, 24),
    (154, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 20, 20, True, True, 42),
    (154, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 5, 5, True, True, 57),
    (154, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 47, 47, True, True, 69),
    (203, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 35, 35, True, True, 29),
    (203, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 43, 43, True, True, 37),
    (203, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 14, 14, True, True, 50),
    (55, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 26, 26, True, True, 91),
    (55, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 59, 59, True, True, 91),
    (55, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 5, 5, True, True, 133),
    (158, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 7, 7, True, True, 65),
    (30, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 8, 8, True, True, 9),
    (30, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 17, 17, True, True, 9),
    (52, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 8, 8, True, True, 43),
    (52, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 51, 51, True, True, 43),
    (53, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 11, 11, True, True, 8),
    (53, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 19, 19, True, True, 8),
    (149, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 3, 3, True, True, 9),
    (149, u'8', 'NUMBER', 4, 4, True, False, 9)]
question: What extras does Windows 8 Pro have?
expected: BitLocker, Hyper-V, the ability to join a domain, and the ability to install Windows Media Center as a paid add-on
expected sentence: For example, Pro added BitLocker, Hyper-V, the ability to join a domain, and the ability to install Windows Media Center as a paid add-on.
actual: (121, u'Windows Media Center', 'OTHER', 18, 20, False, True, 71)
question open class words: ['windows', 'does', 'have']



all results:
[   (161, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 26, 26, False, True, 32),
    (161, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, True, 38),
    (98, u'Windows Store', 'OTHER', 22, 23, False, True, 9),
    (98, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, True, 18),
    (98, u'Modern UI', 'OTHER', 7, 8, False, True, 24),
    (42, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 18, 18, False, True, None),
    (42, u'Enterprise N', 'OTHER', 20, 21, False, True, None),
    (42, u'European', 'OTHER', 26, 26, False, True, None),
    (42, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 50, 50, False, True, None),
    (42, u'Pro', 'OTHER', 52, 52, False, True, None),
    (42, u'Enterprise', 'OTHER', 54, 54, False, True, None),
    (213, u'Build', 'OTHER', 8, 8, False, True, None),
    (213, u'June', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, True, None),
    (167, u'Windows Phone', 'OTHER', 34, 35, False, True, 11),
    (167, u'ARM', 'OTHER', 50, 50, False, True, 28),
    (167, u'ARM', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, True, 34),
    (167, u'The Verge', 'OTHER', 5, 6, False, True, 60),
    (167, u'Android', 'OTHER', 70, 70, False, True, 68),
    (167, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 72, 72, False, True, 72),
    (1, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 10, 10, False, True, 4),
    (1, u'Metro', 'OTHER', 18, 18, False, True, 4),
    (1, u'Start', 'OTHER', 24, 24, False, True, 10),
    (1, u'Windows Store', 'OTHER', 70, 71, False, True, 56),
    (3, u'SmartScreen', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, True, 1),
    (3, u'UEFI Secure Boot', 'OTHER', 24, 26, False, True, 8),
    (3, u'UEFI', 'OTHER', 31, 31, False, True, 15),
    (129, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 16, 16, False, True, 16),
    (129, u'PC', 'OTHER', 32, 32, False, True, 32),
    (9, u'CEO', 'OTHER', 18, 18, False, True, 1),
    (9, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 28, 28, False, True, 11),
    (215, u'OEMs', 'OTHER', 36, 36, False, True, 4),
    (215, u'RTM', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, True, 15),
    (215, u'Plus', 'OTHER', 10, 10, False, True, 22),
    (215, u'TechNet', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, True, 23),
    (215, u'MSDN Plus', 'OTHER', 6, 7, False, True, 25),
    (141, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, True, 2),
    (141, u'January', 'OTHER', 37, 37, False, True, 30),
    (141, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 44, 44, False, True, 37),
    (141, u'Pro', 'OTHER', 55, 55, False, True, 48),
    (216, u'RTM', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, True, 7),
    (216, u'MSDN', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, True, 10),
    (131, u'March', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 5),
    (22, u'Confidential', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, True, 1),
    (22, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, True, 11),
    (153, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, True, 6),
    (153, u'SKU', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, True, 8),
    (153, u'OEM', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, True, 11),
    (157, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 8, 8, False, True, 8),
    (30, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 8, 8, False, True, 2),
    (30, u'February', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 5),
    (30, u'Windows', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, True, 11),
    (163, u'Building Windows', 'OTHER', 8, 9, False, True, 4),
    (163, u'At', 'OTHER', 31, 31, False, True, 18),
    (213, u'26,2013', 'NUMBER', 22, 24, False, False, None),
    (129, u'8', 'NUMBER', 17, 17, False, False, 17),
    (9, u'Steve Ballmer', u'PERSON', 19, 20, False, False, 2),
    (141, u'US', u'LOCATION', 18, 18, False, False, 11),
    (141, u'31,2013', 'NUMBER', 38, 40, False, False, 31),
    (153, u'8.1', 'NUMBER', 15, 17, False, False, 3),
    (153, u'Bing', u'PERSON', 23, 23, False, False, 3),
    (153, u'8.1', 'NUMBER', 1, 3, False, False, 17),
    (28, u'535,000 downloads', 'NUMBER', 7, 10, False, False, 5),
    (30, u'8250', 'NUMBER', 21, 21, False, False, 15),
    (197, u'100 million licenses', 'NUMBER', 13, 16, False, False, 6),
    (197, u'six months', 'NUMBER', 19, 20, False, False, 12),
    (163, u'8 blog', 'NUMBER', 10, 11, False, False, 2),
    (163, u'Tony Mangefeste', u'PERSON', 15, 16, False, False, 2),
    (161, u'Microsoft', 'OTHER', 7, 7, True, True, 32),
    (161, u'Microsoft', 'OTHER', 39, 39, True, True, 32),
    (98, u'Microsoft', 'OTHER', 32, 32, True, True, 0),
    (167, u'Microsoft', 'OTHER', 30, 30, True, True, 12),
    (167, u'Microsoft', 'OTHER', 42, 42, True, True, 12),
    (1, u'Microsoft', 'OTHER', 14, 14, True, True, 0),
    (3, u'Microsoft', 'OTHER', 16, 16, True, True, 0),
    (129, u'Microsoft', 'OTHER', 0, 0, True, True, 0),
    (9, u'Microsoft', 'OTHER', 17, 17, True, True, 0),
    (215, u'Microsoft', 'OTHER', 32, 32, True, True, 0),
    (141, u'Microsoft', 'OTHER', 7, 7, True, True, 0),
    (216, u'Microsoft', 'OTHER', 5, 5, True, True, 0),
    (131, u'Microsoft', 'OTHER', 6, 6, True, True, 0),
    (22, u'Microsoft', 'OTHER', 13, 13, True, True, 0),
    (153, u'Microsoft', 'OTHER', 20, 20, True, True, 0),
    (28, u'Microsoft', 'OTHER', 2, 2, True, True, 0),
    (157, u'Microsoft', 'OTHER', 0, 0, True, True, 0),
    (30, u'Microsoft', 'OTHER', 6, 6, True, True, 0),
    (197, u'Microsoft', 'OTHER', 7, 7, True, True, 0),
    (163, u'Microsoft', 'OTHER', 13, 13, True, True, 0)]
question: What ideology does Microsoft follow?
expected: to provide customers with the best experience first, and allow them to make decisions themselves
expected sentence: Microsoft's philosophy is to provide customers with the best experience first, and allow them to make decisions themselves."
question open class words: ['ideology', 'does', 'follow', 'microsoft']



all results:
[   (167, u'Sell', 'OTHER', 8, 8, False, True, 201),
    (98, u'Freud', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 37),
    (206, u'Western', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, True, 7),
    (210, u'Bockting', 'OTHER', 44, 44, False, True, 40),
    (33, u'Lesbian Task Force', 'OTHER', 17, 19, False, True, 0),
    (33, u'National Gay', 'OTHER', 14, 15, False, True, 2),
    (34, u'Voeller', u'PERSON', 0, 0, False, False, 8),
    (111, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 2, 3, False, False, None),
    (210, u'1987', 'NUMBER', 40, 40, False, False, 32),
    (210, u'1988', 'NUMBER', 46, 46, False, False, 44),
    (210, u'Bagemihl', u'PERSON', 0, 0, False, False, 48),
    (210, u'1989 ).', 'NUMBER', 50, 51, False, False, 52),
    (33, u'Bruce Voeller', u'PERSON', 7, 8, False, False, 9),
    (33, u'7 %', 'NUMBER', 46, 47, False, False, 29)]
question: What do some lesbian woman see as important part of the sexual orientation?
expected: choice
expected sentence: Some studies report that "[a number of] lesbian women, and some heterosexual women as well, perceive choice as an important element in their sexual orientations."
question open class words: ['do', 'woman', 'orientation', 'see', 'important', 'part', 'sexual', 'lesbian']



all results:
[   (74, u'Sexual Orientation', 'OTHER', 4, 5, False, True, 2),
    (74, u'Sell Assessment', 'OTHER', 1, 2, False, True, 5),
    (74, u'Kinsey Scale', 'OTHER', 18, 19, False, True, 11),
    (74, u'Klein Sexual Orientation Grid', 'OTHER', 21, 24, False, True, 14),
    (132, u'12 questions', 'NUMBER', 4, 5, False, False, 3),
    (169, u'SASO', 'OTHER', 4, 4, True, True, 0),
    (74, u'SASO', 'OTHER', 7, 7, True, True, 0),
    (75, u'SASO', 'OTHER', 18, 18, True, True, 0),
    (132, u'SASO', 'OTHER', 1, 1, True, True, 0)]
question: What does SASO stand for?
expected: Sell Assessment of Sexual Orientation
expected sentence: The Sell Assessment of Sexual Orientation (SASO) was developed to address the major concerns with the Kinsey Scale and Klein Sexual Orientation Grid and as such, measures sexual orientation on a continuum, considers various dimensions of sexual orientation, and considers homosexuality and heterosexuality separately.
actual: (74, u'Sexual Orientation', 'OTHER', 4, 5, False, True, 2)
question open class words: ['does', 'stand', 'saso']



all results:
[   (65, u'AAC', 'OTHER', 56, 56, False, True, 2),
    (65, u'MPEG', 'OTHER', 53, 53, False, True, 5),
    (   65,
        u'Binaural Masking Level Depression',
        'OTHER',
        27,
        30,
        False,
        True,
        28),
    (206, u'AAC', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, True, None),
    (206, u'MP2', 'OTHER', 8, 8, False, True, None),
    (206, u'MP3', 'OTHER', 18, 18, False, True, None),
    (99, u'MPEG', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, None),
    (99, u'MP3', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, True, None),
    (145, u'CD', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, True, 31),
    (145, u'MP3', 'OTHER', 28, 28, False, True, 64),
    (210, u'MP3', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, True, 27),
    (0, u'MP3', 'OTHER', 16, 16, False, True, 19),
    (0, u'Audio Layer III', 'OTHER', 7, 9, False, True, 33),
    (0, u'MPEG', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, True, 43),
    (0, u'MPEG', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, True, 51),
    (139, u'Diner', 'OTHER', 36, 36, False, True, 13),
    (139, u'MP3', 'OTHER', 27, 27, False, True, 15),
    (139, u'MP3', 'OTHER', 47, 47, False, True, 25),
    (139, u'Diner', 'OTHER', 18, 18, False, True, 33),
    (140, u'MP3', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, True, 8),
    (140, u'Proceedings', 'OTHER', 30, 30, False, True, 40),
    (   140,
        u'International Computer Music Conference',
        33,
        36,
        True,
        46),
    (25, u'February', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, True, 12),
    (62, u'CD', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, True, 22),
    (62, u'Diner', 'OTHER', 16, 16, False, True, 22),
    (62, u'MP3', 'OTHER', 23, 23, False, True, 22),
    (138, u'MP3', 'OTHER', 31, 31, False, True, 1),
    (138, u'MP3', 'OTHER', 24, 24, False, True, 8),
    (138, u'The Ghost', 'OTHER', 20, 21, False, True, 11),
    (138, u'MP3', 'OTHER', 6, 6, False, True, 26),
    (13, u'MP3', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 4),
    (   21,
        u'Lincoln Laboratory Technical Report',
        'OTHER',
        30,
        33,
        False,
        True,
        12),
    (149, u'CD', 'OTHER', 8, 8, False, True, 46),
    (65, u'2', 'NUMBER', 55, 55, False, False, 3),
    (65, u'two channels', 'NUMBER', 10, 11, False, False, 47),
    (99, u'1 standard', 'NUMBER', 3, 4, False, False, None),
    (0, u'1', 'NUMBER', 2, 2, False, False, 47),
    (139, u'Tom', u'PERSON', 33, 33, False, False, 13),
    (140, u'2014', 'NUMBER', 29, 29, False, False, 38),
    (25, u'1988', 'NUMBER', 5, 5, False, False, 11),
    (62, u'Suzanne Vega', u'PERSON', 7, 8, False, False, 21),
    (62, u'Tom', u'PERSON', 13, 13, False, False, 22),
    (62, u'Karlheinz Brandenburg', u'PERSON', 0, 1, False, False, 24),
    (138, u'Ryan Maguire', u'PERSON', 14, 15, False, False, 17),
    (21, u'Krasner', u'PERSON', 0, 0, False, False, 18),
    (149, u'1', 'NUMBER', 68, 68, False, False, 14),
    (149, u'1000 bits', 'NUMBER', 37, 38, False, False, 16),
    (149, u'2 channels', 'NUMBER', 34, 35, False, False, 19),
    (149, u'44100 samples', 'NUMBER', 29, 30, False, False, 24),
    (149, u'16 bit', 'NUMBER', 24, 25, False, False, 29),
    (149, u'1,411', 'NUMBER', 14, 16, False, False, 38)]
question: What kind of model is used in this kind of compression?
expected: psychoacoustic
expected sentence: It uses psychoacoustic models to discard or reduce precision of components less audible to human hearing, and then records the remaining information in an efficient manner.
question open class words: ['used', 'compression', 'is', 'kind', 'model']



all results:
[   (159, u'two', 'NUMBER', 10, 10, False, False, 77),
    (159, u'VBR', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, False, 91),
    (154, u'MP3', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, False, 69),
    (96, u'MP3', 'OTHER', 11, 11, False, False, None),
    (97, u'3', 'NUMBER', 5, 5, False, False, None),
    (145, u'44.1 kHz', 'NUMBER', 4, 7, False, False, 43),
    (145, u'CD', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, False, 48),
    (145, u'MP3', 'OTHER', 28, 28, False, False, 90),
    (127, u'Constant Bit Rate', 'OTHER', 19, 21, False, False, 25),
    (127, u'one bit', 'NUMBER', 7, 8, False, False, 34),
    (127, u'CBR', 'OTHER', 23, 23, False, False, 41),
    (127, u'MP3', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, False, 54),
    (3, u'128,000 bit', 'NUMBER', 70, 73, False, False, 181),
    (3, u'1,000', 'NUMBER', 80, 82, False, False, 191),
    (3, u'128 kbit', 'NUMBER', 65, 66, False, False, 194),
    (3, u'1024', 'NUMBER', 85, 85, False, False, 202),
    (3, u'1,411', 'NUMBER', 53, 55, False, False, 210),
    (3, u'2 channels', 'NUMBER', 50, 51, False, False, 224),
    (3, u'16 bits', 'NUMBER', 45, 46, False, False, 239),
    (3, u'44,100 samples', 'NUMBER', 38, 41, False, False, 250),
    (3, u'1 /', 'NUMBER', 22, 23, False, False, 308),
    (3, u'128 kbit', 'NUMBER', 10, 11, False, False, 363),
    (3, u'MP3', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, 420),
    (124, u'MP3', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, False, 32),
    (104, u'LAME', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, False, 40),
    (152, u'Constant Bit Rate', 'OTHER', 10, 12, False, False, 9),
    (152, u'CBR', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, False, 21),
    (152, u'MPEG Layer III', 'OTHER', 1, 3, False, False, 23),
    (99, u'MP3', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, False, 11),
    (99, u'1 standard', 'NUMBER', 3, 4, False, False, 29),
    (99, u'MPEG', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, 35),
    (60, u'2', 'NUMBER', 26, 26, False, False, 50),
    (60, u'Digital Audio Tape', 'OTHER', 34, 36, False, False, 50),
    (60, u'16 bits', 'NUMBER', 21, 22, False, False, 53),
    (60, u'2 channels', 'NUMBER', 18, 19, False, False, 56),
    (60, u'DAT', 'OTHER', 38, 38, False, False, 56),
    (60, u'44.1 kHz', 'NUMBER', 13, 16, False, False, 57),
    (60, u'SP', 'OTHER', 40, 40, False, False, 58),
    (60, u'48 kHz', 'NUMBER', 43, 44, False, False, 60),
    (60, u'2 \xd7', 'NUMBER', 46, 47, False, False, 63),
    (60, u'16 bit', 'NUMBER', 48, 49, False, False, 65),
    (60, u'CD', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, False, 69),
    (60, u'Compact Disc', 'OTHER', 4, 5, False, False, 70),
    (150, u'640 kbit', 'NUMBER', 7, 8, False, False, 13),
    (150, u'LAME', 'OTHER', 16, 16, False, False, 14),
    (150, u'MP3', 'OTHER', 25, 25, False, False, 30),
    (147, u'1', 'NUMBER', 18, 18, False, False, 37)]
question: An average bit rate is used when who choses an average value for the encoder to use?
expected: the user
expected sentence: Average bitrate is VBR implemented as a compromise between the two: the bitrate is allowed to vary for more consistent quality, but is controlled to remain near an average value chosen by the user, for predictable file sizes.
question open class words: ['use', 'used', 'is', 'when', 'value', 'rate', 'choses', 'bit', 'encoder', 'average']



all results:
[   (203, u'SCN', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 10),
    (114, u'two vesicles', 'NUMBER', 9, 10, False, False, 1),
    (201, u'24 hours', 'NUMBER', 14, 15, False, False, 17),
    (5, u'one', 'NUMBER', 4, 4, False, False, 25),
    (75, u'three parts', 'NUMBER', 13, 14, False, False, None),
    (73, u'three swellings', 'NUMBER', 9, 10, False, False, None),
    (113, u'three vesicles', 'NUMBER', 12, 13, False, False, None)]
question: A set of interconnected areas at the base of the forebrain is called what?
expected: basal ganglia
expected sentence: In vertebrates, the reward-punishment system is implemented by a specific set of brain structures, at the heart of which lie the basal ganglia, a set of interconnected areas at the base of the forebrain.
question open class words: ['set', 'is', 'called', 'base', 'interconnected', 'areas']



all results:
[   (48, u'Cambrian', 'OTHER', 16, 16, False, True, 13),
    (11, u'CPU', 'OTHER', 55, 55, False, True, 48),
    (200, u'SCN', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, None),
    (148, u'EEG', 'OTHER', 24, 24, False, True, 42),
    (48, u'485', 'NUMBER', 19, 19, False, False, 16),
    (48, u'540 million years', 'NUMBER', 21, 24, False, False, 18),
    (278, u'Galen', u'PERSON', 3, 3, False, False, 2),
    (278, u'Descartes', u'PERSON', 0, 0, False, False, 5),
    (166, u'1959 paper', 'NUMBER', 9, 10, False, False, 71),
    (166, u'One', 'NUMBER', 0, 0, False, False, 91),
    (174, u'One', 'NUMBER', 0, 0, False, False, 15),
    (166, u'What', 'OTHER', 12, 12, True, True, 67)]
question: The function of the brain from an evolutionary-biological thought is what?
expected: provide coherent control over the actions of an animal
expected sentence: From an evolutionary-biological perspective, the function of the brain is to provide coherent control over the actions of an animal.
question open class words: ['function', 'evolutionary', 'is', 'thought', 'brain']


