all results:
[   (29, u'German States', 'OTHER', 21, 22, False, True, 11.857142857142858),
    (29, u'Stadtteilschule', 'OTHER', 29, 29, False, True, 12.142857142857142),
    (29, u'German', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, True, 12.428571428571429),
    (29, u'Sekundarschule', 'OTHER', 33, 33, False, True, 13.571428571428571),
    (29, u'Education', 'OTHER', 39, 39, False, True, 16.714285714285715),
    (29, u'Education', 'OTHER', 43, 43, False, True, 19.571428571428573),
    (39, u'Abitur', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, True, 2.0),
    (39, u'Gymnasium', 'OTHER', 8, 8, False, True, 6.0),
    (39, u'Abitur', 'OTHER', 11, 11, False, True, 9.0),
    (39, u'Abitur', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, True, 12.0),
    (39, u'Gesamtschule', 'OTHER', 18, 18, False, True, 16.0),
    (39, u'Abitur', 'OTHER', 20, 20, False, True, 18.0),
    (29, u'Hamburg', u'LOCATION', 26, 26, False, False, 11.714285714285714),
    (29, u'Hamburg', u'LOCATION', 31, 31, False, False, 12.714285714285714),
    (29, u'Hamburg', u'LOCATION', 45, 45, False, False, 21.571428571428573),
    (39, u'Abitur', u'PERSON', 4, 4, False, False, 2.0),
    (39, u'Abitur', u'PERSON', 11, 11, False, False, 9.0),
    (39, u'Abitur', u'PERSON', 14, 14, False, False, 12.0),
    (39, u'Abitur', u'PERSON', 20, 20, False, False, 18.0),
    (29, u'Gesamtschulen', 'OTHER', 10, 10, True, True, 14.571428571428571),
    (29, u'Hauptschulen', 'OTHER', 4, 4, True, True, 19.428571428571427),
    (42, u'Gesamtschulen', 'OTHER', 0, 0, True, True, 0.0),
    (29, u'Berlin', u'LOCATION', 24, 24, True, False, 12.0),
    (29, u'Berlin', u'LOCATION', 35, 35, True, False, 14.428571428571429),
    (29, u'Realschulen', u'PERSON', 8, 8, True, False, 16.0),
actual: (29, u'German States', 'OTHER', 21, 22, False, True, 11.857142857142858)
question open class words: ['was', 'combination', 'hauptschulen', 'realschulen', 'gesamtschulen', 'called', 'berlin']



all results:
[   (71, u'1970', u'DATE', 1, 1, False, True, 4.2),
    (66, u'1965', u'DATE', 15, 15, False, True, 7.0),
    (66, u'1965', u'DATE', 7, 7, False, True, 15.0),
    (52, u'1966', u'DATE', 7, 7, False, True, 25.2),
    (28, u'2007', u'DATE', 16, 16, False, True, 9.5),
    (71, u'Conservative', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, False, 7.8),
    (72, u'Mrs Thatcher', u'PERSON', 42, 43, False, False, 3.0),
    (36, u'Education Minister', 'OTHER', 8, 9, False, False, 18.5),
    (36, u'North Rhine-Westphalia', u'LOCATION', 11, 12, False, False, 18.5),
    (36, u'Social Democratic Party', 'OTHER', 44, 46, False, False, 19.0),
    (36, u'Abitur', u'PERSON', 30, 30, False, False, 19.0),
    (36, u'Minister', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, False, 19.0),
    (36, u'Gymnasium', 'OTHER', 26, 26, False, False, 19.0),
    (36, u'Abitur', 'OTHER', 30, 30, False, False, 19.0),
    (36, u'Looking', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, 19.0),
    (   36,
        u'Christian Democratic Union',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        3,
        5,
        False,
        False,
        21.0),
    (36, u'Germany', u'LOCATION', 48, 48, False, False, 22.0),
    (36, u'Barbara Sommer', u'PERSON', 0, 1, False, False, 25.0),
    (36, u'Gymnasium', 'OTHER', 55, 55, False, False, 29.0),
    (66, u'1964–1970', 'NUMBER', 27, 27, False, False, 5.0),
    (66, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 28, 28, False, False, 6.0),
    (66, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, False, 22.0),
    (59, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, False, 3.3333333333333335),
    (11, u'Specialist', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, False, 4.0),
    (   11,
        u'City Technology Colleges',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        8,
        10,
        False,
        False,
        6.0),
    (29, u'Berlin', u'LOCATION', 41, 41, False, False, 2.0),
    (29, u'Hamburg', u'LOCATION', 45, 45, False, False, 2.0),
    (29, u'Berlin', u'LOCATION', 35, 35, False, False, 8.0),
    (29, u'Sekundarschule', 'OTHER', 33, 33, False, False, 10.0),
    (29, u'Hamburg', u'LOCATION', 31, 31, False, False, 12.0),
    (29, u'Stadtteilschule', 'OTHER', 29, 29, False, False, 14.0),
    (29, u'Hamburg', u'LOCATION', 26, 26, False, False, 17.0),
    (29, u'Berlin', u'LOCATION', 24, 24, False, False, 19.0),
    (29, u'German States', 'OTHER', 21, 22, False, False, 21.0),
    (29, u'States', 'OTHER', 22, 22, False, False, 21.0),
    (29, u'German', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, False, 22.0),
    (29, u'Gesamtschulen', 'OTHER', 10, 10, False, False, 33.0),
    (29, u'Realschulen', u'PERSON', 8, 8, False, False, 35.0),
    (29, u'Hauptschulen', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, False, 39.0),
    (   52,
        u'Minister for Education',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        15,
        17,
        False,
        False,
        15.2),
    (52, u'Minister', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, False, 17.2),
    (52, u'Patrick Hillery', u'PERSON', 12, 13, False, False, 19.2),
    (52, u'Ireland', u'LOCATION', 5, 5, False, False, 27.2),
    (52, u'Comprehensive', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, False, 32.2),
    (   9,
        u'Further Education Colleges',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        33,
        35,
        False,
        False,
        9.0),
    (9, u'11–16', 'NUMBER', 20, 20, False, False, 10.0),
    (28, u'State of Brandenburg', u'ORGANIZATION', 2, 4, False, False, 8.5),
    (28, u'50 %', u'PERCENT', 7, 8, False, False, 9.0),
    (28, u'Gesamtschule', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, False, 9.5),
    (28, u'Bavaria', u'LOCATION', 23, 23, False, False, 11.5),
    (28, u'1 %', u'PERCENT', 26, 27, False, False, 14.5),
    (   61,
        u'Minister for Education',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        14,
        16,
        False,
        False,
        4.5),
    (61, u'Minister', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, False, 6.5),
    (61, u'Training Board', u'ORGANIZATION', 27, 28, False, False, 6.5),
    (61, u'two', 'NUMBER', 5, 5, False, False, 15.5),
    (61, u'Community', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, False, 20.5),
    (4, u'German', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, None),
    (4, u'Gesamtschule', 'OTHER', 18, 18, False, False, None),
    (4, u'German Gesamtschule', 'OTHER', 17, 18, False, False, None),
    (4, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 10, 11, False, False, None),
    (4, u'Canada', u'LOCATION', 13, 13, False, False, None),
    (4, u'States', 'OTHER', 11, 11, False, False, None),
    (16, u'England', u'LOCATION', 19, 19, False, False, 4.0),
    (20, u'Academies Programme', u'ORGANIZATION', 4, 5, False, False, 3.0),
    (   20,
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        7,
        12,
        False,
        False,
        6.0),
    (30, u'Mittelschule', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, False, None),
    (30, u'Germany', u'LOCATION', 11, 11, False, False, None),
    (30, u'States', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, False, None),
    (30, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, False, None),
    (31, u'Mittelschule', 'OTHER', 27, 27, False, False, None),
    (31, u'Germany', u'LOCATION', 4, 4, False, False, None),
    (31, u'Hauptschule', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, False, None),
    (31, u'States', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, False, None),
    (   35,
        u'State of North Rhine-Westphalia',
        u'LOCATION',
        9,
        12,
        False,
        False,
        4.5),
    (   35,
        u'North Rhine-Westphalia',
        u'LOCATION',
        11,
        12,
        False,
        False,
        5.833333333333333),
    (35, u'Abitur', u'PERSON', 3, 3, False, False, 6.833333333333333),
    (35, u'Abitur', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, False, 6.833333333333333),
    (35, u'Gesamtschule', 'OTHER', 18, 18, False, False, 9.166666666666666),
    (   71,
        u'Secretary of State for Education',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        5,
        9,
        True,
        False,
        1.4),
    (71, u'Margaret Thatcher', u'PERSON', 2, 3, True, False, 2.4),
    (71, u'State', u'ORGANIZATION', 7, 7, True, False, 2.6),
    (71, u'Education', 'OTHER', 9, 9, True, False, 3.8),
    (36, u'Education', 'OTHER', 8, 8, True, False, 19.0),
    (   66,
        u'Secretary of State for Education',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        20,
        24,
        True,
        False,
        0.6666666666666666),
    (66, u'State', u'ORGANIZATION', 22, 22, True, False, 1.3333333333333333),
    (66, u'Education', 'OTHER', 24, 24, True, False, 2.0),
    (29, u'Education', 'OTHER', 43, 43, True, False, 2.0),
    (29, u'Education', 'OTHER', 39, 39, True, False, 4.0),
    (52, u'Education', 'OTHER', 17, 17, True, False, 15.2),
    (9, u'Education', 'OTHER', 34, 34, True, False, 10.0),
    (28, u'State', u'ORGANIZATION', 2, 2, True, False, 9.5),
    (28, u'State', u'ORGANIZATION', 21, 21, True, False, 9.5),
    (61, u'Education', 'OTHER', 16, 16, True, False, 4.5),
    (61, u'Education', 'OTHER', 25, 25, True, False, 4.5),
    (35, u'State', u'ORGANIZATION', 9, 9, True, False, 5.5)]



all results:
[   (   83,
        u'United States',
        u'LOCATION',
        31,
        32,
        False,
        True,
        20.923076923076923),
    (   83,
        u'Southeastern United States',
        42,
        44,
        27.53846153846154),
    (   83,
        u'United States',
        u'LOCATION',
        43,
        44,
        False,
        True,
        28.384615384615383),
    (50, u'Florida Bay', u'LOCATION', 23, 24, False, True, 6.2),
    (50, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 23, 23, False, True, 6.6),
    (50, u'Miami Springs', u'LOCATION', 35, 36, False, True, 9.0),
    (50, u'Hialeah', u'LOCATION', 38, 38, False, True, 12.0),
    (0, u'Atlantic', u'LOCATION', 17, 17, False, True, 11.0),
    (1, u'Southeastern United States', u'LOCATION', 41, 43, False, True, 18.4),
    (1, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 42, 43, False, True, 18.9),
    (1, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 7, 8, False, True, 42.6),
    (175, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 23, 23, False, True, 7.0),
    (45, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 12, 12, False, True, 8.25),
    (38, u'South Beach', u'LOCATION', 32, 33, False, True, 2.0),
    (38, u'Biscayne Bay', u'LOCATION', 11, 12, False, True, 18.25),
    (   210,
        u'Miami Avenue',
        u'LOCATION',
        21,
        22,
        False,
        True,
        11.714285714285714),
    (144, u'Miami River', u'LOCATION', 30, 31, False, True, 8.8),
    (144, u'Atlantic', u'LOCATION', 3, 3, False, True, 18.2),
    (118, u'South Beach', u'LOCATION', 16, 17, False, True, 8.0),
    (118, u'Basel', u'LOCATION', 10, 10, False, True, 15.0),
    (83, u'Broward', u'ORGANIZATION', 9, 9, False, False, 10.692307692307692),
    (83, u'5.5 million', 'NUMBER', 22, 23, False, False, 16.076923076923077),
    (83, u'million', 'NUMBER', 23, 23, False, False, 16.846153846153847),
    (50, u'Biscayne Aquifer', u'ORGANIZATION', 5, 6, False, False, 20.0),
    (0, u'Spanish', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, False, 15.75),
    (85, u'80 %', u'PERCENT', 6, 7, False, False, 5.4),
    (85, u'80', 'NUMBER', 6, 6, False, False, 6.4),
    (85, u'1960', u'DATE', 1, 1, False, False, 11.4),
    (1, u'U.S. Census Bureau', u'ORGANIZATION', 52, 54, False, False, 18.4),
    (1, u'Census Bureau', u'ORGANIZATION', 53, 54, False, False, 18.9),
    (1, u'Census', 'OTHER', 53, 53, False, False, 19.4),
    (1, u'D.C', 'OTHER', 47, 47, False, False, 19.4),
    (1, u'According', 'OTHER', 49, 49, False, False, 19.4),
    (1, u'5.5 million', 'NUMBER', 78, 79, False, False, 27.9),
    (1, u'430,332', 'NUMBER', 14, 14, False, False, 36.6),
    (37, u'Rock Ridge', 'OTHER', 9, 10, False, False, 6.0),
    (   175,
        u'Florida International University',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        23,
        25,
        False,
        False,
        6.0),
    (175, u'Miami-Dade College', u'ORGANIZATION', 30, 31, False, False, 6.5),
    (175, u'The Beacon', 'OTHER', 27, 28, False, False, 6.5),
    (   175,
        u"University of Miami 's The Miami Hurricane",
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        15,
        21,
        False,
        False,
        6.5),
    (175, u'The Metropolis', 'OTHER', 33, 34, False, False, 7.25),
    (175, u'Barry University', u'ORGANIZATION', 36, 37, False, False, 10.0),
    (175, u'The Buccaneer', 'OTHER', 39, 40, False, False, 13.0),
    (   70,
        u'MiMo Historic District',
        'OTHER',
        33,
        35,
        False,
        False,
        13.666666666666666),
    (70, u'1950s', u'DATE', 46, 46, False, False, 14.666666666666666),
    (70, u'1920s', u'DATE', 27, 27, False, False, 17.0),
    (   70,
        u'Upper East Side',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        19,
        21,
        False,
        False,
        18.333333333333332),
    (70, u'East', 'OTHER', 20, 20, False, False, 19.333333333333332),
    (   70,
        u'Design District',
        'OTHER',
        14,
        15,
        False,
        False,
        20.666666666666668),
    (70, u'Design', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, False, 21.333333333333332),
    (70, u'Midtown', 'OTHER', 11, 11, False, False, 22.333333333333332),
    (87, u'1980s', u'DATE', 22, 22, False, False, 22.0),
    (87, u'1960s', u'DATE', 33, 33, False, False, 33.0),
    (87, u'1990s', u'DATE', 36, 36, False, False, 36.0),
    (45, u'Dry Tortugas', 'OTHER', 26, 27, False, False, 5.75),
    (38, u'South', 'OTHER', 32, 32, False, False, 2.25),
    (116, u'38', 'NUMBER', 16, 16, False, False, None),
    (116, u'$ 17.1 billion', u'MONEY', 34, 36, False, False, None),
    (116, u'million', 'NUMBER', 17, 17, False, False, None),
    (116, u'38 million', 'NUMBER', 16, 17, False, False, None),
    (210, u'Grid', 'OTHER', 11, 11, False, False, 7.714285714285714),
    (210, u'Flagler Street', 'OTHER', 14, 15, False, False, 8.714285714285714),
    (210, u'Avenue', 'OTHER', 22, 22, False, False, 12.428571428571429),
    (31, u'New South', 'OTHER', 11, 12, False, False, 3.0),
    (31, u'South', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, False, 4.0),
    (   118,
        u'Mercedes-Benz Fashion Week',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        24,
        26,
        False,
        False,
        4.333333333333333),
    (   118,
        u'South Beach Wine & Food Festival',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        16,
        21,
        False,
        False,
        5.666666666666667),
    (118, u'South', 'OTHER', 16, 16, False, False, 9.0),
    (   118,
        u'Winter Music Conference',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        12,
        14,
        False,
        False,
        11.0),
    (118, u'Art', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, False, 16.0),
    (118, u'Open', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, False, 18.0),
    (118, u'Sony Ericsson', u'ORGANIZATION', 5, 6, False, False, 19.0),
    (118, u'Sony', u'ORGANIZATION', 5, 5, False, False, 20.0),
    (218, u'Midtown', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, False, 2.3333333333333335),
    (   218,
        u'Julia Tuttle Causeway',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        1,
        3,
        False,
        False,
        4.333333333333333),
    (218, u'Julia Tuttle', u'PERSON', 1, 2, False, False, 5.333333333333333),
    (83, u'Palm Beach', u'LOCATION', 11, 12, True, True, 10.76923076923077),
    (83, u'Miami', u'LOCATION', 1, 1, True, True, 13.615384615384615),
    (50, u'Palm Beach County', u'LOCATION', 19, 21, True, True, 5.8),
    (50, u'Palm Beach', u'LOCATION', 19, 20, True, True, 6.2),
    (50, u'Miami', u'LOCATION', 35, 35, True, True, 9.0),
    (0, u'Miami-Dade County', u'LOCATION', 26, 27, True, True, 8.875),
    (0, u'Miami', u'LOCATION', 0, 0, True, True, 17.75),
    (199, u'Miami-Dade County', u'LOCATION', 14, 15, True, True, 0.8),
    (1, u'Miami', u'LOCATION', 56, 56, True, True, 19.4),
    (1, u'Miami', u'LOCATION', 29, 29, True, True, 23.2),
    (37, u'Miami', u'LOCATION', 19, 19, True, True, 4.6),
    (37, u'Miami', u'LOCATION', 8, 8, True, True, 6.8),
    (51, u'Miami', u'LOCATION', 3, 3, True, True, 0.75),
    (175, u'Miami', u'LOCATION', 20, 20, True, True, 7.5),
    (175, u'Miami', u'LOCATION', 17, 17, True, True, 9.0),
    (70, u'Miami', u'LOCATION', 43, 43, True, True, 11.666666666666666),
    (87, u'Miami', u'LOCATION', 0, 0, True, True, 0.0),
    (45, u'Miami', u'LOCATION', 19, 19, True, True, 1.25),
    (38, u'Miami Beach', u'LOCATION', 29, 30, True, True, 0.75),
    (38, u'Miami', u'LOCATION', 29, 29, True, True, 1.25),
    (210, u'Miami', u'LOCATION', 10, 10, True, True, 7.857142857142857),
    (210, u'Miami', u'LOCATION', 0, 0, True, True, 10.714285714285714),
    (210, u'Miami', u'LOCATION', 21, 21, True, True, 12.0),
    (144, u'Miami', u'LOCATION', 15, 15, True, True, 6.2),
    (144, u'Miami', u'LOCATION', 30, 30, True, True, 8.8),
    (118, u'Miami', u'LOCATION', 27, 27, True, True, 4.666666666666667),
    (218, u'Miami Beach', u'LOCATION', 7, 8, True, True, 0.0),
    (218, u'Miami', u'LOCATION', 7, 7, True, True, 0.3333333333333333),
    (83, u'Miami-Dade', 'OTHER', 7, 7, True, False, 10.846153846153847),
    (83, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, True, False, 14.615384615384615),
    (0, u'Miami-Dade', 'OTHER', 26, 26, True, False, 9.25),
    (85, u'Miami-Dade', 'OTHER', 9, 9, True, False, 3.4),
    (199, u'Miami-Dade', 'OTHER', 14, 14, True, False, 1.4),
    (1, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, True, False, 50.6),
    (37, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, True, False, 14.8),
    (175, u'The', 'OTHER', 27, 27, True, False, 7.0),
    (175, u'Miami-Dade', 'OTHER', 30, 30, True, False, 7.0),
    (175, u'The', 'OTHER', 33, 33, True, False, 7.5),
    (175, u'The', 'OTHER', 19, 19, True, False, 8.0),
    (175, u'The', 'OTHER', 39, 39, True, False, 13.0),
    (70, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, True, False, 31.333333333333332),
    (38, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, True, False, 30.25),
    (218, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, True, False, 7.333333333333333)]
question: Along with Palm Beach and Miami-Dade, what county is part of the Miami-Dade metropolitan area?
expected: Broward
expected sentence: The Miami metropolitan area, which includes Miami-Dade, Broward and Palm Beach counties, had a combined population of more than 5.5 million people, ranked seventh largest in the United States, and is the largest metropolitan area in the Southeastern United States.
question open class words: ['palm', 'beach', 'miami', 'dade', 'county', 'is', 'part', 'miami', 'dade', 'metropolitan', 'area']



all results:
    (9, u'American', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 13.666666666666666),
    (9, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, True, 14.666666666666666),
    (157, u'Chief Executive Magazine', 'OTHER', 0, 2, False, True, 1.5),
    (157, u'Best State', 'OTHER', 8, 9, False, True, 4.5),
    (157, u'State', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, True, 5.5),
    (157, u'Business', 'OTHER', 11, 11, False, True, 7.5),
    (20, u'Cow Ford', 'OTHER', 23, 24, False, True, None),
    (20, u'British', 'OTHER', 20, 20, False, True, None),
    (20, u'Seminole', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, True, None),
    (20, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, True, None),
    (21, u'British', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 8.666666666666666),
    (21, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, True, 9.666666666666666),
    (48, u'Territory', 'OTHER', 20, 20, False, True, 4.666666666666667),
    (30, u'Declaration', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, True, 11.5),
    (46, u'President', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, True, 16.5),
    (94, u'Floridians', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, True, 15.5),
    (102, u'South', 'OTHER', 11, 11, False, True, 2.0),
    (102, u'Americans', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, True, 5.0),
    (102, u'Cuban Americans', 'OTHER', 4, 5, False, True, 5.0),
    (102, u'Cuban', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, True, 6.0),
    (0, u'Spanish', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, True, 3.0),
    (1, u'Straits', 'OTHER', 35, 35, False, True, 2.0),
    (1, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, True, 37.0),
    (6, u'Straits', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, True, 2.0),
    (13, u'Spanish', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, True, 6.0),
    (13, u'Spanish', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 17.0),
    (13, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, True, 18.0),
    (   9,
        u'Everglades National Park',
        u'LOCATION',
        17,
        19,
        False,
        False,
        3.6666666666666665),
    (9, u'Everglades', u'LOCATION', 17, 17, False, False, 4.333333333333333),
    (157, u'2011', u'DATE', 14, 14, False, False, 10.5),
    (20, u'Wacca Pilatka', u'ORGANIZATION', 16, 17, False, False, None),
    (20, u'St. Johns River', u'LOCATION', 4, 6, False, False, None),
    (159, u'2009', u'DATE', 1, 1, False, False, 11.5),
    (   21,
        u'East Florida',
        u'LOCATION',
        10,
        11,
        False,
        False,
        3.6666666666666665),
    (   21,
        u'West Florida',
        u'LOCATION',
        14,
        15,
        False,
        False,
        4.666666666666667),
    (21, u'two', 'NUMBER', 6, 6, False, False, 5.666666666666667),
    (   48,
        u'West Florida',
        u'LOCATION',
        15,
        16,
        False,
        False,
        2.3333333333333335),
    (   48,
        u'East Florida',
        u'LOCATION',
        10,
        11,
        4.333333333333333),
    (48, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 7, 8, False, False, 7.333333333333333),
    (   48,
        u'United States',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        7,
        8,
        False,
        False,
        7.333333333333333),
    (48, u'March 30 , 1822', u'DATE', 1, 4, False, False, 11.333333333333334),
    (30, u'West Florida', u'LOCATION', 4, 5, False, False, 1.0),
    (34, u'Florida Crackers', u'ORGANIZATION', 29, 30, False, False, 7.5),
    (46, u'West Florida', u'LOCATION', 17, 18, False, False, 1.0),
    (46, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 21, 22, False, False, 4.5),
    (46, u'United States', u'ORGANIZATION', 21, 22, False, False, 4.5),
    (46, u'1821', u'DATE', 9, 9, False, False, 7.5),
    (46, u'March 3 , 1821', u'DATE', 6, 9, False, False, 7.5),
    (46, u'3', 'NUMBER', 7, 7, False, False, 9.5),
    (46, u'James Monroe', u'PERSON', 1, 2, False, False, 14.5),
    (94, u'one', 'NUMBER', 32, 32, False, False, 13.5),
    (102, u'South Florida', u'LOCATION', 11, 12, False, False, 1.5),
    (102, u'80 %', u'PERCENT', 1, 2, False, False, 8.0),
    (138, u'40 %', u'PERCENT', 14, 15, False, False, 8.0),
    (138, u'40', 'NUMBER', 14, 14, False, False, 9.0),
    (138, u'20th century', u'DATE', 3, 4, False, False, 19.0),
    (0, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 20, 21, False, False, 20.0),
    (0, u'United States', u'ORGANIZATION', 20, 21, False, False, 20.0),
    (1, u'Straits of Florida', u'LOCATION', 35, 37, False, False, 0.0),
    (1, u'Atlantic Ocean', u'LOCATION', 26, 27, False, False, 10.0),
    (1, u'Georgia', u'LOCATION', 19, 19, False, False, 18.0),
    (1, u'Alabama', u'LOCATION', 17, 17, False, False, 20.0),
    (1, u'Gulf of Mexico', u'LOCATION', 9, 11, False, False, 26.0),
    (2, u'22nd', 'NUMBER', 3, 3, False, False, 3.0),
    (2, u'3rd', 'NUMBER', 8, 8, False, False, 8.0),
    (2, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 20, 21, False, False, 20.0),
    (2, u'United States', u'ORGANIZATION', 20, 21, False, False, 20.0),
    (3, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 18, 19, False, False, 11.0),
    (3, u'United States', u'ORGANIZATION', 18, 19, False, False, 11.0),
    (6, u'Straits of Florida', u'LOCATION', 14, 16, False, False, 0.0),
    (6, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 26, 27, False, False, 10.0),
    (6, u'United States', u'ORGANIZATION', 26, 27, False, False, 10.0),
    (6, u'Gulf of Mexico', u'LOCATION', 4, 6, False, False, 10.0),
    (6, u'1,350 miles', 'NUMBER', 30, 31, False, False, 14.0),
    (6, u'2,170 km', 'NUMBER', 33, 34, False, False, 17.0),
    (6, u'Gulf of Mexico', u'LOCATION', 46, 48, False, False, 30.0),
    (6, u'Atlantic Ocean', u'LOCATION', 51, 52, False, False, 35.0),
    (10, u'Conquistador Hernando de Soto', u'PERSON', 5, 8, False, False, 5.0),
    (10, u'May 1539', u'DATE', 2, 3, False, False, 10.0),
    (9, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 7, 7, True, False, 7.666666666666667),
    (157, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 4, 4, True, False, 0.5),
    (119, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 13, 13, True, False, 4.0),
    (159, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 21, 21, True, False, 8.5),
    (21, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 11, 11, True, False, 4.0),
    (21, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 15, 15, True, False, 5.333333333333333),
    (21, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 3, 3, True, False, 6.666666666666667),
    (48, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 16, 16, True, False, 2.6666666666666665),
    (48, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 19, 19, True, False, 3.6666666666666665),
    (48, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 11, 11, True, False, 4.333333333333333),
    (30, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 2, 2, True, False, 1.5),
    (30, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 5, 5, True, False, 1.5),
    (34, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 14, 14, True, False, 7.5),
    (34, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 29, 29, True, False, 7.5),
    (46, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 15, 15, True, False, 1.5),
    (46, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 18, 18, True, False, 1.5),
    (94, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 21, 21, True, False, 4.5),
    (94, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 12, 12, True, False, 6.5),
    (102, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 8, 8, True, False, 2.0),
    (102, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 12, 12, True, False, 2.0),
    (138, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 17, 17, True, False, 6.0),
    (138, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 29, 29, True, False, 6.0),
    (0, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 0, 0, True, False, 0.0),
    (1, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 37, 37, True, False, 0.0),
    (2, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 0, 0, True, False, 0.0),
    (3, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 7, 7, True, False, 0.0),
    (6, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 16, 16, True, False, 0.0),
    (10, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 13, 13, True, False, 0.0),
    (13, u'Florida', u'LOCATION', 18, 18, True, False, 0.0)]
question: Name a National Park in Florida 
expected: Everglades National Park
expected sentence: The American alligator, American crocodile, Florida panther, and manatee can be found in the Everglades National Park.
question open class words: ['name', 'national', 'park', 'florida']



    (197, u'17', 'NUMBER', 50, 50, False, True, 15.166666666666666),
    (163, u'18', 'NUMBER', 16, 16, False, True, 1.0),
    (209, u'1500', 'NUMBER', 10, 10, False, True, 4.0),
    (435, u'two', 'NUMBER', 6, 6, False, True, 5.0),
    (74, u'one', 'NUMBER', 9, 9, False, True, None),
    (232, u'American', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, False, 12.5),
    (232, u'2002', u'DATE', 1, 1, False, False, 13.5),
    (263, u'HIV', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, False, 6.5),
    (311, u'Latin', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, False, 31.0),
    (311, u'Adolescence', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, False, 34.0),
    (15, u'90 %', u'PERCENT', 3, 4, False, False, 14.0),
    (15, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, False, 18.0),
    (74, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, False, None),
    (174, u'Fashion', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, False, None),
    (174, u'Fashion', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, None)]
question: At what age does coming out to adults occur on average?
expected: 17
expected sentence: A study of 194 lesbian, gay, and bisexual youths under the age of 21 found that having an awareness of one's sexual orientation occurred, on average, around age 10, but the process of coming out to peers and adults occurred around age 16 and 17, respectively.
question open class words: ['age', 'does', 'coming', 'adults', 'occur', 'average']



all results:
[   (97, u'Abdulrahman Vezirov', u'PERSON', 22, 23, False, True, 2.0),
    (97, u'Kamran Baghirov', u'PERSON', 17, 18, False, True, 5.25),
    (22, u'Eduard Shevardnadze', u'PERSON', 8, 9, False, True, 2.5),
    (22, u'Gorbachev', u'PERSON', 6, 6, False, True, 5.5),
    (22, u'Andrei Gromyko', u'PERSON', 41, 42, False, True, 29.5),
    (   268,
        u'Stanislav Hurenko',
        u'PERSON',
        0,
        1,
        False,
        True,
        2.6666666666666665),
    (29, u'Yeltsin', u'PERSON', 10, 10, False, True, 1.5),
    (29, u'Gorbachev', u'PERSON', 8, 8, False, True, 3.5),
    (29, u'Viktor Grishin', u'PERSON', 19, 20, False, True, 7.5),
    (34, u'Gennady Kolbin', u'PERSON', 47, 48, False, True, 10.0),
    (34, u'Gorbachev', u'PERSON', 22, 22, False, True, 15.0),
    (179, u'Jumber Patiashvili', u'PERSON', 6, 7, False, True, 2.5),
    (179, u'Gorbachev', u'PERSON', 4, 4, False, True, 5.5),
    (179, u'Givi Gumbaridze', u'PERSON', 24, 25, False, True, 14.5),
    (187, u'Volodymyr Scherbytsky', u'PERSON', 51, 52, False, True, 7.5),
    (   211,
        u'Ukraine Volodymyr Shcherbytsky',
        u'PERSON',
        12,
        14,
        False,
        True,
        8.0),
    (211, u'Brezhnev', u'PERSON', 20, 20, False, True, 11.333333333333334),
    (   211,
        u'Vladimir Ivashko',
        u'PERSON',
        26,
        27,
        False,
        True,
        15.333333333333334),
    (211, u'Ivashko', u'PERSON', 27, 27, False, True, 16.333333333333332),
    (232, u'Rafiq Nishonov', u'PERSON', 8, 9, False, True, 2.5),
    (232, u'Gorbachev', u'PERSON', 6, 6, False, True, 5.5),
    (232, u'Karimov', u'PERSON', 25, 25, False, True, 13.5),
    (   109,
        u'Suren Harutyunyan',
        u'PERSON',
        21,
        22,
        False,
        True,
        2.6666666666666665),
    (   109,
        u'Karen Demirchian',
        u'PERSON',
        16,
        17,
        False,
        True,
        5.333333333333333),
    (4, u'Mikhail Gorbachev', u'PERSON', 0, 1, False, True, 2.5),
    (4, u'Gorbachev', u'PERSON', 1, 1, False, True, 2.5),
    (4, u'Konstantin Chernenko', u'PERSON', 19, 20, False, True, 15.5),
    (269, u'Ivashko', u'PERSON', 4, 4, False, True, 15.0),
    (62, u'Ligachev', u'PERSON', 48, 48, False, True, 5.0),
    (62, u'Yeltsin', u'PERSON', 55, 55, False, True, 12.0),
    (62, u'Gorbachev', u'PERSON', 18, 18, False, True, 25.0),
    (62, u'Yeltsin', u'PERSON', 14, 14, False, True, 29.0),
    (326, u'Yeltsin', u'PERSON', 13, 13, False, True, 15.0),
    (139, u'Zianon Pazniak', u'PERSON', 11, 12, False, True, 8.0),
    (   97,
        u'First Secretary of the Azerbaijan Communist Party',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        25,
        31,
        False,
        False,
        2.25),
    (97, u'Azerbaijan', u'LOCATION', 29, 29, False, False, 5.75),
    (97, u'Communist Party', 'OTHER', 30, 31, False, False, 6.75),
    (97, u'Communist Party', u'ORGANIZATION', 30, 31, False, False, 6.75),
    (97, u'Communist', 'OTHER', 30, 30, False, False, 6.75),
    (97, u'Party', 'OTHER', 31, 31, False, False, 7.75),
    (97, u'1988', u'DATE', 15, 15, False, False, 8.25),
    (97, u'May 21 , 1988', u'DATE', 12, 15, False, False, 8.25),
    (97, u'May 21', u'DATE', 12, 13, False, False, 10.25),
    (97, u'May', u'DATE', 12, 12, False, False, 11.25),
    (97, u'Republics', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, False, 14.25),
    (   97,
        u'Communist Party Leaders',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        4,
        6,
        False,
        False,
        17.25),
    (97, u'Communist Party Leaders', 'OTHER', 4, 6, False, False, 17.25),
    (97, u'Communist Party', 'OTHER', 4, 5, False, False, 18.25),
    (97, u'Communist Party', u'ORGANIZATION', 4, 5, False, False, 18.25),
    (97, u'Party', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, False, 18.25),
    (97, u'Communist', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, False, 19.25),
    (22, u'Georgian', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, False, 3.5),
    (   22,
        u'Georgian Communist Party',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        15,
        17,
        False,
        False,
        3.5),
    (22, u'Communist Party', 'OTHER', 16, 17, False, False, 4.5),
    (22, u'Communist Party', u'ORGANIZATION', 16, 17, False, False, 4.5),
    (22, u'Communist', 'OTHER', 16, 16, False, False, 4.5),
    (22, u'Gorbachev', 'OTHER', 6, 6, False, False, 5.5),
    (22, u'Party', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, 5.5),
    (22, u'July 1 , 1985', u'DATE', 1, 4, False, False, 7.5),
    (22, u'July 1', u'DATE', 1, 2, False, False, 9.5),
    (22, u'July', u'DATE', 1, 1, False, False, 10.5),
    (22, u'On', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, False, 11.5),
    (22, u'Politburo', 'OTHER', 24, 24, False, False, 12.5),
    (22, u'Foreign Minister', 'OTHER', 39, 40, False, False, 27.5),
    (22, u'Minister', 'OTHER', 40, 40, False, False, 28.5),
    (22, u'Gromyko', 'OTHER', 42, 42, False, False, 30.5),
    (268, u'CPU', 'OTHER', 8, 8, False, False, 4.333333333333333),
    (29, u'Yeltsin First Secretary', 'OTHER', 10, 12, False, False, 0.5),
    (29, u'Yeltsin', 'OTHER', 10, 10, False, False, 1.5),
    (29, u'Gorbachev', 'OTHER', 8, 8, False, False, 3.5),
    (29, u'Moscow', u'LOCATION', 15, 15, False, False, 3.5),
    (   29,
        u'Moscow Communist Party',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        15,
        17,
        False,
        False,
        3.5),
    (29, u'Communist Party', 'OTHER', 16, 17, False, False, 4.5),
    (29, u'Communist Party', u'ORGANIZATION', 16, 17, False, False, 4.5),
    (29, u'Communist', 'OTHER', 16, 16, False, False, 4.5),
    (29, u'December 23 , 1985', u'DATE', 3, 6, False, False, 5.5),
    (29, u'Party', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, 5.5),
    (29, u'December', u'DATE', 3, 3, False, False, 8.5),
    (   34,
        u'Communist Party of Kazakhstan',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        34,
        37,
        False,
        False,
        4.0),
    (34, u'Communist Party', 'OTHER', 34, 35, False, False, 4.666666666666667),
    (   34,
        u'Communist Party',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        34,
        35,
        False,
        False,
        4.666666666666667),
    (34, u'Communist', 'OTHER', 34, 34, False, False, 5.0),
    (   34,
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        30,
        35,
        False,
        False,
        5.0),
    (34, u'Party', 'OTHER', 35, 35, False, False, 5.333333333333333),
    (34, u'Kazakhstan', u'LOCATION', 37, 37, False, False, 6.0),
    (34, u'Kazakh', 'OTHER', 41, 41, False, False, 7.333333333333333),
    (34, u'Konayev', 'OTHER', 27, 27, False, False, 10.0),
    (34, u'Dinmukhamed Konayev', 'OTHER', 26, 27, False, False, 10.0),
    (34, u'Russian SFSR', 'OTHER', 54, 55, False, False, 17.0),
    (34, u'Kazakhstan', u'LOCATION', 18, 18, False, False, 19.0),
    (34, u'Alma-Ata', u'LOCATION', 16, 16, False, False, 21.0),
    (34, u'1986', u'DATE', 12, 12, False, False, 25.0),
    (34, u'December', u'DATE', 8, 8, False, False, 29.0),
    (34, u'Kazakh', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, False, 32.0),
    (34, u'Jeltoqsan', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, False, 35.0),
    (34, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, False, 37.0),
    (179, u'Georgian', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, False, 3.5),
    (   179,
        u'Georgian Communist Party',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        13,
        15,
        False,
        False,
        3.5),
    (179, u'Communist Party', 'OTHER', 14, 15, False, False, 4.5),
    (179, u'Communist Party', u'ORGANIZATION', 14, 15, False, False, 4.5),
    (179, u'Communist', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, False, 4.5),
    (179, u'Gorbachev', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, False, 5.5),
    (179, u'Party', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, False, 5.5),
    (179, u'April 14', u'DATE', 1, 2, False, False, 7.5),
    (179, u'14', 'NUMBER', 2, 2, False, False, 7.5),
    (179, u'On', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, False, 9.5),
    (179, u'Georgian KGB', u'ORGANIZATION', 21, 22, False, False, 11.5),
    (179, u'Georgian', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, False, 11.5),
    (179, u'KGB', u'ORGANIZATION', 22, 22, False, False, 12.5),
    (187, u'Communist Party', 'OTHER', 46, 47, False, False, 2.5),
    (187, u'Communist Party', u'ORGANIZATION', 46, 47, False, False, 2.5),
    (   187,
        u'Communist Party of Ukraine',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        46,
        49,
        False,
        False,
        2.5),
    (187, u'Communist', 'OTHER', 46, 46, False, False, 2.5),
    (187, u'Ukraine', u'LOCATION', 49, 49, False, False, 5.5),
    (187, u'Deputies', 'OTHER', 32, 32, False, False, 11.5),
    (   187,
        u"USSR Congress of People 's Deputies",
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        27,
        32,
        False,
        False,
        11.5),
    (   187,
        u"Congress of People 's Deputies",
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        28,
        32,
        False,
        False,
        11.5),
    (187, u'Congress of People', u'ORGANIZATION', 28, 30, False, False, 13.5),
    (187, u'People', 'OTHER', 30, 30, False, False, 13.5),
    (187, u'USSR', u'ORGANIZATION', 27, 27, False, False, 16.5),
    (187, u'March 26', u'DATE', 22, 23, False, False, 20.5),
    (187, u'March', u'DATE', 22, 22, False, False, 21.5),
    (187, u'Kiev', u'LOCATION', 10, 10, False, False, 33.5),
    (187, u'February', u'DATE', 2, 2, False, False, 41.5),
    (   211,
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        4,
        9,
        False,
        False,
        5.0),
    (211, u'Communist Party', 'OTHER', 8, 9, False, False, 7.0),
    (211, u'Communist Party', u'ORGANIZATION', 8, 9, False, False, 7.0),
    (211, u'Communist', 'OTHER', 8, 8, False, False, 7.333333333333333),
    (211, u'Party', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, False, 7.666666666666667),
    (211, u'September 28', u'DATE', 1, 2, False, False, 8.666666666666666),
    (211, u'Ukraine', u'LOCATION', 12, 12, False, False, 8.666666666666666),
    (211, u'September', u'DATE', 1, 1, False, False, 9.666666666666666),
    (211, u'On', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, False, 10.666666666666666),
    (   232,
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        11,
        16,
        False,
        False,
        0.5),
    (232, u'Communist Party', 'OTHER', 15, 16, False, False, 3.5),
    (232, u'Communist Party', u'ORGANIZATION', 15, 16, False, False, 3.5),
    (232, u'Communist', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, False, 3.5),
    (232, u'Party', 'OTHER', 16, 16, False, False, 4.5),
    (232, u'Gorbachev', 'OTHER', 6, 6, False, False, 5.5),
    (232, u'1989', u'DATE', 4, 4, False, False, 7.5),
    (232, u'June 23 , 1989', u'DATE', 1, 4, False, False, 7.5),
    (232, u'Uzbek', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, False, 7.5),
    (232, u'Uzbek SSR', u'ORGANIZATION', 19, 20, False, False, 7.5),
    (232, u'On', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, False, 11.5),
    (232, u'Uzbekistan', u'LOCATION', 32, 32, False, False, 20.5),
    (232, u'Soviet', 'OTHER', 35, 35, False, False, 23.5),
    (232, u'Soviet Republic', 'OTHER', 35, 36, False, False, 23.5),
    (   109,
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        24,
        29,
        False,
        False,
        2.3333333333333335),
    (109, u'Harutyunyan', 'OTHER', 22, 22, False, False, 3.0),
    (   109,
        u'Communist Party',
        'OTHER',
        28,
        29,
        False,
        False,
        5.666666666666667),
    (   109,
        u'Communist Party',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        28,
        29,
        False,
        False,
        5.666666666666667),
    (109, u'Communist', 'OTHER', 28, 28, False, False, 5.666666666666667),
    (109, u'Party', 'OTHER', 29, 29, False, False, 6.666666666666667),
    (109, u'1988', u'DATE', 14, 14, False, False, 8.333333333333334),
    (109, u'May 21 , 1988', u'DATE', 11, 14, False, False, 8.333333333333334),
    (109, u'Armenia', u'LOCATION', 31, 31, False, False, 8.666666666666666),
    (109, u'May 21', u'DATE', 11, 12, False, False, 10.333333333333334),
    (109, u'May', u'DATE', 11, 11, False, False, 11.333333333333334),
    (109, u'On', 'OTHER', 10, 10, False, False, 12.333333333333334),
    (   109,
        u'Communist Party Leaders',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        6,
        8,
        False,
        False,
        14.333333333333334),
    (   109,
        u'Communist Party Leaders',
        'OTHER',
        6,
        8,
        False,
        False,
        14.333333333333334),
    (109, u'Communist Party', 'OTHER', 6, 7, False, False, 15.333333333333334),
    (   109,
        u'Communist Party',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        6,
        7,
        False,
        False,
        15.333333333333334),
    (109, u'Party', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, False, 15.333333333333334),
    (109, u'Communist', 'OTHER', 6, 6, False, False, 16.333333333333332),
    (109, u'Republics', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, False, 18.333333333333332),
    (4, u'General Secretary', 'OTHER', 4, 5, False, False, 1.0),
    (4, u'Gorbachev', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, 2.5),
    (4, u'Politburo', 'OTHER', 8, 8, False, False, 4.5),
    (4, u'March 11 , 1985', u'DATE', 10, 13, False, False, 6.5),
    (4, u'11', 'NUMBER', 11, 11, False, False, 7.5),
    (4, u'73', 'NUMBER', 25, 25, False, False, 21.5),
    (6, u'Soviet', 'OTHER', 10, 10, False, False, 4.5),
    (269, u'Ukrainian Parliament', u'ORGANIZATION', 13, 14, False, False, 5.0),
    (269, u'Parliament', u'ORGANIZATION', 14, 14, False, False, 5.0),
    (269, u'Communist Party', 'OTHER', 24, 25, False, False, 5.0),
    (269, u'Communist Party', u'ORGANIZATION', 24, 25, False, False, 5.0),
    (269, u'Parliament', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, False, 5.0),
    (269, u'Communist', 'OTHER', 24, 24, False, False, 5.0),
    (269, u'Ukrainian', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, False, 6.0),
    (269, u'Party', 'OTHER', 25, 25, False, False, 6.0),
    (269, u'Soviet Union', u'LOCATION', 28, 29, False, False, 9.0),
    (269, u'11', 'NUMBER', 2, 2, False, False, 17.0),
    (269, u'July 11', u'DATE', 1, 2, False, False, 17.0),
    (269, u'July', u'DATE', 1, 1, False, False, 18.0),
    (269, u'On', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, False, 19.0),
    (62, u'Yeltsin', 'OTHER', 55, 55, False, False, 12.0),
    (62, u'Gorbachev', 'OTHER', 18, 18, False, False, 25.0),
    (62, u'Yeltsin', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, False, 29.0),
    (62, u'Central Committee', u'ORGANIZATION', 11, 12, False, False, 31.0),
    (62, u'October 27 , 1987', u'DATE', 2, 5, False, False, 38.0),
    (62, u'October 27', u'DATE', 2, 3, False, False, 40.0),
    (326, u'December 24 , 1991', u'DATE', 19, 22, False, False, 9.5),
    (326, u'Alma-Ata Protocol', u'ORGANIZATION', 31, 32, False, False, 10.5),
    (326, u'December', u'DATE', 19, 19, False, False, 11.0),
    (326, u'Russia', u'LOCATION', 34, 34, False, False, 11.0),
    (326, u'UN Secretary-General', 'OTHER', 16, 17, False, False, 11.0),
    (326, u'UN', u'ORGANIZATION', 16, 16, False, False, 12.0),
    (326, u'UN', 'OTHER', 16, 16, False, False, 12.0),
    (326, u'USSR', u'ORGANIZATION', 41, 41, False, False, 13.0),
    (326, u'Yeltsin', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, False, 15.0),
    (326, u'Russian President', 'OTHER', 11, 12, False, False, 16.0),
    (326, u'Russian', 'OTHER', 11, 11, False, False, 17.0),
    (326, u'UN', u'ORGANIZATION', 5, 5, False, False, 23.0),
    (326, u'UN', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, False, 23.0),
    (326, u'Soviet Ambassador', 'OTHER', 1, 2, False, False, 26.0),
    (326, u'Soviet', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, 27.0),
    (326, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, False, 28.0),
    (32, u'Helsinki-86', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, False, 10.333333333333334),
    (32, u'Soviet', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, False, 11.333333333333334),
    (110, u'70', 'NUMBER', 32, 32, False, False, 3.0),
    (   110,
        u'First Armenian Republic',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        22,
        24,
        False,
        False,
        5.0),
    (110, u'Armenian', 'OTHER', 23, 23, False, False, 6.0),
    (110, u'Armenians', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, 12.0),
    (110, u'28', 'NUMBER', 14, 14, False, False, 15.0),
    (110, u'May 28', u'DATE', 13, 14, False, False, 15.0),
    (110, u'May', u'DATE', 13, 13, False, False, 16.0),
    (110, u'Harutyunyan', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, False, 27.0),
    (   265,
        u'Ukrainian Autocephalous Orthodox Church',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        19,
        22,
        False,
        False,
        8.0),
    (265, u'Church', 'OTHER', 22, 22, False, False, 8.5),
    (265, u'Church', 'OTHER', 28, 28, False, False, 8.5),
    (265, u'UAOC', u'ORGANIZATION', 24, 24, False, False, 8.5),
    (265, u'UAOC', 'OTHER', 24, 24, False, False, 8.5),
    (265, u'Church', u'ORGANIZATION', 22, 22, False, False, 8.5),
    (265, u'Church', u'ORGANIZATION', 28, 28, False, False, 8.5),
    (265, u'Ukrainian', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, False, 9.5),
    (265, u'Church', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, False, 15.5),
    (   265,
        u'U.S.-based Ukrainian Orthodox Church',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        10,
        13,
        False,
        False,
        15.5),
    (265, u'Church', u'ORGANIZATION', 13, 13, False, False, 15.5),
    (265, u'Ukrainian Orthodox', 'OTHER', 11, 12, False, False, 16.5),
    (265, u'Ukrainian', 'OTHER', 11, 11, False, False, 17.5),
    (265, u'Metropolitan Mstyslav', 'OTHER', 6, 7, False, False, 21.5),
    (265, u'Mstyslav', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, False, 21.5),
    (265, u'Metropolitan', 'OTHER', 6, 6, False, False, 22.5),
    (265, u'June 5–6 , 1990', u'DATE', 1, 4, False, False, 24.5),
    (265, u'1990', u'DATE', 4, 4, False, False, 24.5),
    (265, u'On', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, False, 28.5),
    (   139,
        u'Belarusian Popular Front’s',
        'OTHER',
        15,
        17,
        3.0),
    (139, u'Belarus', u'LOCATION', 31, 31, False, False, 11.0),
    (139, u'Minsk', u'LOCATION', 8, 8, False, False, 12.0),
    (139, u'Kurapaty', u'LOCATION', 6, 6, False, False, 14.0),
    (139, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, False, 20.0),
    (142, u'1917', u'DATE', 22, 22, False, False, 3.0),
    (142, u'Congress of People', u'ORGANIZATION', 29, 31, False, False, 10.0),
    (   142,
        u"Congress of People 's Deputies",
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        29,
        33,
        False,
        False,
        10.0),
    (142, u'Soviet Union', u'LOCATION', 7, 8, False, False, 11.0),
    (142, u'People', 'OTHER', 31, 31, False, False, 12.0),
    (142, u'Deputies', 'OTHER', 33, 33, False, False, 14.0),
    (142, u'1989', u'DATE', 1, 1, False, False, 18.0),
    (142, u'Spring 1989', u'DATE', 0, 1, False, False, 18.0),
    (97, u'First Secretary', 'OTHER', 25, 26, True, False, 2.0),
    (22, u'First Secretary', 'OTHER', 11, 12, True, False, 0.0),
    (29, u'First Secretary', 'OTHER', 11, 12, True, False, 0.0),
    (34, u'First Secretary', 'OTHER', 30, 31, True, False, 6.0),
    (179, u'First Secretary', 'OTHER', 9, 10, True, False, 0.0),
    (211, u'First Secretary', 'OTHER', 4, 5, True, False, 6.0),
    (232, u'First Secretary', 'OTHER', 11, 12, True, False, 0.0),
    (109, u'First Secretary', 'OTHER', 24, 25, True, False, 2.0)]
question: Who was First Secretary prior to Vezirov?
expected: Kamran Baghirov
expected sentence: He instead sacked the Communist Party Leaders in both Republics  on May 21, 1988, Kamran Baghirov was replaced by Abdulrahman Vezirov as First Secretary of the Azerbaijan Communist Party.
actual: (97, u'Abdulrahman Vezirov', u'PERSON', 22, 23, False, True, 2.0)
question open class words: ['was', 'first', 'secretary', 'prior', 'vezirov']



all results:
[   (81, u'Parliament', u'LOCATION', 27, 27, False, True, 5.0),
    (21, u'Parliament', u'LOCATION', 12, 12, False, True, None),
    (28, u'Parliament', u'LOCATION', 13, 13, False, True, 8.0),
    (   9,
        u'Amalgamated Society of Railway Servants',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        8,
        12,
        False,
        False,
        3.25),
    (9, u'Doncaster', u'ORGANIZATION', 4, 4, False, False, 8.75),
    (9, u'1899', u'DATE', 1, 1, False, False, 11.75),
    (9, u'Trade Union Congress', u'ORGANIZATION', 25, 27, False, False, 12.25),
    (9, u'Parliamentary', 'OTHER', 48, 48, False, False, 35.25),
    (2, u'Party', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, False, 3.0),
    (2, u'The Labour Party', 'OTHER', 0, 2, False, False, 4.0),
    (2, u'Party', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, False, 4.0),
    (2, u'Labour Party', u'ORGANIZATION', 1, 2, False, False, 4.0),
    (2, u'European Socialists', 'OTHER', 11, 12, False, False, 5.0),
    (2, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 1, 1, False, False, 5.0),
    (2, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, 5.0),
    (2, u'Socialists', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, False, 6.0),
    (2, u'Progressive Alliance', u'ORGANIZATION', 14, 15, False, False, 8.0),
    (2, u'Alliance', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, False, 9.0),
    (   2,
        u'Socialist International',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        23,
        24,
        False,
        False,
        17.0),
    (5, u'1867', u'DATE', 25, 25, False, False, None),
    (5, u'1885', u'DATE', 27, 27, False, False, None),
    (5, u'Liberal Party', u'ORGANIZATION', 30, 31, False, False, None),
    (5, u'Party', 'OTHER', 31, 31, False, False, None),
    (5, u'Liberal', 'OTHER', 30, 30, False, False, None),
    (81, u'one', 'NUMBER', 31, 31, False, False, 1.0),
    (81, u'one', 'NUMBER', 34, 34, False, False, 2.0),
    (81, u'Parliament', u'ORGANIZATION', 27, 27, False, False, 5.0),
    (81, u'OMOV', 'OTHER', 39, 39, False, False, 7.0),
    (81, u'John Prescott', u'PERSON', 51, 52, False, False, 19.0),
    (81, u'Smith', 'PERSON', 55, 55, False, False, 23.0),
    (81, u'Smith', u'ORGANIZATION', 55, 55, False, False, 23.0),
    (81, u'Smith', 'PERSON', 5, 5, False, False, 27.0),
    (81, u'Smith', u'ORGANIZATION', 5, 5, False, False, 27.0),
    (81, u'1993', u'DATE', 2, 2, False, False, 30.0),
    (   21,
        u'Members of Parliament',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        10,
        12,
        False,
        False,
        None),
    (21, u'Parliament', u'ORGANIZATION', 12, 12, False, False, None),
    (21, u'15', 'NUMBER', 25, 25, False, False, None),
    (21, u'The Labour Party', 'OTHER', 19, 21, False, False, None),
    (21, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 20, 20, False, False, None),
    (21, u'February 1906', u'DATE', 26, 27, False, False, None),
    (21, u'Party', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, False, None),
    (21, u'Labour Party', u'ORGANIZATION', 20, 21, False, False, None),
    (21, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 20, 20, False, False, None),
    (73, u'two', 'NUMBER', 32, 32, False, False, None),
    (73, u'MPs', 'OTHER', 33, 33, False, False, None),
    (   73,
        u'National Executive Committee',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        6,
        8,
        False,
        False,
        None),
    (73, u'1987', u'DATE', 2, 2, False, False, None),
    (73, u'Militant', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, False, None),
    (58, u'22', 'NUMBER', 11, 11, False, False, 5.0),
    (58, u'Militant', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, 5.0),
    (58, u'February 1983', u'DATE', 12, 13, False, False, 6.0),
    (28, u'Liberal', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, False, 2.0),
    (28, u'Members of Parliament', u'ORGANIZATION', 11, 13, False, False, 6.0),
    (28, u'Parliament', u'ORGANIZATION', 13, 13, False, False, 8.0),
    (28, u'Trade Unions', u'ORGANIZATION', 21, 22, False, False, 16.0),
    (28, u'Trade Unions', 'OTHER', 21, 22, False, False, 16.0),
    (9, u'Thomas R. Steels', u'PERSON', 14, 16, True, False, 2.75)]
question: Where was Thomas R. Steels a member?
expected: Doncaster
expected sentence: In 1899, a Doncaster member of the Amalgamated Society of Railway Servants, Thomas R. Steels, proposed in his union branch that the Trade Union Congress call a special conference to bring together all left-wing organisations and form them into a single body that would sponsor Parliamentary candidates.
actual: (81, u'Parliament', u'LOCATION', 27, 27, False, True, 5.0)
question open class words: ['where', 'was', 'thomas', 'r', 'steels', 'member']



all results:
[   (35, u'January 1924', u'DATE', 20, 21, False, True, 7.2),
    (35, u'January', u'DATE', 20, 20, False, True, 7.6),
    (35, u'1924', u'DATE', 21, 21, False, True, 7.8),
    (4, u'late 19th century', u'DATE', 8, 10, False, True, 7.0),
    (26, u'1910', u'DATE', 1, 1, False, True, 25.666666666666668),
    (5, u'1867', u'DATE', 25, 25, False, True, None),
    (5, u'1885', u'DATE', 27, 27, False, True, None),
    (23, u'1918', u'DATE', 28, 28, False, True, 12.0),
    (63, u'May that year', u'DATE', 7, 9, False, True, 1.0),
    (63, u'May', u'DATE', 7, 7, False, True, 3.0),
    (63, u'2010', u'DATE', 2, 2, False, True, 8.0),
    (82, u'1992', u'DATE', 7, 7, False, True, 20.5),
    (82, u'September 1992', u'DATE', 6, 7, False, True, 20.5),
    (82, u'Wednesday', u'DATE', 2, 2, False, True, 25.5),
    (92, u'May 2007', u'DATE', 25, 26, False, True, 16.5),
    (92, u'2007', u'DATE', 26, 26, False, True, 17.0),
    (92, u'May', u'DATE', 25, 25, False, True, 17.0),
    (92, u'May', u'DATE', 38, 38, False, True, 17.0),
    (92, u'September 2006', u'DATE', 3, 4, False, True, 26.0),
    (43, u'August 1931', u'DATE', 2, 3, False, True, 1.0),
    (43, u'1931', u'DATE', 3, 3, False, True, 1.0),
    (51, u'1979', u'DATE', 24, 24, False, True, 13.0),
    (85, u'1994', u'DATE', 28, 28, False, True, 15.75),
    (85, u'1996', u'DATE', 43, 43, False, True, 23.25),
    (35, u'Labour Prime Minister', 'OTHER', 16, 18, False, False, 6.4),
    (35, u'Prime Minister', 'OTHER', 17, 18, False, False, 6.6),
    (35, u'191', 'NUMBER', 33, 33, False, False, 13.4),
    (35, u'Asquith', u'PERSON', 6, 6, False, False, 13.6),
    (35, u'MPs', 'OTHER', 34, 34, False, False, 14.4),
    (35, u'House of Commons )', u'ORGANIZATION', 42, 45, False, False, 22.4),
    (35, u'House of Commons', u'ORGANIZATION', 42, 44, False, False, 22.4),
    (   14,
        u'Labour Party',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        15,
        16,
        False,
        False,
        1.6666666666666667),
    (   14,
        u'Independent Labour Party',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        14,
        16,
        False,
        False,
        2.0),
    (14, u'Party', 'OTHER', 16, 16, False, False, 2.0),
    (14, u'Secretary', 'OTHER', 23, 23, False, False, 5.666666666666667),
    (14, u'one', 'NUMBER', 11, 11, False, False, 6.333333333333333),
    (14, u'It', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, False, 17.333333333333332),
    (   33,
        u'Labour Party',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        15,
        16,
        False,
        False,
        5.333333333333333),
    (33, u'Party', 'OTHER', 16, 16, False, False, 6.0),
    (4, u'Labour Party', u'ORGANIZATION', 1, 2, False, False, 0.0),
    (4, u'The Labour Party', 'OTHER', 0, 2, False, False, 1.0),
    (4, u'Party', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, False, 1.0),
    (44, u'Labour Party', u'ORGANIZATION', 27, 28, False, False, 9.75),
    (44, u'Party', 'OTHER', 28, 28, False, False, 10.25),
    (   44,
        u'National Labour Organisation',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        33,
        35,
        False,
        False,
        12.25),
    (44, u'Labour Party', u'ORGANIZATION', 8, 9, False, False, 12.5),
    (44, u'Party', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, False, 12.75),
    (26, u'House of Lords', u'ORGANIZATION', 26, 28, False, False, 18.0),
    (   26,
        u'House of Commons',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        10,
        12,
        False,
        False,
        18.666666666666668),
    (26, u'Osborne', u'PERSON', 32, 32, False, False, 20.666666666666668),
    (26, u'Labour MPs', 'OTHER', 5, 6, False, False, 21.0),
    (26, u'MPs', 'OTHER', 6, 6, False, False, 21.333333333333332),
    (   26,
        u'Trades Unions',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        36,
        37,
        False,
        False,
        21.666666666666668),
    (26, u'United Kingdom', u'LOCATION', 40, 41, False, False, 23.0),
    (26, u'Labour MPs', 'OTHER', 55, 56, False, False, 28.333333333333332),
    (26, u'MPs', 'OTHER', 56, 56, False, False, 29.333333333333332),
    (5, u'Liberal Party', u'ORGANIZATION', 30, 31, False, False, None),
    (5, u'Party', 'OTHER', 31, 31, False, False, None),
    (5, u'Liberal', 'OTHER', 30, 30, False, False, None),
    (23, u'ILP', u'ORGANIZATION', 11, 11, False, False, 7.0),
    (   23,
        u'Independent Labour Party',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        7,
        9,
        False,
        False,
        7.0),
    (23, u'Party', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, False, 7.0),
    (23, u'Labour Party', u'ORGANIZATION', 8, 9, False, False, 7.0),
    (63, u'258', 'NUMBER', 26, 26, False, False, 16.0),
    (82, u'Tories', 'OTHER', 34, 34, False, False, 6.5),
    (82, u'Conservative', 'OTHER', 10, 10, False, False, 17.5),
    (82, u'Black', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, 26.5),
    (92, u'Blair', u'PERSON', 0, 0, False, False, 30.0),
    (36, u'Campbell Case', u'ORGANIZATION', 18, 19, False, False, 5.0),
    (36, u'Select Committee', u'ORGANIZATION', 13, 14, False, False, 10.0),
    (36, u'Liberals', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, False, 15.0),
    (36, u'nine', 'NUMBER', 5, 5, False, False, 19.0),
    (41, u'Zinoviev', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, False, None),
    (41, u'Zinoviev Letter', 'OTHER', 13, 14, False, False, None),
    (41, u'Labourites', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, False, None),
    (41, u'A. J. P. Taylor', u'PERSON', 20, 23, False, False, None),
    (42, u'National Government', 'OTHER', 11, 12, False, False, 6.0),
    (42, u'National Government', u'ORGANIZATION', 11, 12, False, False, 6.0),
    (42, u'Conservatives', 'OTHER', 16, 16, False, False, 11.0),
    (43, u'24', 'NUMBER', 1, 1, False, False, 3.0),
    (43, u'National Government', 'OTHER', 23, 24, False, False, 19.0),
    (43, u'National Government', u'ORGANIZATION', 23, 24, False, False, 19.0),
    (85, u'Labour Party', u'ORGANIZATION', 13, 14, False, False, 13.75),
    (85, u'Labour Party', u'ORGANIZATION', 25, 26, False, False, 14.0),
    (85, u'Party', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, False, 14.25),
    (85, u'Party', 'OTHER', 26, 26, False, False, 14.75),
    (85, u'New Labour', 'OTHER', 1, 2, False, False, 19.75),
    (85, u'New Labour', u'LOCATION', 1, 2, False, False, 19.75),
    (85, u'New Labour', 'OTHER', 46, 47, False, False, 24.5),
    (85, u'New Labour', u'LOCATION', 46, 47, False, False, 24.5),
    (85, u'Britain', u'LOCATION', 52, 52, False, False, 30.25),
    (   8,
        u'Marxist Social Democratic Federation',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        17,
        20,
        False,
        False,
        9.0),
    (8, u'Scottish Labour Party', u'ORGANIZATION', 23, 25, False, False, 9.5),
    (8, u'Fabian Society', u'ORGANIZATION', 13, 14, False, False, 10.0),
    (8, u'Labour Party', u'ORGANIZATION', 5, 6, False, False, 10.0),
    (8, u'Labour Party', u'ORGANIZATION', 24, 25, False, False, 10.0),
    (8, u'Scottish', 'OTHER', 23, 23, False, False, 10.5),
    (   8,
        u'Independent Labour Party',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        4,
        6,
        False,
        False,
        10.5),
    (8, u'Party', 'OTHER', 6, 6, False, False, 10.5),
    (8, u'Party', 'OTHER', 25, 25, False, False, 10.5),
    (12, u'Parliament', u'ORGANIZATION', 19, 19, False, False, 22.0),
    (12, u'Parliament', u'LOCATION', 19, 19, False, False, 22.0),
    (12, u'129', 'NUMBER', 5, 5, False, False, 34.0),
    (87, u'Old Labour', 'OTHER', 33, 34, False, False, 15.5),
    (87, u'New Labour', 'OTHER', 1, 2, False, False, 16.0),
    (87, u'New Labour', u'LOCATION', 1, 2, False, False, 16.0),
    (35, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 16, 16, True, False, 7.2),
    (35, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 16, 16, True, False, 7.2),
    (35, u'MacDonald', u'ORGANIZATION', 11, 11, True, False, 8.6),
    (35, u'Ramsay MacDonald', u'ORGANIZATION', 10, 11, True, False, 8.6),
    (35, u'MacDonald', u'PERSON', 11, 11, True, False, 8.6),
    (35, u'Ramsay MacDonald', u'PERSON', 10, 11, True, False, 8.6),
    (35, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 26, 26, True, False, 8.8),
    (35, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 26, 26, True, False, 8.8),
    (35, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 30, 30, True, False, 10.8),
    (35, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 30, 30, True, False, 10.8),
    (14, u'Ramsay MacDonald', u'ORGANIZATION', 18, 19, True, False, 1.0),
    (14, u'Ramsay MacDonald', u'PERSON', 18, 19, True, False, 1.0),
    (   14,
        u'MacDonald',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        19,
        19,
        True,
        False,
        1.6666666666666667),
    (14, u'MacDonald', u'PERSON', 19, 19, True, False, 1.6666666666666667),
    (14, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 15, 15, True, False, 2.3333333333333335),
    (14, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 15, 15, True, False, 2.3333333333333335),
    (33, u'MacDonald', u'ORGANIZATION', 6, 6, True, False, 4.666666666666667),
    (   33,
        u'Ramsay MacDonald',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        5,
        6,
        True,
        False,
        4.666666666666667),
    (33, u'MacDonald', u'PERSON', 6, 6, True, False, 4.666666666666667),
    (33, u'Ramsay MacDonald', u'PERSON', 5, 6, True, False, 4.666666666666667),
    (33, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 15, 15, True, False, 5.666666666666667),
    (33, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 15, 15, True, False, 5.666666666666667),
    (4, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 1, 1, True, False, 0.0),
    (4, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 1, 1, True, False, 0.0),
    (44, u'MacDonald', u'ORGANIZATION', 14, 14, True, False, 10.25),
    (44, u'MacDonald', u'PERSON', 14, 14, True, False, 10.25),
    (44, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 27, 27, True, False, 10.25),
    (44, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 27, 27, True, False, 10.25),
    (44, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 8, 8, True, False, 13.25),
    (44, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 34, 34, True, False, 13.25),
    (44, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 8, 8, True, False, 13.25),
    (44, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 34, 34, True, False, 13.25),
    (26, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 5, 5, True, False, 21.666666666666668),
    (26, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 5, 5, True, False, 21.666666666666668),
    (26, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 55, 55, True, False, 28.333333333333332),
    (26, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 55, 55, True, False, 28.333333333333332),
    (23, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 8, 8, True, False, 8.0),
    (23, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 8, 8, True, False, 8.0),
    (63, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 11, 11, True, False, 1.0),
    (63, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 11, 11, True, False, 1.0),
    (82, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 27, 27, True, False, 0.5),
    (82, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 27, 27, True, False, 0.5),
    (92, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 47, 47, True, False, 17.0),
    (92, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 47, 47, True, False, 17.0),
    (36, u'MacDonald', u'ORGANIZATION', 24, 24, True, False, 0.0),
    (36, u'MacDonald', u'PERSON', 24, 24, True, False, 0.0),
    (42, u'MacDonald', u'ORGANIZATION', 5, 5, True, False, 0.0),
    (42, u'MacDonald', u'PERSON', 5, 5, True, False, 0.0),
    (43, u'MacDonald', u'ORGANIZATION', 4, 4, True, False, 0.0),
    (43, u'MacDonald', u'PERSON', 4, 4, True, False, 0.0),
    (85, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 13, 13, True, False, 14.25),
    (85, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 25, 25, True, False, 14.25),
    (85, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 13, 13, True, False, 14.25),
    (85, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 25, 25, True, False, 14.25),
    (85, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 2, 2, True, False, 19.75),
    (85, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 2, 2, True, False, 19.75),
    (85, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 47, 47, True, False, 25.25),
    (85, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 47, 47, True, False, 25.25),
    (8, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 5, 5, True, False, 10.5),
    (8, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 24, 24, True, False, 10.5),
    (8, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 5, 5, True, False, 10.5),
    (8, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 24, 24, True, False, 10.5),
    (12, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 16, 16, True, False, 23.0),
    (12, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 16, 16, True, False, 23.0),
    (87, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 2, 2, True, False, 16.0),
    (87, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 34, 34, True, False, 16.0),
    (87, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 2, 2, True, False, 16.0),
    (87, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 34, 34, True, False, 16.0)]
question: In what year did Ramsay MacDonald become the Labour PM?
expected: 1924
expected sentence: Thus, with the acquiescence of Asquith's Liberals, Ramsay MacDonald became the first ever Labour Prime Minister in January 1924, forming the first Labour government, despite Labour only having 191 MPs (less than a third of the House of Commons).
extracted id: [35, 14, 33, 4, 44, 26, 5, 23, 63, 82, 92, 36, 41, 42, 43, 51, 85, 8, 12, 87]
predicted question type: DATE
question open class words: ['year', 'did', 'ramsay', 'macdonald', 'labour', 'pm']



all results:
[   (49, u'Callaghan', u'LOCATION', 40, 40, False, True, 16.0),
    (81, u'Parliament', u'LOCATION', 27, 27, False, True, 24.0),
    (85, u'New Labour', u'LOCATION', 1, 2, False, True, 16.0),
    (85, u'New Labour', u'LOCATION', 46, 47, False, True, 28.0),
    (85, u'Britain', u'LOCATION', 52, 52, False, True, 34.0),
    (87, u'New Labour', u'LOCATION', 1, 2, False, True, None),
    (10, u'TUC', u'ORGANIZATION', 9, 9, False, False, 5.8),
    (10, u'Memorial Hall', u'ORGANIZATION', 19, 20, False, False, 7.0),
    (10, u'27', 'NUMBER', 27, 27, False, False, 15.0),
    (10, u'February 1900', u'DATE', 28, 29, False, False, 16.0),
    (9, u'Trade Union Congress', u'ORGANIZATION', 25, 27, False, False, 5.5),
    (9, u'Thomas R. Steels', u'PERSON', 14, 16, False, False, 9.5),
    (   9,
        u'Amalgamated Society of Railway Servants',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        8,
        12,
        False,
        False,
        13.5),
    (9, u'Doncaster', u'ORGANIZATION', 4, 4, False, False, 21.5),
    (9, u'Parliamentary', 'OTHER', 48, 48, False, False, 22.5),
    (9, u'1899', u'DATE', 1, 1, False, False, 24.5),
    (49, u'Scottish Assembly', 'OTHER', 14, 15, False, False, 15.5),
    (49, u'Callaghan', 'OTHER', 40, 40, False, False, 16.0),
    (49, u'Scottish', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, False, 16.0),
    (49, u'28', 'NUMBER', 51, 51, False, False, 22.0),
    (49, u'March 1979', u'DATE', 52, 53, False, False, 23.0),
    (49, u'1979', u'DATE', 53, 53, False, False, 24.0),
    (49, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 2, 2, False, False, 27.0),
    (49, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, False, 27.0),
    (   66,
        u'Labour Party Conference',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        29,
        31,
        False,
        False,
        0.0),
    (66, u'Party', 'OTHER', 30, 30, False, False, 1.0),
    (66, u'Labour Party', u'ORGANIZATION', 29, 30, False, False, 1.0),
    (66, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 29, 29, False, False, 2.0),
    (66, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 29, 29, False, False, 2.0),
    (66, u'Leader', 'OTHER', 26, 26, False, False, 5.0),
    (66, u'Prime Minister', 'OTHER', 39, 40, False, False, 8.0),
    (66, u'Brown', u'PERSON', 18, 18, False, False, 13.0),
    (66, u'Liberal Democrats', 'OTHER', 13, 14, False, False, 17.0),
    (66, u'Liberal', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, False, 18.0),
    (66, u'2010', u'DATE', 3, 3, False, False, 28.0),
    (66, u'May 2010', u'DATE', 2, 3, False, False, 28.0),
    (66, u'May', u'DATE', 2, 2, False, False, 29.0),
    (66, u'10', 'NUMBER', 1, 1, False, False, 30.0),
    (38, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 7, 7, False, False, 4.0),
    (38, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, False, 4.0),
    (2, u'European Socialists', 'OTHER', 11, 12, False, False, None),
    (2, u'Progressive Alliance', u'ORGANIZATION', 14, 15, False, False, None),
    (   2,
        u'Socialist International',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        23,
        24,
        False,
        False,
        None),
    (2, u'The Labour Party', 'OTHER', 0, 2, False, False, None),
    (2, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 1, 1, False, False, None),
    (2, u'Party', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, False, None),
    (2, u'Party', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, False, None),
    (2, u'Labour Party', u'ORGANIZATION', 1, 2, False, False, None),
    (2, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, None),
    (2, u'Alliance', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, False, None),
    (2, u'Socialists', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, False, None),
    (48, u'March 1979', u'DATE', 10, 11, False, False, 2.5),
    (48, u'Welsh', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, False, 3.0),
    (48, u'1979', u'DATE', 11, 11, False, False, 3.0),
    (48, u'Welsh', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, False, 6.0),
    (48, u'Scottish', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, False, 8.0),
    (48, u'40', 'NUMBER', 33, 33, False, False, 22.0),
    (48, u'40 %', u'PERCENT', 33, 34, False, False, 22.0),
    (81, u'1993', u'DATE', 2, 2, False, False, 1.0),
    (81, u'Smith', 'PERSON', 5, 5, False, False, 2.0),
    (81, u'Smith', u'ORGANIZATION', 5, 5, False, False, 2.0),
    (81, u'Parliament', u'ORGANIZATION', 27, 27, False, False, 24.0),
    (81, u'one', 'NUMBER', 31, 31, False, False, 28.0),
    (81, u'one', 'NUMBER', 34, 34, False, False, 31.0),
    (81, u'OMOV', 'OTHER', 39, 39, False, False, 36.0),
    (81, u'John Prescott', u'PERSON', 51, 52, False, False, 48.0),
    (81, u'Smith', 'PERSON', 55, 55, False, False, 52.0),
    (81, u'Smith', u'ORGANIZATION', 55, 55, False, False, 52.0),
    (   85,
        u'Labour Party',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        13,
        14,
        False,
        False,
        10.333333333333334),
    (85, u'Party', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, False, 10.666666666666666),
    (   85,
        u'Labour Party',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        25,
        26,
        False,
        False,
        10.666666666666666),
    (85, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 13, 13, False, False, 11.0),
    (85, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 25, 25, False, False, 11.0),
    (85, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, False, 11.0),
    (85, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 25, 25, False, False, 11.0),
    (85, u'Party', 'OTHER', 26, 26, False, False, 11.333333333333334),
    (85, u'1994', u'DATE', 28, 28, False, False, 12.0),
    (85, u'New Labour', 'OTHER', 1, 2, False, False, 16.0),
    (85, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 2, 2, False, False, 16.0),
    (85, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, False, 16.0),
    (85, u'1996', u'DATE', 43, 43, False, False, 25.0),
    (85, u'New Labour', 'OTHER', 46, 47, False, False, 28.0),
    (85, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 47, 47, False, False, 29.0),
    (85, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 47, 47, False, False, 29.0),
    (85, u'New Life For', 'OTHER', 49, 51, False, False, 31.0),
    (87, u'New Labour', 'OTHER', 1, 2, False, False, None),
    (87, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 2, 2, False, False, None),
    (87, u'Labour', u'ORGANIZATION', 34, 34, False, False, None),
    (87, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, False, None),
    (87, u'Labour', 'OTHER', 34, 34, False, False, None),
    (87, u'Old Labour', 'OTHER', 33, 34, False, False, None)]
question: WHere was the proposed conference held?
expected: Memorial Hall
expected sentence: The motion was passed at all stages by the TUC, and the proposed conference was held at the Memorial Hall on Farringdon Street on 26 and 27 February 1900.
actual: (49, u'Callaghan', u'LOCATION', 40, 40, False, True, 16.0)
question open class words: ['where', 'was', 'proposed', 'conference', 'held']



all results:
    (22, u'1', 'NUMBER', 10, 10, False, True, 42.0),
    (122, u'5', 'NUMBER', 21, 21, False, True, 12.0),
    (14, u'8:7', 'NUMBER', 5, 5, False, True, None),
    (20, u'two', 'NUMBER', 83, 83, False, True, None),
    (62, u'21,460 ft', 'NUMBER', 16, 17, False, True, None),
    (62, u'6,540 metres', 'NUMBER', 13, 14, False, True, None),
    (129, u'Bombycilla', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, False, 6.333333333333333),
    (   129,
        u'nineteenth century',
        u'DATE',
        21,
        22,
        False,
        False,
        14.666666666666666),
    (129, u'2000', u'DATE', 31, 31, False, False, 24.666666666666668),
    (125, u'Bombycilla', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, False, 1.0),
    (22, u'Swallows', 'OTHER', 42, 42, False, False, 10.0),
    (22, u'Majorca', u'LOCATION', 36, 36, False, False, 16.0),
    (22, u'Minorca', u'ORGANIZATION', 34, 34, False, False, 18.0),
    (22, u'1797', u'DATE', 12, 12, False, False, 40.0),
    (22, u'Volume', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, False, 43.0),
    (22, u'British', 'OTHER', 6, 6, False, False, 46.0),
    (22, u'A History', 'OTHER', 3, 4, False, False, 48.0),
    (22, u'Thomas Bewick', u'PERSON', 0, 1, False, False, 51.0),
    (22, u'Bewick', u'PERSON', 1, 1, False, False, 51.0),
    (23, u'Bewick', u'PERSON', 0, 0, False, False, 12.0),
    (74, u'Iceland', u'LOCATION', 10, 10, False, False, 4.0),
    (74, u'Junco', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, False, 7.0),
    (74, u'American', 'OTHER', 46, 46, False, False, 32.0),
    (74, u'American South', u'ORGANIZATION', 46, 47, False, False, 32.0),
    (74, u'South', 'OTHER', 47, 47, False, False, 33.0),
    (122, u'Europe', u'LOCATION', 14, 14, False, False, 5.0),
    (14, u'Even', 'OTHER', 10, 10, False, False, None),
    (14, u'Jeremiah', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, False, None),
    (20, u'Wight', u'LOCATION', 23, 23, False, False, None),
    (20, u'I', 'OTHER', 31, 31, False, False, None),
    (20, u'Isle', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, False, None),
    (35, u'summer', u'DATE', 8, 8, False, False, None),
    (62, u'GPS', u'ORGANIZATION', 8, 8, False, False, None),
    (62, u'Himalayas', u'LOCATION', 22, 22, False, False, None),
    (62, u'Anser', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, False, None),
    (105, u'Bosphorus', u'LOCATION', 23, 23, False, False, 3.0),
    (105, u'Falsterbo', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, False, 7.0),
    (105, u'Gibraltar', u'LOCATION', 17, 17, False, False, 9.0),
    (105, u'Messina', u'LOCATION', 15, 15, False, False, 11.0),
    (105, u'Strait', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, False, 13.0),
    (129, u'Britain', u'LOCATION', 18, 18, True, False, 11.666666666666666),
    (129, u'1937', u'DATE', 29, 29, True, False, 22.666666666666668),
    (22, u'Britain', u'LOCATION', 52, 52, True, False, 0.0),
    (23, u'Britain', u'LOCATION', 12, 12, True, False, 0.0),
    (74, u'Britain', u'LOCATION', 12, 12, True, False, 2.0),
    (122, u'Britain', u'LOCATION', 9, 9, True, False, 0.0)]
question: How many times did Bohemian waxwings come to Britain between 1937 and 200?
expected: 18
expected sentence: Bohemian waxwings Bombycilla garrulus well show this unpredictable variation in annual numbers, with five major arrivals in Britain during the nineteenth century, but 18 between the years 1937 and 2000.
question open class words: ['how', 'many', 'times', 'did', 'bohemian', 'waxwings', 'come', 'britain']



all results:
[   (336, u'Father Liber', 'OTHER', 18, 19, False, True, 8.0),
    (336, u'Liber', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, True, 8.75),
    (336, u'Punic', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, True, 15.75),
    (336, u'Roman Bacchus', 'OTHER', 34, 35, False, True, 16.25),
    (336, u'Bacchus', 'OTHER', 35, 35, False, True, 17.25),
    (392, u'Greek', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, True, 24.0),
    (338, u'Apollo', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, True, 3.0),
    (338, u'Marsyas', 'OTHER', 6, 6, False, True, 5.0),
    (338, u'Augustus', 'OTHER', 24, 24, False, True, 13.0),
    (318, u'Christian', 'OTHER', 18, 18, False, True, 18.0),
    (430, u'Arab', 'OTHER', 24, 24, False, True, 2.0),
    (430, u'Philip', 'OTHER', 22, 22, False, True, 4.0),
    (430, u'Hippolytus', 'OTHER', 30, 30, False, True, 4.0),
    (430, u'Christian', 'OTHER', 36, 36, False, True, 10.0),
    (19, u'Greek', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, True, 7.0),
    (19, u'Greeks', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, True, 14.0),
    (19, u'Romans', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 27.0),
    (19, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, True, 28.0),
    (26, u'Romans', 'OTHER', 18, 18, False, True, 3.0),
    (26, u'Empire', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, True, 12.0),
    (5, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, True, 23.0),
    (6, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, True, 2.0),
    (27, u'Mithras', 'OTHER', 40, 40, False, True, 10.0),
    (27, u'Rome', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, True, 37.0),
    (27, u'Empire', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, True, 45.0),
    (28, u'Romans', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 12.0),
    (55, u'Rome', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, True, 30.0),
    (185, u'Arvals', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 6.0),
    (185, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, True, 7.0),
    (185, u'Imperial', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, True, 12.0),
    (265, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, True, 5.0),
    (368, u'Rome', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, True, None),
    (368, u'Romans', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, True, None),
    (423, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, True, 15.0),
    (62, u'Rome', 'OTHER', 34, 34, False, True, None),
    (103, u'Manes', 'OTHER', 26, 26, False, True, None),
    (103, u'Dis', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, True, None),
    (336, u'Italy', u'LOCATION', 12, 12, False, False, 7.75),
    (392, u'Augustus', 'PERSON', 22, 22, False, False, 9.0),
    (392, u'Caesar', u'LOCATION', 18, 18, False, False, 9.0),
    (392, u'Caesar', u'PERSON', 18, 18, False, False, 9.0),
    (338, u'Augustus', 'PERSON', 24, 24, False, False, 13.0),
    (318, u'Christian', 'PERSON', 18, 18, False, False, 18.0),
    (430, u'Christian', 'PERSON', 36, 36, False, False, 10.0),
    (26, u'Empire', u'ORGANIZATION', 3, 3, False, False, 12.0),
    (6, u'Jupiter', u'ORGANIZATION', 38, 38, False, False, 36.0),
    (27, u'Britain', u'LOCATION', 51, 51, False, False, 1.0),
    (27, u'Sol Invictus', u'LOCATION', 42, 43, False, False, 7.0),
    (27, u'Epona', u'LOCATION', 31, 31, False, False, 19.0),
    (27, u'Isis', u'ORGANIZATION', 29, 29, False, False, 21.0),
    (27, u'Cybele', u'PERSON', 27, 27, False, False, 23.0),
    (27, u'Rome', u'LOCATION', 13, 13, False, False, 37.0),
    (27, u'Empire', u'ORGANIZATION', 5, 5, False, False, 45.0),
    (28, u'one', 'NUMBER', 11, 11, False, False, 4.0),
    (28, u'one', 'NUMBER', 8, 8, False, False, 5.0),
    (55, u'Rome', u'LOCATION', 0, 0, False, False, 30.0),
    (368, u'Rome', u'LOCATION', 2, 2, False, False, None),
    (62, u'Jupiter', u'ORGANIZATION', 0, 0, False, False, None),
    (62, u'Rome', u'LOCATION', 34, 34, False, False, None),
    (336, u'Dionysus', 'OTHER', 14, 14, True, True, 6.75),
    (336, u'Dionysus', 'OTHER', 8, 8, True, True, 9.75),
    (336, u'Roman', 'OTHER', 34, 34, True, True, 16.25),
    (392, u'Roman', 'OTHER', 32, 32, True, True, 9.0),
    (338, u'Dionysus', 'OTHER', 11, 11, True, True, 0.0),
    (19, u'Roman', 'OTHER', 29, 29, True, True, 1.0),
    (26, u'Roman', 'OTHER', 11, 11, True, True, 4.0),
    (5, u'Roman', 'OTHER', 23, 23, True, True, 0.0),
    (6, u'Roman', 'OTHER', 1, 1, True, True, 1.0),
    (27, u'Roman', 'OTHER', 50, 50, True, True, 0.0),
    (55, u'Roman', 'OTHER', 30, 30, True, True, 0.0),
    (121, u'Roman', 'OTHER', 4, 4, True, True, 0.0),
    (185, u'Roman', 'OTHER', 7, 7, True, True, 0.0),
    (265, u'Roman', 'OTHER', 8, 8, True, True, 3.0),
    (423, u'Roman', 'OTHER', 15, 15, True, True, 0.0),
    (336, u'Roman', 'PERSON', 34, 34, True, False, 16.25),
    (392, u'Roman', 'PERSON', 32, 32, True, False, 9.0),
    (19, u'Roman', 'PERSON', 29, 29, True, False, 1.0),
    (26, u'Roman', 'PERSON', 11, 11, True, False, 4.0),
    (5, u'Roman', 'PERSON', 23, 23, True, False, 0.0),
    (6, u'Roman', 'PERSON', 1, 1, True, False, 1.0),
    (27, u'Roman', 'PERSON', 50, 50, True, False, 0.0),
    (55, u'Roman', 'PERSON', 30, 30, True, False, 0.0),
    (121, u'Roman', 'PERSON', 4, 4, True, False, 0.0),
    (185, u'Roman', 'PERSON', 7, 7, True, False, 0.0),
    (265, u'Roman', 'PERSON', 8, 8, True, False, 3.0),
    (423, u'Roman', 'PERSON', 15, 15, True, False, 0.0)]
question: To what Roman god was Dionysus similar?
expected: Bacchus
expected sentence: During the Punic crisis, popular cult to Dionysus emerged from southern Italy; Dionysus was equated with Father Liber, the inventor of plebeian augury and personification of plebeian freedoms, and with Roman Bacchus.
actual: (336, u'Father Liber', 'OTHER', 18, 19, False, True, 8.0)
question open class words: ['roman', 'god', 'was', 'dionysus', 'similar']



all results:
[   (415, u'Rome', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, True, 3.75),
    (415, u'Emperor', 'OTHER', 10, 10, False, True, 4.75),
    (415, u'Christians', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, True, 7.75),
    (95, u'Public', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, True, None),
    (96, u'Latin', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, True, None),
    (96, u'Roman', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, True, None),
    (96, u'Livy', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, True, None),
    (64, u'Libera', 'OTHER', 20, 20, False, True, None),
    (64, u'Liber', 'OTHER', 18, 18, False, True, None),
    (64, u'Imperial', 'OTHER', 31, 31, False, True, None),
    (72, u'Roman', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, True, None),
    (74, u'Other', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, True, None),
    (17, u'Christian', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, True, 15.0),
    (303, u'Battle', 'OTHER', 27, 27, False, True, 16.0),
    (303, u'Pharsalus', 'OTHER', 29, 29, False, True, 18.0),
    (303, u'Thessalian', 'OTHER', 34, 34, False, True, 23.0),
    (303, u'Erichtho', 'OTHER', 36, 36, False, True, 25.0),
    (459, u'Christian', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, True, 6.0),
    (358, u'Great Mother', 'OTHER', 17, 18, False, True, 0.0),
    (358, u'Mother', 'OTHER', 18, 18, False, True, 1.0),
    (358, u'Pessinus', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, True, 4.0),
    (358, u'BC', 'OTHER', 29, 29, False, True, 12.0),
    (358, u'Sibylline', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, True, 13.0),
    (358, u'BC', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, True, 15.0),
    (358, u'In', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, True, 17.0),
    (111, u'In', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, True, 3.0),
    (111, u'Rome', 'OTHER', 16, 16, False, True, 13.0),
    (143, u'He', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, True, None),
    (204, u'I', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, True, 6.0),
    (204, u'Theodosius', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, True, 7.0),
    (471, u'Vestals', 'OTHER', 18, 18, False, True, 6.0),
    (471, u'Sacred', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, True, 9.0),
    (471, u'Symmachus', 'OTHER', 35, 35, False, True, 12.0),
    (471, u'Western', 'OTHER', 38, 38, False, True, 15.0),
    (471, u'Eastern', 'OTHER', 40, 40, False, True, 17.0),
    (471, u'Victory', 'OTHER', 6, 6, False, True, 17.0),
    (471, u'He', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, True, 23.0),
    (384, u'Gaulish Vertault', 'OTHER', 9, 10, False, True, 20.0),
    (384, u'Sabratha’s', 'OTHER', 41, 41, False, True, 20.5),
    (384, u'Romanised', 'OTHER', 30, 30, False, True, 20.5),
    (296, u'Tiberius', 'OTHER', 18, 18, False, True, 10.0),
    (296, u'Augustus', 'OTHER', 8, 8, False, True, 20.0),
    (296, u'Egyptian', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 27.0),
    (298, u'Tacitus', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, True, 2.0),
    (298, u'In', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, True, 5.0),
    (298, u'Rome', 'OTHER', 20, 20, False, True, 15.0),
    (415, u'Rome', u'LOCATION', 5, 5, False, False, 3.75),
    (415, u'Nero', u'ORGANIZATION', 11, 11, False, False, 5.25),
    (96, u'Roman', 'PERSON', 19, 19, False, False, None),
    (96, u'Livy', u'ORGANIZATION', 2, 2, False, False, None),
    (64, u'Ceres', u'LOCATION', 16, 16, False, False, None),
    (72, u'Roman', 'PERSON', 4, 4, False, False, None),
    (74, u'Bona Dea', u'ORGANIZATION', 25, 26, False, False, None),
    (17, u'Christian', 'PERSON', 21, 21, False, False, 15.0),
    (303, u'Pompey', u'PERSON', 9, 9, False, False, 2.0),
    (303, u'Pompey', u'LOCATION', 9, 9, False, False, 2.0),
    (303, u'Sextus Pompeius', u'PERSON', 2, 3, False, False, 8.0),
    (303, u'Erichtho', u'PERSON', 36, 36, False, False, 25.0),
    (459, u'Constantine', 'PERSON', 0, 0, False, False, 3.0),
    (459, u'Christian', 'PERSON', 9, 9, False, False, 6.0),
    (358, u'Magna Mater', u'ORGANIZATION', 14, 15, False, False, 2.0),
    (358, u'206', 'NUMBER', 1, 1, False, False, 16.0),
    (111, u'Senate', u'ORGANIZATION', 7, 7, False, False, 4.0),
    (111, u'Rome', u'LOCATION', 16, 16, False, False, 13.0),
    (111, u'one', 'NUMBER', 29, 29, False, False, 26.0),
    (195, u'Vesta', u'ORGANIZATION', 9, 9, False, False, 2.0),
    (204, u'Vesta', u'ORGANIZATION', 5, 5, False, False, 4.0),
    (   471,
        u'Quintus Aurelius Symmachus',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        33,
        35,
        False,
        False,
        10.0),
    (296, u'19', 'NUMBER', 29, 29, False, False, 1.0),
    (296, u'Augustus', 'PERSON', 8, 8, False, False, 20.0),
    (415, u'Great Fire', 'OTHER', 2, 3, True, True, 3.5),
    (415, u'AD', 'OTHER', 8, 8, True, True, 3.75),
    (415, u'Great', 'OTHER', 2, 2, True, True, 4.25),
    (96, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, True, True, None),
    (17, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, True, True, 6.0),
    (303, u'Great', 'OTHER', 11, 11, True, True, 0.0),
    (358, u'Great', 'OTHER', 17, 17, True, True, 0.0),
    (384, u'AD', 'OTHER', 7, 7, True, True, 20.5),
    (296, u'AD', 'OTHER', 28, 28, True, True, 0.0),
    (415, u'64', 'NUMBER', 7, 7, True, False, 3.75)]
question: What group was accused of starting the Great Fire of 64 AD?
expected: Christians
expected sentence: After the Great Fire of Rome in 64 AD, Emperor Nero accused the Christians as convenient scapegoats, who were later persecuted and killed.
question open class words: ['group', 'was', 'accused', 'starting', 'great', 'fire', 'ad']


