all results:
    (50, u'10.3–11.5', 'NUMBER', 12, 12, False, False, 10.0)]
question: What is the range of the near-infrared channel in micrometers?
expected: 1.58–1.64
expected sentence: However, using the difference in brightness of the IR4 channel (10.3–11.5 µm) and the near-infrared channel (1.58–1.64 µm), low cloud can be distinguished, producing a fog satellite picture.
question open class words: ['range', 'near', 'infrared', 'channel', 'micrometers']



all results:
[   (   63,
        u'900–14,000',
        14,
        14,
        4.666666666666667),
    (63, u'0.9–14', 'NUMBER', 17, 17, False, False, 7.666666666666667)]
question: What is the range of the electromagnetic spectrum in micrometers?
expected: 0.9–14
expected sentence: Thermographic cameras detect radiation in the infrared range of the electromagnetic spectrum (roughly 900–14,000 nanometers or 0.9–14 μm) and produce images of that radiation.
question open class words: ['range', 'electromagnetic', 'spectrum', 'micrometers']



all results:
question open class words: ['populous', 'city', 'guam']



all results:
[   (10, u'March 6 , 1521', u'DATE', 13, 16, False, False, 4.75),
    (10, u'Magellan', u'ORGANIZATION', 3, 3, False, False, 5.25),
    (10, u'Ferdinand Magellan', u'ORGANIZATION', 2, 3, False, False, 5.25),
    (10, u'Portuguese', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, False, 8.25),
    (10, u'European', 'OTHER', 7, 7, True, False, 1.75)]
question: Who was the first European to visit the island?
expected: Ferdinand Magellan
expected sentence: Portuguese explorer Ferdinand Magellan was the first European to visit the island on March 6, 1521.
question open class words: ['first', 'european', 'visit', 'island']



all results:
[   (30, u'These', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, True, 1.5),
    (30, u'Proas', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, True, 3.5),
    (30, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, True, 10.5),
    (30, u'Islas', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, True, 11.5),
    (30, u'Velas Latinas', 'OTHER', 16, 17, False, True, 14.5),
    (30, u'Islands', 'OTHER', 20, 20, False, True, 18.5),
    (30, u'Lateen', 'OTHER', 23, 23, False, True, 21.5),
question open class words: ['name', 'outrigger', 'canoes']



all results:
[   (34, u'January', u'DATE', 13, 13, False, True, 3.6666666666666665),
    (   34,
        u'January 26 , 1565',
        u'DATE',
        13,
        16,
        False,
        True,
        3.6666666666666665),
    (34, u'1565', u'DATE', 16, 16, False, True, 6.666666666666667),
    (34, u'Magellan', u'ORGANIZATION', 1, 1, False, False, 8.333333333333334),
    (   34,
        u'General Miguel L\xf3pez de Legazpi',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        18,
        22,
        False,
        False,
        8.666666666666666),
    (34, u'Spain', u'LOCATION', 11, 11, True, False, 2.3333333333333335),
    (34, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 5, 5, True, False, 4.333333333333333),
    (34, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 5, 5, True, False, 4.333333333333333),
extracted id: [34]
predicted question type: DATE
question open class words: ['year', 'guam', 'claimed', 'spain']



all results:
[   (   34,
        u'January 26 , 1565',
        u'DATE',
        13,
        16,
        False,
        False,
        4.333333333333333),
    (34, u'Spain', u'LOCATION', 11, 11, False, False, 4.666666666666667),
    (34, u'January', u'DATE', 13, 13, False, False, 5.333333333333333),
    (34, u'1565', u'DATE', 16, 16, False, False, 6.333333333333333),
    (   34,
        u'General Miguel L\xf3pez de Legazpi',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        18,
        22,
        False,
        False,
        7.0),
    (34, u'Magellan', u'ORGANIZATION', 1, 1, False, False, 10.666666666666666),
    (34, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 5, 5, True, True, 6.666666666666667),
    (34, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 5, 5, True, False, 6.666666666666667),
question: What was the name of the general who claimed Guam?
expected: General Miguel López de Legazpi
question open class words: ['name', 'general', 'claimed', 'guam']



all results:
[   (64, u'Chamorros', 'OTHER', 26, 26, False, False, 4.0),
    (   64,
        u'Northern Mariana Chamorros',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        24,
        26,
        False,
        False,
        4.0),
    (64, u'Mariana', u'LOCATION', 25, 25, False, False, 5.0),
    (64, u'Mariana', 'OTHER', 25, 25, False, False, 5.0),
    (64, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 0, 0, False, False, 30.0),
    (64, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, False, 30.0),
    (64, u'Japan', u'LOCATION', 30, 30, True, False, 1.0)]
question: Who were loyal to Japan?
expected: Northern Mariana Chamorros
expected sentence: Guam's Chamorros believed their northern brethren should have been compassionate towards them, whereas having been occupied for over 30 years, the Northern Mariana Chamorros were loyal to Japan.
question open class words: ['loyal', 'japan']



all results:
[   (68, u'32nd', 'NUMBER', 28, 28, False, True, 13.666666666666666),
    (68, u'212', 'NUMBER', 17, 17, False, True, 17.333333333333332),
    (68, u'145.0\xb0E', 'NUMBER', 10, 10, False, True, 19.666666666666668),
    (68, u'144.6\xb0E', 'NUMBER', 8, 8, False, True, 20.333333333333332),
    (68, u'13.7\xb0N', 'NUMBER', 5, 5, False, True, 21.333333333333332),
    (   68,
        u'United States',
        u'LOCATION',
        33,
        34,
        False,
        11.333333333333334),
    (68, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 0, 0, True, False, 23.0),
    (68, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 0, 0, True, False, 23.0),
    (68, u'Guam', u'ORGANIZATION', 0, 0, True, False, 23.0)]
question: How many square miles is Guam?
expected: 212
expected sentence: Guam lies between 13.2°N and 13.7°N and between 144.6°E and 145.0°E, and has an area of 212 square miles (549 km2), making it the 32nd largest island of the United States.
question open class words: ['many', 'square', 'miles', 'guam']



all results:
[   (112, u'Mariana', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, True, 8.0),
    (112, u'Islands', 'OTHER', 20, 20, False, True, 9.0),
    (   112,
        u'Northern Mariana Islands',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        18,
        20,
    (112, u'Mariana', u'LOCATION', 19, 19, False, False, 8.0),
    (112, u'Mariana Islands', u'LOCATION', 19, 20, False, False, 8.0),
    (112, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 6, 6, True, True, 6.2),
    (112, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 6, 6, True, False, 6.2),
question open class words: ['name', 'u', 'state', 'could', 'possibly', 'form', 'union', 'guam']



all results:
    (123, u'Republic', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, True, 14.0),
    (123, u'Territory', 'OTHER', 34, 34, False, True, 16.77777777777778),
    (123, u'Compacts', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 24.0),
    (123, u'Republic of Palau', u'ORGANIZATION', 24, 26, False, False, 13.0),
    (   123,
        u'Marshall Islands',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        20,
        21,
        False,
        False,
        13.11111111111111),
    (   123,
        u'Federated States of Micronesia',
        u'LOCATION',
        11,
        14,
        False,
        False,
        13.555555555555555),
    (   123,
        u'Trust Territory',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        33,
        34,
        False,
        False,
        16.11111111111111),
    (   123,
        u'Pacific Islands',
        u'LOCATION',
        37,
        38,
        17.444444444444443),
    (123, u'Pacific', u'LOCATION', 37, 37, False, False, 17.77777777777778),
    (   123,
        u'The Compacts of Free Association',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        0,
        4,
        False,
        False,
        21.0),
    (123, u'Islands', 'OTHER', 21, 21, True, True, 13.555555555555555),
    (123, u'Islands', 'OTHER', 38, 38, True, True, 18.11111111111111),
    (123, u'The', 'OTHER', 0, 0, True, True, 25.0),
    (123, u'Palau', u'ORGANIZATION', 26, 26, True, False, 14.11111111111111),
    (   123,
        49,
        50,
        False,
        24.11111111111111)]
question: What is the name of the pact held between the United States, Micronesia, Marshal Islands, and Palau?
expected: The Compacts of Free Association
expected sentence: The Compacts of Free Association between the United States, the Federated States of Micronesia, the Republic of the Marshall Islands and the Republic of Palau accorded the former entities of the Trust Territory of the Pacific Islands a political status of "free association" with the United States.
question open class words: ['name', 'pact', 'held', 'united', 'states', 'micronesia', 'marshal', 'islands', 'palau']



all results:
[   (130, u'U.S.', u'LOCATION', 7, 8, False, True, 12.6),
    (130, u'96910–96932', 'NUMBER', 21, 21, False, False, 6.2),
    (130, u'GU', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, False, 8.6),
    (130, u'Postal System', 'OTHER', 9, 10, False, False, 11.4),
    (130, u'U.S', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, False, 13.4),
    (130, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 26, 26, True, True, 9.2),
    (130, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 1, 1, True, True, 17.0),
    (130, u'ZIP', 'OTHER', 17, 17, True, False, 7.4),
    (130, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 26, 26, True, False, 9.2),
    (130, u'Guam', u'ORGANIZATION', 26, 26, True, False, 9.2),
    (130, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 1, 1, True, False, 17.0),
question: What is the current Zip Code range in Guam?
expected: 96910–96932
expected sentence: Because Guam is also part of the U.S. Postal System (postal abbreviation: GU, ZIP code range: 96910–96932), mail to Guam from the U.S. mainland is considered domestic and no additional charges are required.
question open class words: ['current', 'zip', 'code', 'range', 'guam']



all results:
    (141, u'Antonio', 'PERSON', 5, 5, False, False, 6.0),
    (141, u'United Airlines', u'ORGANIZATION', 18, 19, False, False, 7.0),
    (141, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 0, 0, False, False, 11.0),
question open class words: ['major', 'airline', 'resides', 'airport']



all results:
[   (180, u'Islands', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 8.333333333333334),
    (180, u'Schools', 'OTHER', 20, 20, False, True, 10.666666666666666),
    (   180,
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        14,
        18,
        False,
        6.0),
    (   180,
        u'Pacific Islands University',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        0,
        2,
        False,
        False,
        7.333333333333333),
    (   180,
        u'Pacific Islands',
        u'LOCATION',
        0,
        1,
        8.333333333333334),
    (180, u'Pacific', u'LOCATION', 0, 0, False, False, 9.333333333333334),
    (180, u'Christian', 'OTHER', 6, 6, True, True, 4.0),
question open class words: ['name', 'small', 'christian', 'college', 'guam']



all results:
[   (187, u'Government', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 8.833333333333334),
    (   187,
        u'Guam Memorial Hospital',
        u'ORGANIZATION',
        13,
        15,
        3.5),
    (187, u'Tamuning', u'LOCATION', 18, 18, False, False, 8.166666666666666),
    (187, u'Guam', 'OTH