all results:
    (2, u'Dededo', u'LOCATION', 12, 12, False, True, 29),
    (39, u'Mexico City', u'LOCATION', 29, 30, False, True, 0),
    (39, u'New Spain', u'LOCATION', 25, 26, False, True, 4),
    (39, u'Philippines', u'LOCATION', 14, 14, False, True, 16),
    (39, u'Spanish East Indies', u'LOCATION', 8, 10, False, True, 20),
    (0, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 31, 32, False, True, 49),
    (43, u'Northern Marianas', u'LOCATION', 17, 18, False, True, 19),
    (58, u'Philippines', u'LOCATION', 36, 36, False, True, 51),
    (58, u'Germany', u'LOCATION', 45, 45, False, True, 69),
    (65, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 20, 21, False, True, 22),
    (113, u'Okinawa', u'LOCATION', 34, 34, False, True, 21),
    (144, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 13, 14, False, True, 30),
    (154, u'Chamorro', u'LOCATION', 14, 14, False, True, 14),
    (187, u'Tamuning', u'LOCATION', 19, 19, False, True, 21),
    (1, u'Pacific Ocean', u'LOCATION', 4, 5, False, True, 5),
    (191, u'Guam Regional Medical City', 'OTHER', 5, 8, False, False, 0),
    (191, u'2016', 'NUMBER', 14, 14, False, False, 15),
    (39, u'64', 'NUMBER', 1, 1, False, False, 29),
    (0, u'IPA', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, False, 29),
    (0, u'Gu\xe5h\xe5n', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, False, 32),
    (0, u'Chamorro', 'OTHER', 10, 10, False, False, 34),
    (43, u'Spanish', 'OTHER', 23, 23, False, False, 31),
    (43, u'Mexican', 'OTHER', 25, 25, False, False, 35),
    (43, u'Spanish', 'OTHER', 32, 32, False, False, 49),
    (58, u'Executive Order', 'OTHER', 15, 16, False, False, 20),
    (58, u'U', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, False, 21),
    (58, u'S', 'OTHER', 6, 6, False, False, 21),
    (58, u'Navy', 'OTHER', 8, 8, False, False, 21),
    (58, u'108', 'NUMBER', 17, 17, False, False, 21),
    (58, u'American', 'OTHER', 29, 29, False, False, 37),
    (65, u'1950', 'NUMBER', 10, 10, False, False, 6),
    (65, u'World War II', 'OTHER', 1, 3, False, False, 12),
    (65, u'U', 'OTHER', 39, 39, False, False, 60),
    (66, u'1968', 'NUMBER', 8, 8, False, False, 9),
    (66, u'Guam Elective Governor Act', 'OTHER', 12, 15, False, False, 9),
    (66, u'Governor', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, 13),
    (67, u'U', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, False, 45),
    (67, u'S', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, False, 45),
    (67, u'U', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, False, 45),
    (67, u'S', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, False, 45),
    (67, u'242', 'NUMBER', 1, 1, False, False, 55),
    (106, u'U', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, 21),
    (106, u'S', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, False, 21),
    (106, u'Presidential', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, False, 21),
    (106, u'S', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, False, 29),
    (113, u'9,000', 'NUMBER', 24, 26, False, False, 15),
    (113, u'Marines', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, False, 17),
    (113, u'S', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, False, 41),
    (113, u'U', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, 45),
    (130, u'Postal System', 'OTHER', 11, 12, False, False, 61),
    (130, u'U', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, False, 63),
    (130, u'S', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, False, 63),
    (130, u'GU', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, 63),
    (130, u'96932', 'NUMBER', 25, 25, False, False, 63),
    (130, u'U', 'OTHER', 32, 32, False, False, 69),
    (130, u'S', 'OTHER', 34, 34, False, False, 73),
    (137, u'Commercial Port', 'OTHER', 1, 2, False, False, 31),
    (144, u'Guam Customs', 'OTHER', 21, 22, False, False, 39),
    (144, u'Quarantine', 'OTHER', 24, 24, False, False, 48),
    (177, u'Guam National Wildlife Refuge', 'OTHER', 2, 5, False, False, 3),
    (177, u'Mariana', 'OTHER', 22, 22, False, False, 34),
    (178, u'University of Guam', 'OTHER', 1, 3, False, False, 5),
    (178, u'UOG', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, False, 5),
    (178, u'Guam Community College', 'OTHER', 8, 10, False, False, 5),
    (   178,
        u'Western Association of Schools',
        'OTHER',
        17,
        20,
        False,
        False,
        23),
    (178, u'Colleges', 'OTHER', 22, 22, False, False, 33),
    (182, u'Guam Department of Education', 'OTHER', 1, 4, False, False, 6),
    (187, u'Government', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, 15),
    (1, u'one', 'NUMBER', 9, 9, False, False, 3),
    (1, u'American', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, False, 9),
    (43, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 14, 14, True, True, 13),
    (58, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 0, 0, True, True, 21),
    (58, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 21, 21, True, True, 21),
    (65, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 12, 12, True, True, 6),
    (66, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 3, 3, True, True, 9),
    (67, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 20, 20, True, True, 45),
    (106, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 6, 6, True, True, 21),
    (106, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 27, 27, True, True, 21),
    (113, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 15, 15, True, True, 17),
    (113, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 32, 32, True, True, 17),
    (130, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 29, 29, True, True, 63),
    (137, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 4, 4, True, True, 23),
    (137, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 18, 18, True, True, 33),
    (154, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 18, 18, True, True, 14),
    (177, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 8, 8, True, True, 6),
    (187, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 3, 3, True, True, 11),
    (1, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 7, 7, True, True, 1),
    (39, u'The', 'OTHER', 2, 2, True, False, 28),
    (0, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 21, 21, True, False, 23),
    (43, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 1, 1, True, False, 13),
    (130, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 1, 1, True, False, 65),
    (144, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 1, 1, True, False, 21),
    (154, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 4, 4, True, False, 14),
question open class words: ['is', 'most', 'populous', 'city', 'guam']



all results:
[   (100, u'M\xe5tan Guma', u'PERSON', 38, 39, False, True, None),
    (100, u'Suruhanu', u'PERSON', 50, 50, False, True, None),
    (31, u'Antonio Pigafetta', u'PERSON', 0, 1, False, True, 10),
    (29, u'Magellan', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, False, 25),
    (91, u'Chamorros', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, None),
    (91, u'Spanish', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, False, None),
    (91, u'Roman Catholic Christianity', 'OTHER', 11, 13, False, False, None),
    (91, u'Cat\xe1logo', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, False, None),
    (91, u'Philippines', u'LOCATION', 32, 32, False, False, None),
    (100, u'Spanish', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, False, None),
    (31, u'18', 'NUMBER', 9, 9, False, False, 2),
    (31, u'Island', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, False, 2),
actual: (100, u'M\xe5tan Guma', u'PERSON', 38, 39, False, True, None)
question open class words: ['were', 'name', 'outrigger', 'canoes']



    (51, u'75', 'NUMBER', 1, 1, False, True, 7),
    (29, u'41 –', 'NUMBER', 1, 2, False, True, None),
    (29, u'42', 'NUMBER', 3, 3, False, True, None),
    (53, u'77', 'NUMBER', 1, 1, False, True, None),
    (53, u'78', 'NUMBER', 3, 3, False, True, None),
    (55, u'79', 'NUMBER', 1, 1, False, True, None),
    (55, u'1695', 'NUMBER', 4, 4, False, True, None),
    (41, u'2,1669', 'NUMBER', 13, 15, False, True, None),
    (9, u'4,000 years', 'NUMBER', 13, 16, False, True, None),
    (64, u'30 years', 'NUMBER', 21, 22, False, True, None),
    (76, u'5.0', 'NUMBER', 14, 16, False, True, None),
    (84, u'24', 'NUMBER', 27, 27, False, True, 14),
    (119, u'million tourists', 'NUMBER', 24, 25, False, True, 2),
    (119, u'seven', 'NUMBER', 17, 17, False, True, 10),
    (11, u'1668', 'NUMBER', 4, 4, False, True, None),
    (32, u'129 "', 'NUMBER', 1, 2, False, True, None),
    (32, u'three islands', 'NUMBER', 21, 22, False, True, None),
    (34, u'26,1565', 'NUMBER', 15, 17, False, True, None),
    (36, u'51', 'NUMBER', 1, 1, False, True, None),
    (51, u'Capt', 'OTHER', 6, 6, False, False, 2),
    (51, u'Later', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, False, 4),
    (144, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 13, 14, False, False, None),
    (144, u'Guam Customs', 'OTHER', 21, 22, False, False, None),
    (144, u'Quarantine', 'OTHER', 24, 24, False, False, None),
    (29, u'When', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, False, None),
    (29, u'Magellan', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, False, None),
    (29, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 8, 8, False, False, None),
    (53, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 13, 13, False, False, None),
    (55, u'By July', 'OTHER', 2, 3, False, False, None),
    (55, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 13, 13, False, False, None),
    (55, u'Rota', u'LOCATION', 15, 15, False, False, None),
    (55, u'Tinian', u'LOCATION', 17, 17, False, False, None),
    (55, u'Aguigan', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, False, None),
    (   41,
        u'Cathedral Dulce Nombre de Maria',
        'OTHER',
        3,
        7,
        False,
        False,
        None),
    (41, u'February', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, False, None),
    (41, u'Royal College', 'OTHER', 20, 21, False, False, None),
    (41, u'San Juan de Letran', u'LOCATION', 23, 26, False, False, None),
    (9, u'Chamorros', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, None),
    (9, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, False, None),
    (174, u'Department of Agriculture', 'OTHER', 5, 7, False, False, None),
    (174, u'Division', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, False, None),
    (174, u'Aquatic', 'OTHER', 11, 11, False, False, None),
    (174, u'Wildlife Resources', 'OTHER', 13, 14, False, False, None),
    (64, u'Chamorros', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, False, None),
    (64, u'Northern Mariana Chamorros', 'OTHER', 25, 27, False, False, None),
    (64, u'Japan', u'LOCATION', 31, 31, False, False, None),
    (76, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 8, 8, False, False, None),
    (84, u'January', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, False, 10),
    (84, u'F', 'OTHER', 23, 23, False, False, 10),
    (119, u'Hawaii', u'LOCATION', 12, 12, False, False, 15),
    (119, u'Australia', u'LOCATION', 9, 9, False, False, 18),
    (125, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 10, 10, False, False, None),
    (126, u'Over', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, False, None),
    (126, u'Congress', 'OTHER', 8, 8, False, False, None),
    (126, u'Compact Impact', 'OTHER', 12, 13, False, False, None),
    (126, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 17, 17, False, False, None),
    (   126,
        u'LOCATION',
        20,
        22,
        False,
        False,
        None),
    (126, u'Hawaii', u'LOCATION', 24, 24, False, False, None),
    (126, u'Compact', 'OTHER', 35, 35, False, False, None),
    (11, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 0, 0, False, False, None),
    (11, u'Diego Luis de San Vitores', u'PERSON', 9, 13, False, False, None),
    (11, u'Catholic', 'OTHER', 16, 16, False, False, None),
    (30, u'Proas', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, False, None),
    (30, u'Magellan', 'OTHER', 10, 10, False, False, None),
    (30, u'Latinas', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, None),
    (30, u'Islands', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, False, None),
    (30, u'Lateen', u'LOCATION', 22, 22, False, False, None),
    (32, u'Those', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, False, None),
    (32, u'Islas de los Ladrones', 'OTHER', 23, 26, False, False, None),
    (32, u'Islands', 'OTHER', 28, 28, False, False, None),
    (34, u'Magellan', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, None),
    (34, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 6, 6, False, False, None),
    (34, u'Spain', u'LOCATION', 12, 12, False, False, None),
    (34, u'January', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, False, None),
    (34, u'General', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, False, None),
    (36, u'To', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, False, None),
    (36, u'Pacific', u'LOCATION', 5, 5, False, False, None),
    (36, u'Spain', u'LOCATION', 8, 8, False, False, None),
    (36, u'Fort Nuestra Se\xf1ora', 'OTHER', 21, 23, False, False, None),
    (36, u'Soledad', 'OTHER', 26, 26, False, False, None),
    (36, u'Umatac', u'LOCATION', 28, 28, False, False, None),
    (51, u'Jose de Quiroga', u'PERSON', 8, 10, True, False, 0),
    (53, u'Quiroga', u'PERSON', 4, 4, True, False, None),
    (55, u'Quiroga', u'PERSON', 6, 6, True, False, None)]
question: In what year did Jose de Quiroga arrive?
expected: 1680
expected sentence: :75–76 Later, Capt. Jose de Quiroga arrived in 1680 and continued some of the development projects started by his predecessors.
question open class words: ['year', 'did', 'jose']



all results:
[   (31, u'Antonio Pigafetta', u'PERSON', 0, 1, False, True, 47),
    (123, u'Palau', u'PERSON', 26, 26, False, True, None),
    (59, u'Emilio Aguinaldo', u'PERSON', 31, 32, False, True, 65),
    (59, u'Apolinario Mabini', u'PERSON', 34, 35, False, True, 68),
    (31, u'18', 'NUMBER', 9, 9, False, False, 27),
    (31, u'Island', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, False, 27),
    (31, u'Magellan', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, False, 35),
    (31, u'one', 'NUMBER', 3, 3, False, False, 41),
    (136, u'USA', u'LOCATION', 16, 16, False, False, 46),
    (136, u'Americas', u'LOCATION', 5, 5, False, False, 80),
    (103, u'While', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, False, None),
    (103, u'Chamorros', 'OTHER', 22, 22, False, False, None),
    (103, u'Chamorros', 'OTHER', 37, 37, False, False, None),
    (103, u'Chamorro', u'LOCATION', 47, 47, False, False, None),
    (30, u'Latinas', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, 5),
    (91, u'Chamorros', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, None),
    (91, u'Spanish', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, False, None),
    (91, u'Roman Catholic Christianity', 'OTHER', 11, 13, False, False, None),
    (91, u'Cat\xe1logo', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, False, None),
    (91, u'Philippines', u'LOCATION', 32, 32, False, False, None),
    (67, u'Since Guam', 'OTHER', 2, 3, False, False, 87),
    (67, u'242', 'NUMBER', 1, 1, False, False, 105),
    (123, u'Compacts', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, None),
    (123, u'Free Association', 'OTHER', 3, 4, False, False, None),
    (123, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 7, 8, False, False, None),
    (   123,
        u'Federated States of Micronesia',
        u'LOCATION',
        11,
        14,
        False,
        False,
        None),
    (123, u'Republic', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, None),
    (123, u'Marshall Islands', u'LOCATION', 20, 21, False, False, None),
    (123, u'Republic', 'OTHER', 24, 24, False, False, None),
    (123, u'Trust Territory', 'OTHER', 33, 34, False, False, None),
    (123, u'Pacific Islands', u'LOCATION', 37, 38, False, False, None),
    (65, u'1950', 'NUMBER', 10, 10, False, False, 87),
    (65, u'Guam Organic Act', 'OTHER', 6, 8, False, False, 91),
    (65, u'World War II', 'OTHER', 1, 3, False, False, 114),
    (106, u'Presidential', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, False, 67),
    (106, u'Electoral College', 'OTHER', 33, 34, False, False, 127),
    (130, u'Postal System', 'OTHER', 11, 12, False, False, 109),
    (130, u'GU', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, 113),
    (179, u'76', 'NUMBER', 10, 10, False, False, 13),
    (179, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 22, 23, False, False, 41),
    (0, u'IPA', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, False, 29),
    (0, u'Gu\xe5h\xe5n', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, False, 32),
    (0, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 31, 32, False, False, 49),
    (58, u'Navy', 'OTHER', 8, 8, False, False, 27),
    (58, u'1898', 'NUMBER', 13, 13, False, False, 37),
    (113, u'8,600', 'NUMBER', 18, 20, False, False, 47),
    (113, u'9,000', 'NUMBER', 24, 26, False, False, 59),
    (144, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 13, 14, False, False, 30),
    (144, u'Guam Customs', 'OTHER', 21, 22, False, False, 39),
    (13, u'21,1898', 'NUMBER', 14, 16, False, False, 3),
    (13, u'Spanish', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, False, 9),
    (14, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 11, 12, False, False, 3),
    (14, u'10,1898', 'NUMBER', 15, 17, False, False, 7),
    (59, u'Navy', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, False, 40),
    (59, u'1899', 'NUMBER', 12, 12, False, False, 47),
    (59, u'13', 'NUMBER', 23, 23, False, False, 58),
    (59, u'Following', 'OTHER', 24, 24, False, False, 59),
    (59, u'Philippine', u'LOCATION', 26, 26, False, False, 61),
    (112, u'S', 'OTHER', 5, 5, True, False, 34),
    (112, u'U', 'OTHER', 3, 3, True, False, 42),
    (136, u'U', 'OTHER', 27, 27, True, False, 24),
    (136, u'S', 'OTHER', 29, 29, True, False, 24),
    (67, u'S', 'OTHER', 9, 9, True, False, 59),
    (67, u'U', 'OTHER', 13, 13, True, False, 59),
    (67, u'U', 'OTHER', 7, 7, True, False, 65),
    (67, u'S', 'OTHER', 15, 15, True, False, 65),
    (67, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 20, 20, True, False, 90),
    (65, u'U', 'OTHER', 39, 39, True, False, 70),
    (65, u'S', 'OTHER', 41, 41, True, False, 76),
    (65, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 12, 12, True, False, 81),
    (106, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 6, 6, True, False, 55),
    (106, u'U', 'OTHER', 17, 17, True, False, 55),
    (106, u'S', 'OTHER', 19, 19, True, False, 59),
    (130, u'S', 'OTHER', 9, 9, True, False, 113),
    (130, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 29, 29, True, False, 113),
    (130, u'U', 'OTHER', 7, 7, True, False, 117),
    (130, u'U', 'OTHER', 32, 32, True, False, 119),
    (130, u'S', 'OTHER', 34, 34, True, False, 127),
    (130, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 1, 1, True, False, 143),
    (179, u'U', 'OTHER', 11, 11, True, False, 12),
    (179, u'S', 'OTHER', 13, 13, True, False, 14),
    (0, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 21, 21, True, False, 23),
    (58, u'U', 'OTHER', 4, 4, True, False, 23),
    (58, u'S', 'OTHER', 6, 6, True, False, 23),
    (58, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 0, 0, True, False, 31),
    (113, u'S', 'OTHER', 3, 3, True, False, 43),
    (113, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 15, 15, True, False, 43),
    (113, u'U', 'OTHER', 1, 1, True, False, 47),
    (113, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 32, 32, True, False, 77),
    (144, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 1, 1, True, False, 21),
actual: (31, u'Antonio Pigafetta', u'PERSON', 0, 1, False, True, 47)
question open class words: ['is', 'name', 'u', 's', 'state', 'could', 'possibly', 'form', 'union', 'guam']



all results:
    (141, u'United Airlines', 'OTHER', 18, 19, False, True, 7),
    (67, u'Since Guam', 'OTHER', 2, 3, False, True, None),
    (67, u'U', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, True, None),
    (67, u'S', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, True, None),
    (67, u'U', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, True, None),
    (67, u'S', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, True, None),
    (124, u'Compacts', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, None),
    (124, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 27, 27, False, True, None),
    (67, u'242', 'NUMBER', 1, 1, False, False, None),
    (3, u'2015,161', 'NUMBER', 1, 3, False, False, None),
    (3, u'785 people', 'NUMBER', 5, 6, False, False, None),
question open class words: ['major', 'airline', 'resides', 'airport']



all results:
[   (31, u'Antonio Pigafetta', u'PERSON', 0, 1, False, True, 50),
    (43, u'Chamorro', u'PERSON', 4, 4, False, True, 13),
        'OTHER',
        14,
        18,
        False,
        29),
    (180, u'Schools', 'OTHER', 20, 20, False, False, 49),
    (31, u'Island', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, False, 30),
    (31, u'Sails', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, False, 30),
    (31, u'Magellan', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, False, 42),
    (31, u'one', 'NUMBER', 3, 3, False, False, 46),
    (178, u'Guam Community College', 'OTHER', 8, 10, False, False, 5),
    (178, u'UOG', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, False, 10),
    (178, u'University of Guam', 'OTHER', 1, 3, False, False, 12),
    (   178,
        u'Western Association of Schools',
        'OTHER',
        17,
        20,
        False,
        False,
        30),
    (30, u'Latinas', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, 5),
    (91, u'Chamorros', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, None),
    (91, u'Spanish', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, False, None),
    (91, u'Roman Catholic Christianity', 'OTHER', 11, 13, False, False, None),
    (91, u'Cat\xe1logo', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, False, None),
    (91, u'Philippines', u'LOCATION', 32, 32, False, False, None),
    (106, u'Electoral College', 'OTHER', 33, 34, False, False, 33),
    (106, u'Presidential', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, False, 34),
    (106, u'S', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, False, 36),
    (106, u'U', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, 38),
    (106, u'S', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, False, 61),
    (41, u'Cathedral Dulce Nombre de Maria', 'OTHER', 3, 7, False, False, 17),
    (41, u'2,1669', 'NUMBER', 13, 15, False, False, 19),
    (41, u'February', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, False, 21),
    (41, u'San Juan de Letran', u'LOCATION', 23, 26, False, False, 25),
    (177, u'Guam National Wildlife Refuge', 'OTHER', 2, 5, False, False, 17),
    (29, u'Magellan', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, False, 14),
    (29, u'41 –', 'NUMBER', 1, 2, False, False, 20),
    (185, u'6,000 miles', 'NUMBER', 15, 18, False, False, 18),
    (185, u'9,700 km', 'NUMBER', 20, 23, False, False, 28),
    (185, u'U', 'OTHER', 27, 27, False, False, 42),
    (185, u'American', 'OTHER', 47, 47, False, False, 82),
    (0, u'IPA', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, False, 29),
    (0, u'Gu\xe5h\xe5n', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, False, 32),
    (0, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 31, 32, False, False, 49),
    (43, u'Northern Marianas', u'LOCATION', 17, 18, False, False, 19),
    (43, u'Spanish', 'OTHER', 23, 23, False, False, 31),
    (43, u'Mexican', 'OTHER', 25, 25, False, False, 35),
    (43, u'Spanish', 'OTHER', 32, 32, False, False, 49),
    (58, u'Executive Order', 'OTHER', 15, 16, False, False, 20),
    (58, u'U', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, False, 21),
    (58, u'S', 'OTHER', 6, 6, False, False, 21),
    (58, u'Navy', 'OTHER', 8, 8, False, False, 21),
    (58, u'108', 'NUMBER', 17, 17, False, False, 21),
    (58, u'Japan', u'LOCATION', 50, 50, False, False, 79),
    (65, u'1950', 'NUMBER', 10, 10, False, False, 6),
    (65, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 20, 21, False, False, 22),
    (65, u'U', 'OTHER', 39, 39, False, False, 60),
    (66, u'1968', 'NUMBER', 8, 8, False, False, 9),
    (66, u'Guam Elective Governor Act', 'OTHER', 12, 15, False, False, 9),
    (66, u'Governor', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, 13),
    (67, u'U', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, False, 45),
    (67, u'S', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, False, 45),
    (67, u'U', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, False, 45),
    (67, u'S', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, False, 45),
    (113, u'9,000', 'NUMBER', 24, 26, False, False, 15),
    (113, u'Marines', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, False, 17),
    (113, u'Japan', u'LOCATION', 36, 36, False, False, 25),
    (113, u'S', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, False, 41),
    (113, u'U', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, 45),
    (130, u'Postal System', 'OTHER', 11, 12, False, False, 61),
    (130, u'U', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, False, 63),
    (130, u'S', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, False, 63),
    (130, u'GU', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, 63),
    (130, u'96932', 'NUMBER', 25, 25, False, False, 63),
    (130, u'U', 'OTHER', 32, 32, False, False, 69),
    (130, u'S', 'OTHER', 34, 34, False, False, 73),
    (144, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 13, 14, False, False, 30),
    (144, u'Guam Customs', 'OTHER', 21, 22, False, False, 39),
    (180, u'Christian', 'OTHER', 6, 6, True, False, 15),
    (106, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 27, 27, True, False, 28),
    (106, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 6, 6, True, False, 49),
    (177, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 8, 8, True, False, 17),
    (29, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 8, 8, True, False, 8),
    (0, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 21, 21, True, False, 23),
    (43, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 1, 1, True, False, 13),
    (43, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 14, 14, True, False, 13),
    (58, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 0, 0, True, False, 21),
    (58, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 21, 21, True, False, 21),
    (65, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 12, 12, True, False, 6),
    (66, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 3, 3, True, False, 9),
    (67, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 20, 20, True, False, 45),
    (113, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 15, 15, True, False, 17),
    (113, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 32, 32, True, False, 17),
    (130, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 29, 29, True, False, 63),
    (130, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 1, 1, True, False, 65),
    (137, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 4, 4, True, False, 15),
    (137, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 18, 18, True, False, 27),
actual: (31, u'Antonio Pigafetta', u'PERSON', 0, 1, False, True, 50)
question open class words: ['is', 'name', 'small', 'christian', 'college', 'guam']



all results:
[   (31, u'Antonio Pigafetta', u'PERSON', 0, 1, False, True, 10),
    (43, u'Chamorro', u'PERSON', 4, 4, False, True, 13),
    (30, u'Latinas', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, 5),
    (31, u'18', 'NUMBER', 9, 9, False, False, 2),
    (31, u'Island', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, False, 2),
    (31, u'Magellan', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, False, 6),
    (91, u'Chamorros', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, None),
    (91, u'Spanish', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, False, None),
    (91, u'Roman Catholic Christianity', 'OTHER', 11, 13, False, False, None),
    (91, u'Cat\xe1logo', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, False, None),
    (91, u'Philippines', u'LOCATION', 32, 32, False, False, None),
    (0, u'IPA', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, False, 29),
    (0, u'Gu\xe5h\xe5n', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, False, 32),
    (0, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 31, 32, False, False, 49),
    (43, u'Northern Marianas', u'LOCATION', 17, 18, False, False, 19),
    (43, u'Spanish', 'OTHER', 23, 23, False, False, 31),
    (43, u'Mexican', 'OTHER', 25, 25, False, False, 35),
    (43, u'Spanish', 'OTHER', 32, 32, False, False, 49),
    (58, u'Executive Order', 'OTHER', 15, 16, False, False, 20),
    (58, u'U', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, False, 21),
    (58, u'S', 'OTHER', 6, 6, False, False, 21),
    (58, u'Navy', 'OTHER', 8, 8, False, False, 21),
    (58, u'108', 'NUMBER', 17, 17, False, False, 21),
    (58, u'Japan', u'LOCATION', 50, 50, False, False, 79),
    (65, u'1950', 'NUMBER', 10, 10, False, False, 6),
    (65, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 20, 21, False, False, 22),
    (65, u'U', 'OTHER', 39, 39, False, False, 60),
    (66, u'1968', 'NUMBER', 8, 8, False, False, 9),
    (66, u'Guam Elective Governor Act', 'OTHER', 12, 15, False, False, 9),
    (66, u'Governor', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, 13),
    (67, u'U', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, False, 45),
    (67, u'S', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, False, 45),
    (67, u'U', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, False, 45),
    (67, u'S', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, False, 45),
    (67, u'242', 'NUMBER', 1, 1, False, False, 55),
    (106, u'U', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, 21),
    (106, u'S', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, False, 21),
    (106, u'Presidential', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, False, 21),
    (106, u'S', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, False, 29),
    (113, u'9,000', 'NUMBER', 24, 26, False, False, 15),
    (113, u'Marines', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, False, 17),
    (113, u'Japan', u'LOCATION', 36, 36, False, False, 25),
    (113, u'S', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, False, 41),
    (113, u'U', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, 45),
    (130, u'Postal System', 'OTHER', 11, 12, False, False, 61),
    (130, u'U', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, False, 63),
    (130, u'S', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, False, 63),
    (130, u'GU', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, 63),
    (130, u'96932', 'NUMBER', 25, 25, False, False, 63),
    (130, u'U', 'OTHER', 32, 32, False, False, 69),
    (130, u'S', 'OTHER', 34, 34, False, False, 73),
    (144, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 13, 14, False, False, 30),
    (144, u'Guam Customs', 'OTHER', 21, 22, False, False, 39),
    (144, u'Quarantine', 'OTHER', 24, 24, False, False, 48),
    (154, u'Chamorro', u'LOCATION', 14, 14, False, False, 14),
    (177, u'Guam National Wildlife Refuge', 'OTHER', 2, 5, False, False, 3),
    (177, u'Mariana', 'OTHER', 22, 22, False, False, 34),
    (178, u'University of Guam', 'OTHER', 1, 3, False, False, 5),
    (178, u'UOG', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, False, 5),
    (178, u'Guam Community College', 'OTHER', 8, 10, False, False, 5),
    (   178,
        u'Western Association of Schools',
        'OTHER',
        17,
        20,
        False,
        False,
        23),
    (178, u'Colleges', 'OTHER', 22, 22, False, False, 33),
    (182, u'Guam Department of Education', 'OTHER', 1, 4, False, False, 6),
    (1, u'one', 'NUMBER', 9, 9, False, False, 3),
    (1, u'Pacific Ocean', u'LOCATION', 4, 5, False, False, 5),
    (187, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 3, 3, True, False, 41),
    (0, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 21, 21, True, False, 23),
    (43, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 1, 1, True, False, 13),
    (43, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 14, 14, True, False, 13),
    (58, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 0, 0, True, False, 21),
    (58, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 21, 21, True, False, 21),
    (65, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 12, 12, True, False, 6),
    (66, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 3, 3, True, False, 9),
    (67, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 20, 20, True, False, 45),
    (106, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 6, 6, True, False, 21),
    (106, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 27, 27, True, False, 21),
    (113, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 15, 15, True, False, 17),
    (113, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 32, 32, True, False, 17),
    (130, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 29, 29, True, False, 63),
    (130, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 1, 1, True, False, 65),
    (137, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 4, 4, True, False, 15),
    (137, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 18, 18, True, False, 27),
    (144, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 1, 1, True, False, 21),
    (154, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 4, 4, True, False, 14),
    (154, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 18, 18, True, False, 14),
    (177, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 8, 8, True, False, 6),
    (182, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 10, 10, True, False, 9),
actual: (31, u'Antonio Pigafetta', u'PERSON', 0, 1, False, True, 10)
question open class words: ['is', 'name', 'main', 'health', 'care', 'facility', 'guam']



    (12, u'Olympics', 'OTHER', 38, 38, False, True, 87),
    (36, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 11, 11, False, True, 14),
    (104, u'Pulldown', 'OTHER', 39, 39, False, True, 52),
    (104, u'Over', 'OTHER', 41, 41, False, True, 52),
    (104, u'TV', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, True, 154),
    (104, u'NTSC', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 178),
    (59, u'HD Model Station', 'OTHER', 48, 50, False, True, 31),
    (59, u'WRAL', 'OTHER', 33, 33, False, True, 33),
    (59, u'TV', 'OTHER', 35, 35, False, True, 33),
    (59, u'July', 'OTHER', 61, 61, False, True, 35),
    (59, u'HD', 'OTHER', 25, 25, False, True, 37),
    (59, u'WRAL', 'OTHER', 23, 23, False, True, 41),
    (59, u'WHD', 'OTHER', 68, 68, False, True, 49),
    (59, u'July', 'OTHER', 11, 11, False, True, 65),
    (59, u'NBC', 'OTHER', 78, 78, False, True, 69),
    (59, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, True, 81),
    (59, u'TV', 'OTHER', 85, 85, False, True, 83),
    (68, u'Belgian TV', 'OTHER', 10, 11, False, True, None),
    (68, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, True, None),
    (68, u'European', 'OTHER', 24, 24, False, True, None),
    (68, u'HD', 'OTHER', 29, 29, False, True, None),
    (68, u'HD TVs', 'OTHER', 33, 34, False, True, None),
    (68, u'HD', 'OTHER', 38, 38, False, True, None),
    (68, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 45, 45, False, True, None),
    (72, u'HD', 'OTHER', 42, 42, False, True, 2),
    (72, u'Astra', 'OTHER', 44, 44, False, True, 4),
    (72, u'HD', 'OTHER', 49, 49, False, True, 9),
    (72, u'Satellite Monitor', 'OTHER', 28, 29, False, True, 11),
    (72, u'TVs', 'OTHER', 51, 51, False, True, 11),
    (72, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 20, 20, False, True, 20),
    (72, u'European', 'OTHER', 71, 71, False, True, 31),
    (72, u'TV', 'OTHER', 74, 74, False, True, 34),
    (72, u'HD', 'OTHER', 78, 78, False, True, 38),
    (72, u'Astra', 'OTHER', 85, 85, False, True, 45),
    (26, u'BS', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, True, 2),
    (26, u'November', 'OTHER', 22, 22, False, True, 7),
    (100, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, True, 5),
    (107, u'TV', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, True, 4),
    (107, u'ABC', 'OTHER', 28, 28, False, True, 27),
    (107, u'Ion Television', 'OTHER', 33, 34, False, True, 32),
    (107, u'CBS', 'OTHER', 40, 40, False, True, 39),
    (107, u'My Network TV', 'OTHER', 42, 44, False, True, 41),
    (107, u'NBC', 'OTHER', 46, 46, False, True, 45),
    (107, u'PBS', 'OTHER', 48, 48, False, True, 47),
    (107, u'CW', 'OTHER', 52, 52, False, True, 51),
    (113, u'IPTV', 'OTHER', 16, 16, False, True, None),
    (113, u'GoogleTV Roku', 'OTHER', 19, 20, False, True, None),
    (113, u'Smart Televisions', 'OTHER', 28, 29, False, True, None),
    (113, u'Blu', 'OTHER', 31, 31, False, True, None),
    (113, u'BD', 'OTHER', 37, 37, False, True, None),
    (122, u'Blu', 'OTHER', 27, 27, False, True, None),
    (10, u'NTSC', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, True, None),
    (11, u'PAL', 'OTHER', 11, 11, False, True, None),
    (11, u'SECAM', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, True, None),
    (18, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, True, 7),
    (18, u'NTSC', 'OTHER', 26, 26, False, True, 19),
    (18, u'PAL', 'OTHER', 29, 29, False, True, 22),
    (18, u'European', 'OTHER', 39, 39, False, True, 32),
    (18, u'PAL', 'OTHER', 43, 43, False, True, 36),
    (18, u'SECAM', 'OTHER', 45, 45, False, True, 38),
    (33, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, None),
    (33, u'NHK', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, True, None),
    (33, u'MUSE', 'OTHER', 10, 10, False, True, None),
    (40, u'Digital Video Broadcasting', 'OTHER', 6, 8, False, True, 0),
    (40, u'DVB', 'OTHER', 10, 10, False, True, 2),
    (12, u'Tokyo', u'LOCATION', 37, 37, False, False, 84),
    (84, u'60i.60', 'NUMBER', 38, 40, False, False, 30),
    (84, u'59.94i', 'NUMBER', 32, 34, False, False, 32),
    (84, u'24p', 'NUMBER', 29, 29, False, False, 39),
    (84, u'23.976p', 'NUMBER', 23, 25, False, False, 49),
    (85, u'23.976p', 'NUMBER', 16, 18, False, False, 14),
    (85, u'60i', 'NUMBER', 13, 13, False, False, 18),
    (85, u'24p', 'NUMBER', 21, 21, False, False, 24),
    (85, u'59.94i', 'NUMBER', 6, 8, False, False, 28),
    (85, u'29.97i', 'NUMBER', 2, 4, False, False, 44),
    (36, u'seven broadcasters', 'NUMBER', 14, 15, False, False, 20),
    (104, u'3', 'NUMBER', 36, 36, False, False, 52),
    (104, u'one', 'NUMBER', 49, 49, False, False, 52),
    (104, u'20', 'NUMBER', 59, 59, False, False, 70),
    (104, u'30', 'NUMBER', 76, 76, False, False, 122),
    (104, u'30 frame', 'NUMBER', 11, 12, False, False, 134),
    (104, u'12', 'NUMBER', 92, 92, False, False, 186),
    (59, u'Raleigh', u'LOCATION', 38, 38, False, False, 33),
    (59, u'31,1996', 'NUMBER', 62, 64, False, False, 37),
    (68, u'Alfacam', u'PERSON', 14, 14, False, False, None),
    (72, u'2010', 'NUMBER', 33, 33, False, False, 7),
    (72, u'Europe', u'LOCATION', 54, 54, False, False, 14),
    (72, u'2010', 'NUMBER', 59, 59, False, False, 19),
    (72, u'27 %', 'NUMBER', 67, 68, False, False, 27),
    (26, u'1991', 'NUMBER', 12, 12, False, False, 3),
    (26, u'1989', 'NUMBER', 5, 5, False, False, 10),
    (107, u'1940s', 'NUMBER', 15, 15, False, False, 14),
    (107, u'Fox', u'PERSON', 30, 30, False, False, 29),
    (107, u'720p resolution', 'NUMBER', 37, 38, False, False, 36),
    (10, u'1953', 'NUMBER', 16, 16, False, False, None),
    (10, u'525 lines', 'NUMBER', 31, 32, False, False, None),
    (11, u'625 line', 'NUMBER', 21, 22, False, False, None),
question open class words: ['is', 'japan', 'broadcasting', 'corporation', 'called']



all results:
    (36, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 11, 11, False, True, 11),
    (13, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 6, 6, False, True, 6),
    (13, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 24, 24, False, True, 24),
    (14, u'Color', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, True, 1),
    (14, u'Hz', 'OTHER', 23, 23, False, True, 19),
    (24, u'Japanese', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, True, 3),
    (26, u'November', 'OTHER', 22, 22, False, True, 9),
    (26, u'BS', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, True, 14),
    (12, u'Tokyo', u'LOCATION', 37, 37, False, False, 61),
    (36, u'seven broadcasters', 'NUMBER', 14, 15, False, False, 14),
    (14, u'1972', 'NUMBER', 9, 9, False, False, 5),
    (14, u'5', 'NUMBER', 16, 16, False, False, 12),
    (24, u'5', 'NUMBER', 17, 17, False, False, 10),
    (26, u'25,1994', 'NUMBER', 23, 25, False, False, 6),
    (26, u'1989', 'NUMBER', 5, 5, False, False, 26),
    (12, u'NHK', 'OTHER', 5, 5, True, True, 3),
    (33, u'NHK', 'OTHER', 7, 7, True, True, 0),
    (13, u'NHK', 'OTHER', 0, 0, True, True, 0),
    (14, u'NHK', 'OTHER', 4, 4, True, True, 0),
    (24, u'NHK', 'OTHER', 7, 7, True, True, 0),
    (26, u'NHK', 'OTHER', 31, 31, True, True, 0),
    (36, u'Japan', u'LOCATION', 0, 0, True, False, 0)]
question open class words: ['does', 'nhk', 'stand', 'japan']



all results:
    (14, u'60', 'NUMBER', 22, 22, False, True, 5),
    (27, u'1981', 'NUMBER', 1, 1, False, True, 54),
    (22, u'1958', 'NUMBER', 1, 1, False, True, 39),
    (72, u'2010', 'NUMBER', 33, 33, False, True, 107),
    (72, u'2010', 'NUMBER', 59, 59, False, True, 135),
    (72, u'27 %', 'NUMBER', 67, 68, False, True, 158),
    (117, u'722', 'NUMBER', 62, 62, False, True, 32),
    (53, u'709', 'NUMBER', 17, 17, False, True, 15),
    (53, u'709', 'NUMBER', 11, 11, False, True, 27),
    (53, u'1,080', 'NUMBER', 49, 51, False, True, 49),
    (94, u'16', 'NUMBER', 9, 9, False, True, 7),
    (24, u'Japanese', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, False, 55),
    (14, u'Hz', 'OTHER', 23, 23, False, False, 7),
    (27, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 14, 15, False, False, 21),
    (27, u'Japanese', 'OTHER', 27, 27, False, False, 24),
    (27, u'MUSE', 'OTHER', 4, 4, False, False, 45),
    (22, u'Transformer', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, False, 13),
    (   22,
        u'Трансформатор',
        'OTHER',
        11,
        11,
        False,
        19),
    (22, u'Russian', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, False, 23),
    (22, u'Soviet Union', u'LOCATION', 4, 5, False, False, 31),
    (41, u'DVB', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, None),
    (41, u'ETSI', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, False, None),
    (72, u'Astra', 'OTHER', 44, 44, False, False, 100),
    (72, u'Satellite Monitor', 'OTHER', 28, 29, False, False, 109),
    (72, u'TVs', 'OTHER', 51, 51, False, False, 111),
    (72, u'SES', 'OTHER', 24, 24, False, False, 116),
    (72, u'Europe', u'LOCATION', 54, 54, False, False, 120),
    (72, u'TV', 'OTHER', 74, 74, False, False, 180),
    (66, u'January', 'OTHER', 6, 6, False, False, 23),
    (66, u'Belgian', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, False, 23),
    (66, u'Euro1080', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, False, 23),
    (66, u'HD1', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, 23),
    (66, u'Vienna', u'LOCATION', 22, 22, False, False, 23),
    (66, u'Concert', 'OTHER', 27, 27, False, False, 29),
    (59, u'WRAL', 'OTHER', 23, 23, False, False, 73),
    (59, u'TV', 'OTHER', 35, 35, False, False, 81),
    (59, u'Raleigh', u'LOCATION', 38, 38, False, False, 84),
    (59, u'Raleigh', u'LOCATION', 17, 17, False, False, 87),
    (59, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 7, 8, False, False, 113),
    (59, u'Washington', u'LOCATION', 52, 52, False, False, 120),
    (59, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, False, 129),
    (59, u'D', 'OTHER', 54, 54, False, False, 130),
    (59, u'July', 'OTHER', 61, 61, False, False, 165),
    (59, u'TV', 'OTHER', 70, 70, False, False, 210),
    (59, u'NBC', 'OTHER', 78, 78, False, False, 250),
    (59, u'TV', 'OTHER', 85, 85, False, False, 285),
    (52, u'IWP11', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, 35),
    (52, u'BBC', 'OTHER', 24, 24, False, False, 56),
    (52, u'Research', 'OTHER', 27, 27, False, False, 65),
    (52, u'Development', 'OTHER', 29, 29, False, False, 71),
    (52, u'Kingswood Warren', u'LOCATION', 32, 33, False, False, 80),
    (123, u'W', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, False, 16),
    (123, u'VHS', 'OTHER', 16, 16, False, False, 16),
    (16, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, False, None),
    (35, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, False, None),
    (35, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, False, None),
    (35, u'Sony', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, False, None),
    (35, u'HDVS', 'OTHER', 22, 22, False, False, None),
    (67, u'September', 'OTHER', 10, 10, False, False, 6),
    (67, u'IBC', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, False, 9),
    (67, u'HD1', 'OTHER', 27, 27, False, False, 11),
    (67, u'Europe', u'LOCATION', 42, 42, False, False, 26),
    (114, u'Windows Media Center HTPC', 'OTHER', 34, 37, False, False, 42),
    (114, u'Blu', u'LOCATION', 14, 14, False, False, 45),
    (114, u'Microsoft', 'OTHER', 23, 23, False, False, 45),
    (114, u'Xbox', 'OTHER', 26, 26, False, False, 45),
    (114, u'Netflix', 'OTHER', 32, 32, False, False, 45),
    (114, u'Zune', 'OTHER', 43, 43, False, False, 45),
    (114, u'PlayStation', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, False, 53),
    (114, u'Sony', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, False, 59),
    (117, u'Dish Network', 'OTHER', 54, 55, False, False, 31),
    (117, u'Sky HD', 'OTHER', 45, 46, False, False, 32),
    (117, u'VIP', 'OTHER', 58, 58, False, False, 32),
    (117, u'VIP', 'OTHER', 61, 61, False, False, 32),
    (117, u'Digital', 'OTHER', 66, 66, False, False, 32),
    (117, u'TiVo', 'OTHER', 72, 72, False, False, 32),
    (117, u'Series', 'OTHER', 75, 75, False, False, 32),
    (117, u'Digital', 'OTHER', 41, 41, False, False, 42),
    (117, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 83, 83, False, False, 42),
    (117, u'HTPC', 'OTHER', 86, 86, False, False, 48),
    (117, u'DirecTV', 'OTHER', 35, 35, False, False, 54),
    (117, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 26, 26, False, False, 72),
    (117, u'VHS', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, False, 86),
    (117, u'W', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, 90),
    (117, u'VHS', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, False, 94),
    (117, u'Data', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, False, 98),
    (117, u'VHS', 'OTHER', 11, 11, False, False, 102),
    (117, u'Digital', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, False, 106),
    (117, u'VHS', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, False, 110),
    (117, u'D', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, False, 114),
    (50, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, False, 25),
    (53, u'Rec', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, False, 19),
    (53, u'R BT', 'OTHER', 8, 9, False, False, 31),
    (53, u'R Recommendation ITU', 'OTHER', 4, 6, False, False, 37),
    (53, u'ITU', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, False, 45),
    (94, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, False, 15),
    (24, u'5', 'NUMBER', 17, 17, True, True, 28),
    (51, u'5', 'NUMBER', 42, 42, True, True, 106),
    (51, u'3', 'NUMBER', 44, 44, True, True, 114),
    (14, u'3 aspect', 'NUMBER', 18, 19, True, True, 1),
    (14, u'5', 'NUMBER', 16, 16, True, True, 7),
    (7, u'5', 'NUMBER', 45, 45, True, True, 67),
    (7, u'3', 'NUMBER', 54, 54, True, True, 85),
    (114, u'3', 'NUMBER', 4, 4, True, True, 51),
    (117, u'3', 'NUMBER', 76, 76, True, True, 32),
    (24, u'NHK', 'OTHER', 7, 7, True, False, 40),
    (14, u'NHK', 'OTHER', 4, 4, True, False, 31),
    (72, u'HD', 'OTHER', 42, 42, True, False, 98),
    (72, u'HD', 'OTHER', 49, 49, True, False, 105),
    (72, u'HD', 'OTHER', 78, 78, True, False, 192),
    (59, u'HD', 'OTHER', 25, 25, True, False, 71),
    (123, u'HD', 'OTHER', 9, 9, True, False, 16),
    (114, u'HD', 'OTHER', 7, 7, True, False, 45),
    (114, u'HD', 'OTHER', 52, 52, True, False, 45),
    (117, u'HD', 'OTHER', 78, 78, True, False, 32)]
question: In what year did NHK first develop consumer HD television with a 5:3 aspect ratio?
expected: 1979
expected sentence: In 1979, the Japanese state broadcaster NHK first developed consumer high-definition television with a 5:3 display aspect ratio.
question open class words: ['year', 'did', 'first', 'develop', 'consumer', 'hd', 'television', 'aspect', 'ratio']



all results:
[   (57, u'Sarnoff', u'PERSON', 47, 47, False, True, 74),
    (57, u'Thomson', u'PERSON', 49, 49, False, True, 78),
    (68, u'Alfacam', u'PERSON', 14, 14, False, True, 34),
    (15, u'Charles Ginsburg', u'PERSON', 13, 14, False, True, 9),
    (28, u'Ronald Reagan', u'PERSON', 11, 12, False, True, 16),
    (41, u'DVB', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, 5),
    (41, u'ETSI', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, False, 6),
    (90, u'10', 'NUMBER', 7, 7, False, False, None),
    (90, u'YUV', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, False, None),
    (90, u'RGB', 'OTHER', 35, 35, False, False, None),
    (32, u'1990s', 'NUMBER', 8, 8, False, False, 28),
    (117, u'VHS', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, False, 90),
    (117, u'W', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, 92),
    (117, u'DirecTV', 'OTHER', 35, 35, False, False, 92),
    (117, u'VHS', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, False, 94),
    (117, u'Data', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, False, 96),
    (117, u'VHS', 'OTHER', 11, 11, False, False, 98),
    (117, u'Digital', 'OTHER', 41, 41, False, False, 98),
    (117, u'Digital', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, False, 100),
    (117, u'Sky HD', 'OTHER', 45, 46, False, False, 101),
    (117, u'VHS', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, False, 102),
    (117, u'D', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, False, 104),
    (117, u'Dish Network', 'OTHER', 54, 55, False, False, 110),
    (117, u'VIP', 'OTHER', 58, 58, False, False, 115),
    (117, u'622', 'NUMBER', 59, 59, False, False, 116),
    (117, u'VIP', 'OTHER', 61, 61, False, False, 118),
    (117, u'722', 'NUMBER', 62, 62, False, False, 119),
    (117, u'Digital', 'OTHER', 66, 66, False, False, 123),
    (117, u'TiVo', 'OTHER', 72, 72, False, False, 129),
    (117, u'3', 'NUMBER', 76, 76, False, False, 133),
    (117, u'HD', 'OTHER', 78, 78, False, False, 135),
    (117, u'HTPC', 'OTHER', 86, 86, False, False, 149),
    (13, u'NTSC', 'OTHER', 18, 18, False, False, 18),
    (13, u'NHK', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, False, 30),
    (35, u'Sony', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, False, 16),
    (57, u'1993', 'NUMBER', 16, 16, False, False, 20),
    (57, u'Digital HDTV Grand Alliance', 'OTHER', 19, 22, False, False, 20),
    (57, u'AT & T Bell Labs', 'OTHER', 36, 40, False, False, 52),
    (57, u'General Instrument', 'OTHER', 42, 43, False, False, 64),
    (57, u'Philips', 'OTHER', 45, 45, False, False, 70),
    (57, u'Zenith', 'OTHER', 51, 51, False, False, 82),
    (   57,
        'OTHER',
        54,
        57,
        False,
        False,
        88),
    (62, u'Italian', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, False, 29),
    (62, u'RAI', 'OTHER', 23, 23, False, False, 29),
    (62, u'HD', 'OTHER', 26, 26, False, False, 29),
    (62, u'MAC', 'OTHER', 28, 28, False, False, 29),
    (62, u'1990', 'NUMBER', 36, 36, False, False, 39),
    (62, u'FIFA', 'OTHER', 37, 37, False, False, 41),
    (62, u'World Cup', 'OTHER', 38, 39, False, False, 43),
    (68, u'European', 'OTHER', 24, 24, False, False, 28),
    (68, u'HD', 'OTHER', 29, 29, False, False, 28),
    (68, u'Europe', u'LOCATION', 48, 48, False, False, 34),
    (68, u'Belgian TV', 'OTHER', 10, 11, False, False, 40),
    (101, u'PAL', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, False, 19),
    (101, u'50', 'NUMBER', 15, 15, False, False, 19),
    (101, u'Hz', 'OTHER', 16, 16, False, False, 19),
    (101, u'60', 'NUMBER', 28, 28, False, False, 37),
    (101, u'Hz', 'OTHER', 29, 29, False, False, 39),
    (118, u'two', 'NUMBER', 9, 9, False, False, 20),
    (1, u'In', 'OTHER', 30, 30, False, False, 19),
    (1, u'4k,5k', 'NUMBER', 43, 45, False, False, 32),
        'OTHER',
        1,
        7,
        False,
        False,
        16),
    (17, u'four', 'NUMBER', 2, 2, False, False, 2),
    (17, u'1979', 'NUMBER', 16, 16, False, False, 12),
        'OTHER',
        25,
        28,
        False,
        False,
        21),
    (18, u'DVB', 'OTHER', 11, 11, False, False, 3),
    (18, u'525', 'NUMBER', 23, 23, False, False, 9),
    (18, u'NTSC', 'OTHER', 26, 26, False, False, 12),
    (18, u'PAL', 'OTHER', 29, 29, False, False, 15),
    (18, u'625', 'NUMBER', 40, 40, False, False, 26),
    (18, u'PAL', 'OTHER', 43, 43, False, False, 29),
    (28, u'US', u'LOCATION', 9, 9, False, False, 19),
    (28, u'Washington', u'LOCATION', 7, 7, False, False, 21),
    (28, u'MUSE', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, False, 23),
    (31, u'NTSC', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, 4),
    (33, u'NHK', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, False, 6),
    (33, u'MUSE', 'OTHER', 10, 10, False, False, 9),
    (33, u'four times', 'NUMBER', 14, 15, False, False, 13),
    (34, u'SDTV', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, False, 7),
    (32, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 14, 14, True, False, 22),
    (32, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 5, 5, True, False, 31),
    (32, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 27, 27, True, False, 35),
    (117, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 26, 26, True, False, 83),
    (117, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 83, 83, True, False, 140),
    (13, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 6, 6, True, False, 18),
    (13, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 24, 24, True, False, 18),
    (35, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 7, 7, True, False, 12),
    (35, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 19, 19, True, False, 12),
    (62, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 2, 2, True, False, 29),
    (68, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 17, 17, True, False, 28),
    (68, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 45, 45, True, False, 28),
    (101, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 0, 0, True, False, 19),
    (101, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 19, 19, True, False, 19),
    (118, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 17, 17, True, False, 4),
    (118, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 21, 21, True, False, 4),
    (1, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 11, 11, True, False, 0),
    (15, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 23, 23, True, False, 0),
    (16, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 3, 3, True, False, 0),
    (17, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 4, 4, True, False, 0),
    (18, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 14, 14, True, False, 0),
    (28, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 28, 28, True, False, 0),
    (31, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 13, 13, True, False, 0),
question open class words: ['standardizes', 'hdtv', 'specifications']



    (53, u'16', 'NUMBER', 21, 21, False, True, 64),
    (53, u'9 aspect', 'NUMBER', 23, 24, False, True, 72),
    (53, u'1,080', 'NUMBER', 37, 39, False, True, 128),
    (39, u'1', 'NUMBER', 5, 5, False, True, 22),
    (56, u'720', 'NUMBER', 16, 16, False, True, 32),
    (56, u'1080i', 'NUMBER', 49, 49, False, True, 34),
    (56, u'1280 \xd7', 'NUMBER', 51, 52, False, True, 38),
    (56, u'720p', 'NUMBER', 12, 12, False, True, 40),
    (56, u'750', 'NUMBER', 8, 8, False, True, 48),
    (26, u'1989', 'NUMBER', 5, 5, False, True, None),
    (26, u'1991', 'NUMBER', 12, 12, False, True, None),
    (26, u'9ch', 'NUMBER', 19, 19, False, True, None),
    (26, u'25,1994', 'NUMBER', 23, 25, False, True, None),
    (49, u'6', 'NUMBER', 3, 3, False, True, None),
    (49, u'1980s', 'NUMBER', 12, 12, False, True, None),
    (49, u'two', 'NUMBER', 31, 31, False, True, None),
    (52, u'16', 'NUMBER', 4, 4, False, True, None),
    (52, u'9', 'NUMBER', 6, 6, False, True, None),
    (52, u'6', 'NUMBER', 19, 19, False, True, None),
    (106, u'2009', 'NUMBER', 36, 36, False, True, None),
    (67, u'2003', 'NUMBER', 11, 11, False, True, 51),
    (2, u'1936', 'NUMBER', 11, 11, False, True, None),
    (2, u'2', 'NUMBER', 17, 17, False, True, None),
    (2, u'1936', 'NUMBER', 19, 19, False, True, None),
    (2, u'240 line', 'NUMBER', 27, 28, False, True, None),
    (2, u'405 line', 'NUMBER', 48, 49, False, True, None),
    (7, u'4', 'NUMBER', 8, 8, False, True, None),
    (7, u'3 aspect', 'NUMBER', 10, 11, False, True, None),
    (7, u'240', 'NUMBER', 15, 15, False, True, None),
    (7, u'405', 'NUMBER', 38, 38, False, True, None),
    (7, u'5', 'NUMBER', 45, 45, False, True, None),
    (7, u'4', 'NUMBER', 47, 47, False, True, None),
    (7, u'4', 'NUMBER', 52, 52, False, True, None),
    (7, u'3', 'NUMBER', 54, 54, False, True, None),
    (10, u'1953', 'NUMBER', 16, 16, False, True, None),
    (10, u'525 lines', 'NUMBER', 31, 32, False, True, None),
    (   47,
        'OTHER',
        4,
        6,
        155),
    (   37,
        'OTHER',
        3,
        5,
        False,
        False,
        37),
    (37, u'Analog HDTV', 'OTHER', 25, 26, False, False, 46),
    (53, u'R Recommendation ITU', 'OTHER', 4, 6, False, False, 4),
    (53, u'R BT', 'OTHER', 8, 9, False, False, 12),
    (53, u'Rec', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, False, 40),
    (39, u'R BT', 'OTHER', 17, 18, False, False, 2),
    (39, u'MPEG', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, False, 26),
        'OTHER',
        1,
        7,
        False,
        36),
    (36, u'Japan', u'LOCATION', 0, 0, False, False, 29),
    (56, u'US', u'LOCATION', 67, 67, False, False, 70),
    (56, u'SMPTE', 'OTHER', 68, 68, False, False, 72),
    (26, u'BS', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, None),
    (26, u'November', 'OTHER', 22, 22, False, False, None),
    (26, u'NHK', 'OTHER', 31, 31, False, False, None),
    (49, u'IWP11', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, None),
    (52, u'IWP11', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, None),
    (52, u'BBC', 'OTHER', 24, 24, False, False, None),
    (52, u'Research', 'OTHER', 27, 27, False, False, None),
    (52, u'Development', 'OTHER', 29, 29, False, False, None),
    (52, u'Kingswood Warren', u'LOCATION', 32, 33, False, False, None),
    (106, u'US', u'LOCATION', 2, 2, False, False, None),
    (124, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 2, 3, False, False, None),
    (124, u'FCC', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, False, None),
    (124, u'HD', 'OTHER', 26, 26, False, False, None),
    (124, u'FireWire', 'OTHER', 41, 41, False, False, None),
    (124, u'IEEE', 'OTHER', 43, 43, False, False, None),
    (117, u'VHS', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, False, 90),
    (117, u'W', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, 92),
    (117, u'DirecTV', 'OTHER', 35, 35, False, False, 92),
    (117, u'VHS', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, False, 94),
    (117, u'Data', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, False, 96),
    (117, u'VHS', 'OTHER', 11, 11, False, False, 98),
    (117, u'Digital', 'OTHER', 41, 41, False, False, 98),
    (117, u'Digital', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, False, 100),
    (117, u'Sky HD', 'OTHER', 45, 46, False, False, 101),
    (117, u'VHS', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, False, 102),
    (117, u'D', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, False, 104),
    (117, u'Dish Network', 'OTHER', 54, 55, False, False, 110),
    (117, u'VIP', 'OTHER', 58, 58, False, False, 115),
    (117, u'VIP', 'OTHER', 61, 61, False, False, 118),
    (117, u'Digital', 'OTHER', 66, 66, False, False, 123),
    (117, u'TiVo', 'OTHER', 72, 72, False, False, 129),
    (117, u'Series', 'OTHER', 75, 75, False, False, 132),
    (117, u'HD', 'OTHER', 78, 78, False, False, 135),
    (117, u'HTPC', 'OTHER', 86, 86, False, False, 149),
    (13, u'NTSC', 'OTHER', 18, 18, False, False, 18),
    (13, u'NHK', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, False, 30),
    (68, u'HD', 'OTHER', 38, 38, False, False, 34),
    (68, u'Europe', u'LOCATION', 48, 48, False, False, 38),
    (68, u'Alfacam', u'PERSON', 14, 14, False, False, 64),
    (67, u'Europe', u'LOCATION', 42, 42, False, False, 11),
    (67, u'September', 'OTHER', 10, 10, False, False, 53),
    (2, u'British', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, None),
    (2, u'TV', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, False, None),
    (2, u'August', 'OTHER', 10, 10, False, False, None),
    (2, u'November', 'OTHER', 18, 18, False, False, None),
    (2, u'Baird', 'OTHER', 26, 26, False, False, None),
    (2, u'Marconi', 'OTHER', 45, 45, False, False, None),
    (2, u'EMI', 'OTHER', 47, 47, False, False, None),
    (10, u'US', u'LOCATION', 11, 11, False, False, None),
    (10, u'NTSC', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, False, None),
    (47, u'R', 'OTHER', 15, 15, True, False, 107),
    (47, u'ITU', 'OTHER', 13, 13, True, False, 115),
    (37, u'ITU', 'OTHER', 12, 12, True, False, 25),
    (37, u'R', 'OTHER', 14, 14, True, False, 25),
    (53, u'ITU', 'OTHER', 2, 2, True, False, 12),
    (39, u'ITU', 'OTHER', 15, 15, True, False, 2),
    (89, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 6, 6, True, False, 5),
    (15, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 23, 23, True, False, 4),
    (36, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 11, 11, True, False, 7),
    (56, u'ITU', 'OTHER', 27, 27, True, False, 10),
    (56, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 37, 37, True, False, 10),
    (117, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 26, 26, True, False, 83),
    (117, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 83, 83, True, False, 140),
    (13, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 6, 6, True, False, 18),
    (13, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 24, 24, True, False, 18),
    (68, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 45, 45, True, False, 29),
question open class words: ['when', 'did', 'itu', 'r', 'start', 'trying', 'work', 'towards', 'setting', 'single', 'international', 'hdtv', 'standard']



all results:
    (68, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 45, 45, False, True, 158),
    (101, u'PAL', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, True, 19),
    (101, u'SECAM', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, True, 19),
    (101, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, True, 19),
    (101, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, True, 23),
    (101, u'Hz', 'OTHER', 29, 29, False, True, 35),
    (66, u'January', 'OTHER', 6, 6, False, True, 15),
    (66, u'New Year', 'OTHER', 23, 24, False, True, 19),
    (66, u'Concert', 'OTHER', 27, 27, False, True, 27),
    (71, u'MPEG', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, True, 5),
    (71, u'AVC', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, True, 9),
    (71, u'DVB', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, True, 13),
    (71, u'S2', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, True, 15),
    (1, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 11, 11, False, True, None),
    (1, u'HD', 'OTHER', 25, 25, False, True, None),
    (1, u'In', 'OTHER', 30, 30, False, True, None),
    (16, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, True, None),
    (118, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, True, 30),
    (57, u'Digital HDTV Grand Alliance', 'OTHER', 19, 22, False, True, 17),
    (57, u'AT & T Bell Labs', 'OTHER', 36, 40, False, True, 34),
    (57, u'General Instrument', 'OTHER', 42, 43, False, True, 40),
    (57, u'Philips', 'OTHER', 45, 45, False, True, 43),
    (57, u'Zenith', 'OTHER', 51, 51, False, True, 49),
    (   57,
        'OTHER',
        54,
        57,
        False,
        True,
        52),
    (124, u'FCC', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, True, None),
    (124, u'HD', 'OTHER', 26, 26, False, True, None),
    (124, u'FireWire', 'OTHER', 41, 41, False, True, None),
    (124, u'IEEE', 'OTHER', 43, 43, False, True, None),
    (125, u'TV', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, True, None),
    (66, u'1,2004', 'NUMBER', 7, 9, False, False, 9),
    (71, u'Europe', u'LOCATION', 24, 24, False, False, 24),
    (1, u'4k,5k', 'NUMBER', 43, 45, False, False, None),
    (1, u'8K systems', 'NUMBER', 48, 49, False, False, None),
    (57, u'1993', 'NUMBER', 16, 16, False, False, 14),
    (57, u'Sarnoff', u'PERSON', 47, 47, False, False, 45),
question open class words: ['euro1080', 'was', 'division', 'former', 'company']



all results:
[   (60, u'John Glenn', u'PERSON', 27, 28, False, True, 16),
    (68, u'Alfacam', u'PERSON', 14, 14, False, True, None),
    (91, u'8', 'NUMBER', 15, 15, False, False, 18),
    (91, u'Internet', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, False, 28),
    (60, u'Space Shuttle Discovery', 'OTHER', 38, 40, False, False, 4),
    (60, u'October', 'OTHER', 16, 16, False, False, 40),
    (60, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, False, 54),
    (60, u'ATSC', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, False, 58),
    (   60,
        u'American Advanced Television Systems Committee',
        'OTHER',
        1,
        5,
        False,
        False,
        62),
    (10, u'1953', 'NUMBER', 16, 16, False, False, 3),
    (10, u'525 lines', 'NUMBER', 31, 32, False, False, 18),
    (11, u'SECAM', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, False, 1),
    (11, u'PAL', 'OTHER', 11, 11, False, False, 3),
    (11, u'625 line', 'NUMBER', 21, 22, False, False, 7),
    (14, u'1972', 'NUMBER', 9, 9, False, False, 4),
    (14, u'5', 'NUMBER', 16, 16, False, False, 11),
    (14, u'60', 'NUMBER', 22, 22, False, False, 17),
    (14, u'Hz', 'OTHER', 23, 23, False, False, 18),
    (89, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 6, 6, False, False, 1),
    (105, u'720p', 'NUMBER', 14, 14, False, False, 5),
    (105, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, False, 6),
    (105, u'1080i format', 'NUMBER', 16, 17, False, False, 7),
    (105, u'720p', 'NUMBER', 24, 24, False, False, 15),
    (105, u'Internet', 'OTHER', 29, 29, False, False, 20),
    (105, u'720p', 'NUMBER', 48, 48, False, False, 39),
    (105, u'1080i', 'NUMBER', 60, 60, False, False, 51),
    (105, u'1080p.1080p', 'NUMBER', 62, 64, False, False, 53),
    (105, u'24,1080i /', 'NUMBER', 66, 69, False, False, 57),
    (105, u'25', 'NUMBER', 74, 74, False, False, 65),
    (105, u'30', 'NUMBER', 79, 79, False, False, 70),
    (105, u'Blu', 'OTHER', 85, 85, False, False, 76),
    (105, u'Disc', 'OTHER', 88, 88, False, False, 79),
    (45, u'H', 'OTHER', 29, 29, False, False, 6),
    (45, u'264', 'NUMBER', 31, 31, False, False, 8),
    (45, u'DVB', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, False, 9),
    (45, u'MPEG', 'OTHER', 33, 33, False, False, 10),
    (45, u'4', 'NUMBER', 35, 35, False, False, 12),
    (45, u'AVC', 'OTHER', 36, 36, False, False, 13),
    (45, u'MPEG', 'OTHER', 8, 8, False, False, 15),
    (45, u'DVB', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, False, 20),
    (45, u'ATSC', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, False, 22),
    (59, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 7, 8, False, False, None),
    (59, u'23,1996', 'NUMBER', 12, 14, False, False, None),
    (59, u'Raleigh', u'LOCATION', 17, 17, False, False, None),
    (59, u'North Carolina', u'LOCATION', 19, 20, False, False, None),
    (59, u'WRAL', 'OTHER', 23, 23, False, False, None),
    (59, u'HD', 'OTHER', 25, 25, False, False, None),
    (59, u'WRAL', 'OTHER', 33, 33, False, False, None),
    (59, u'TV', 'OTHER', 35, 35, False, False, None),
    (59, u'Raleigh', u'LOCATION', 38, 38, False, False, None),
    (59, u'HD Model Station', 'OTHER', 48, 50, False, False, None),
    (59, u'Washington', u'LOCATION', 52, 52, False, False, None),
    (59, u'C', 'OTHER', 56, 56, False, False, None),
    (59, u'31,1996', 'NUMBER', 62, 64, False, False, None),
    (59, u'WHD', 'OTHER', 68, 68, False, False, None),
    (59, u'TV', 'OTHER', 70, 70, False, False, None),
    (59, u'NBC', 'OTHER', 78, 78, False, False, None),
    (59, u'WRC', 'OTHER', 83, 83, False, False, None),
    (59, u'TV', 'OTHER', 85, 85, False, False, None),
    (68, u'Belgian TV', 'OTHER', 10, 11, False, False, None),
    (68, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, None),
    (68, u'European', 'OTHER', 24, 24, False, False, None),
    (68, u'HD', 'OTHER', 29, 29, False, False, None),
    (68, u'HD TVs', 'OTHER', 33, 34, False, False, None),
    (68, u'HD', 'OTHER', 38, 38, False, False, None),
    (68, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 45, 45, False, False, None),
    (68, u'Europe', u'LOCATION', 48, 48, False, False, None),
    (72, u'European HD', 'OTHER', 9, 10, False, False, None),
    (72, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 20, 20, False, False, None),
    (72, u'SES', 'OTHER', 24, 24, False, False, None),
    (72, u'Satellite Monitor', 'OTHER', 28, 29, False, False, None),
    (72, u'200', 'NUMBER', 37, 37, False, False, None),
    (72, u'HD', 'OTHER', 42, 42, False, False, None),
    (72, u'Astra', 'OTHER', 44, 44, False, False, None),
    (72, u'185 million', 'NUMBER', 47, 49, False, False, None),
    (72, u'HD', 'OTHER', 49, 49, False, False, None),
    (72, u'TVs', 'OTHER', 51, 51, False, False, None),
    (72, u'Europe', u'LOCATION', 54, 54, False, False, None),
    (72, u'2010', 'NUMBER', 59, 59, False, False, None),
    (72, u'20 million households', 'NUMBER', 63, 66, False, False, None),
    (72, u'27 %', 'NUMBER', 67, 68, False, False, None),
    (72, u'European', 'OTHER', 71, 71, False, False, None),
    (72, u'TV', 'OTHER', 74, 74, False, False, None),
    (72, u'HD', 'OTHER', 78, 78, False, False, None),
    (72, u'16 million', 'NUMBER', 82, 84, False, False, None),
    (72, u'Astra', 'OTHER', 85, 85, False, False, None),
    (43, u'SDTV', 'OTHER', 8, 8, False, False, None),
    (43, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 10, 10, False, False, None),
    (62, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 2, 2, False, False, None),
    (62, u'Italian', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, False, None),
    (62, u'RAI', 'OTHER', 23, 23, False, False, None),
    (62, u'HD', 'OTHER', 26, 26, False, False, None),
    (62, u'MAC', 'OTHER', 28, 28, False, False, None),
    (62, u'1990', 'NUMBER', 36, 36, False, False, None),
    (62, u'FIFA', 'OTHER', 37, 37, False, False, None),
    (62, u'World Cup', 'OTHER', 38, 39, False, False, None),
    (70, u'European HDTV', 'OTHER', 2, 3, False, False, None),
    (70, u'1080i format', 'NUMBER', 7, 8, False, False, None),
    (70, u'MPEG', 'OTHER', 10, 10, False, False, None),
    (70, u'2 compression', 'NUMBER', 12, 13, False, False, None),
    (70, u'DVB', 'OTHER', 16, 16, False, False, None),
    (70, u'S', 'OTHER', 18, 18, False, False, None),
    (70, u'SES', 'OTHER', 21, 21, False, False, None),
    (70, u'Astra', 'OTHER', 24, 24, False, False, None),
    (70, u'1H satellite', 'NUMBER', 25, 26, False, False, None),
    (94, u'16', 'NUMBER', 9, 9, False, False, 7),
    (94, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, False, 11),
    (26, u'1991', 'NUMBER', 12, 12, False, False, None),
    (26, u'BS', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, False, None),
    (26, u'9ch', 'NUMBER', 19, 19, False, False, None),
    (26, u'25,1994', 'NUMBER', 23, 25, False, False, None),
    (26, u'NHK', 'OTHER', 31, 31, False, False, None),
    (100, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 12, 12, False, False, None),
    (90, u'RGB', 'OTHER', 35, 35, True, False, 156),
    (91, u'RGB', 'OTHER', 18, 18, True, False, 24),
    (14, u'Color', 'OTHER', 5, 5, True, False, 0)]
question: Before being converted to RGB, colors are ususally broadcasted using what color space?
expected: YUV
expected sentence: Colors are typically broadcast using a (10-bits per channel) YUV color space but, depending on the underlying image generating technologies of the receiver, are then subsequently converted to a RGB color space using standardized algorithms.
actual: (60, u'John Glenn', u'PERSON', 27, 28, False, True, 16)
question open class words: ['being', 'converted', 'rgb', 'colors', 'are', 'ususally', 'broadcasted', 'using', 'color', 'space']



all results:
    (113, u'BD', 'OTHER', 37, 37, False, True, 31),
    (117, u'D', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, True, None),
    (117, u'VHS', 'OTHER', 7, 7, False, True, None),
    (117, u'Digital', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, True, None),
    (117, u'VHS', 'OTHER', 11, 11, False, True, None),
    (117, u'Data', 'OTHER', 13, 13, False, True, None),
    (117, u'VHS', 'OTHER', 15, 15, False, True, None),
    (117, u'W', 'OTHER', 17, 17, False, True, None),
    (117, u'VHS', 'OTHER', 19, 19, False, True, None),
    (117, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 26, 26, False, True, None),
    (117, u'DirecTV', 'OTHER', 35, 35, False, True, None),
    (117, u'Digital', 'OTHER', 41, 41, False, True, None),
    (117, u'Sky HD', 'OTHER', 45, 46, False, True, None),
    (117, u'Dish Network', 'OTHER', 54, 55, False, True, None),
    (117, u'VIP', 'OTHER', 58, 58, False, True, None),
    (117, u'VIP', 'OTHER', 61, 61, False, True, None),
    (117, u'Digital', 'OTHER', 66, 66, False, True, None),
    (117, u'TiVo', 'OTHER', 72, 72, False, True, None),
    (117, u'Series', 'OTHER', 75, 75, False, True, None),
    (117, u'HD', 'OTHER', 78, 78, False, True, None),
    (117, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 83, 83, False, True, None),
    (117, u'HTPC', 'OTHER', 86, 86, False, True, None),
    (88, u'24', 'NUMBER', 5, 5, False, False, None),
    (117, u'3', 'NUMBER', 76, 76, False, False, None),
    (79, u'1920 \xd7', 'NUMBER', 3, 4, False, False, None),
    (79, u'1080p25 identifies', 'NUMBER', 5, 6, False, False, None),
    (79, u'25 frames', 'NUMBER', 11, 12, False, False, None),
    (79, u'1,920 pixels', 'NUMBER', 19, 22, False, False, None),
    (79, u'1,080 pixels', 'NUMBER', 25, 28, False, False, None),
question open class words: ['roku', 'appletv', 'are', 'examples']



all results:
[   (121, u'HD', 'OTHER', 3, 3, False, True, 10),
    (121, u'MPEG', 'OTHER', 14, 14, False, True, 12),
    (121, u'Blu', 'OTHER', 26, 26, False, True, 36),
    (121, u'DVD', 'OTHER', 39, 39, False, True, 62),
    (121, u'PVR', 'OTHER', 47, 47, False, True, 78),
    (121, u'USB', 'OTHER', 50, 50, False, True, 84),
    (73, u'European', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, True, 6),
    (73, u'December', 'OTHER', 1, 1, False, True, 14),
    (73, u'Digital TV Group', 'OTHER', 29, 31, False, True, 14),
    (73, u'DTG', 'OTHER', 33, 33, False, True, 18),
    (73, u'D', 'OTHER', 35, 35, False, True, 20),
    (111, u'HD', 'OTHER', 9, 9, False, True, 1),
    (111, u'TV', 'OTHER', 5, 5, False, True, 5),
    (114, u'HD', 'OTHER', 52, 52, False, True, 1),
    (114, u'Zune', 'OTHER', 43, 43, False, True, 10),
    (114, u'Windows Media Center HTPC', 'OTHER', 34, 37, False, True, 16),
    (114, u'Netflix', 'OTHER', 32, 32, False, True, 21),
    (114, u'Xbox', 'OTHER', 26, 26, False, True, 27),
    (114, u'Microsoft', 'OTHER', 23, 23, False, True, 30),
    (114, u'Sony', 'OTHER', 0, 0, False, True, 53),
    (54, u'MBAFF', 'OTHER', 6, 6, False, True, 8),
    (54, u'British Freeview HD', 'OTHER', 1, 3, False, True, 11),
    (127, u'5C', 'NUMBER', 8, 8, False, False, 21),
    (121, u'2 format', 'NUMBER', 16, 17, False, False, 16),
    (114, u'360', 'NUMBER', 27, 27, False, False, 26),
    (114, u'3', 'NUMBER', 4, 4, False, False, 49)]
question: Content is now protected by what encryption?
expected: 5C
expected sentence: This content is protected by encryption known as 5C.
question open class words: ['content', 'is', 'now', 'protected', 'encryption']


