all results:
[   (47, u'Stratocumulus', 'OTHER', 22, 22),
    (47, u'Stratus', 'OTHER', 20, 20),
    (47, u'Cumulonimbus', 'OTHER', 9, 9),
    (61, u'X', 'OTHER', 35, 35),
    (50, u'IR4', 'OTHER', 9, 9),
    (49, u'One disadvantage', 'NUMBER', 0, 1),
    (50, u'11.5 \xb5m', 'NUMBER', 16, 19),
    (50, u'10.3', 'NUMBER', 12, 14),
    (50, u'1.58', 'NUMBER', 28, 30),
    (50, u'1.64', 'NUMBER', 32, 34),
    (92, u'Earth', u'LOCATION', 44, 44),
    (47, u'Cirrus', 'OTHER', 7, 7)]
question: Along with Cirrus, what types of clouds are cold and high?
expected: Cumulonimbus
expected sentence: High, cold ice clouds such as Cirrus or Cumulonimbus show up bright white, lower warmer clouds such as Stratus or Stratocumulus show up as grey with intermediate clouds shaded accordingly.
actual: (47, u'Stratocumulus', 'OTHER', 22, 22)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (2, u'Hag\xe5t\xf1a', u'LOCATION', 4, 4),
    (2, u'Dededo', u'LOCATION', 12, 12),
    (39, u'Mexico City', u'LOCATION', 29, 30),
    (39, u'Philippines', u'LOCATION', 14, 14),
    (39, u'Spanish East Indies', u'LOCATION', 8, 10),
    (39, u'New Spain', u'LOCATION', 25, 26),
    (0, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 31, 32),
    (43, u'Northern Marianas', u'LOCATION', 17, 18),
    (58, u'Northern Mariana Islands', u'LOCATION', 40, 42),
    (58, u'Philippines', u'LOCATION', 36, 36),
    (58, u'Germany', u'LOCATION', 45, 45),
    (58, u'Japan', u'LOCATION', 50, 50),
    (65, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 20, 21),
    (113, u'Okinawa', u'LOCATION', 34, 34),
    (113, u'Japan', u'LOCATION', 36, 36),
    (144, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 13, 14),
    (154, u'Chamorro', u'LOCATION', 14, 14),
    (187, u'Tamuning', u'LOCATION', 19, 19),
    (1, u'Pacific Ocean', u'LOCATION', 4, 5),
    (191, u'Guam Regional Medical City', 'OTHER', 5, 8)]
actual: (2, u'Hag\xe5t\xf1a', u'LOCATION', 4, 4)
predicted question type: LOCATION



all results:
[   (30, u'Islands', 'OTHER', 19, 19),
    (30, u'Latinas', 'OTHER', 17, 17),
    (30, u'Magellan', 'OTHER', 10, 10),
    (30, u'Proas', 'OTHER', 5, 5),
    (29, u'Magellan', 'OTHER', 5, 5),
    (29, u'When', 'OTHER', 4, 4),
    (91, u'Cat\xe1logo', 'OTHER', 21, 21),
    (91, u'Roman Catholic Christianity', 'OTHER', 11, 13),
    (91, u'Spanish', 'OTHER', 4, 4),
    (91, u'Chamorros', 'OTHER', 1, 1),
    (100, u'Spanish', 'OTHER', 3, 3),
    (31, u'Sails', 'OTHER', 15, 15),
    (31, u'Island', 'OTHER', 13, 13),
    (31, u'Magellan', 'OTHER', 5, 5),
    (30, u'Lateen', u'LOCATION', 22, 22),
    (30, u'Guam Islas de las Velas', u'LOCATION', 12, 16),
    (29, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 8, 8),
    (29, u'42', 'NUMBER', 3, 3),
    (29, u'41 –', 'NUMBER', 1, 2),
    (91, u'Philippines', u'LOCATION', 32, 32)]
actual: (30, u'Islands', 'OTHER', 19, 19)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (44, u'86', 'NUMBER', 48, 48),
    (44, u'1688', 'NUMBER', 27, 27),
    (44, u'1671', 'NUMBER', 16, 16),
    (44, u'1695', 'NUMBER', 10, 10),
    (44, u'5,000 .:', 'NUMBER', 44, 47),
    (44, u'50,000', 'NUMBER', 34, 36),
    (44, u'1693', 'NUMBER', 18, 18),
    (44, u'23,1670', 'NUMBER', 5, 7),
    (44, u'10,000', 'NUMBER', 38, 40),
    (162, u'2,500 acres', 'NUMBER', 26, 29),
    (162, u'5', 'NUMBER', 18, 18),
    (162, u'10 km2', 'NUMBER', 31, 32),
    (162, u'25', 'NUMBER', 36, 36),
    (162, u'0.5 miles', 'NUMBER', 39, 42),
    (162, u'800 m', 'NUMBER', 44, 45),
    (133, u'two', 'NUMBER', 31, 31),
    (57, u'1898', 'NUMBER', 10, 10),
    (44, u'Chamorro', u'PERSON', 31, 31),
    (44, u'Precipitated', 'OTHER', 49, 49),
    (44, u'Father', 'OTHER', 60, 60)]
question: When did the Smallpox epidemic take place?
expected: 1688
expected sentence: Intermittent warfare lasting from July 23, 1670 until July 1695, plus the typhoons of 1671 and 1693, and in particular the smallpox epidemic of 1688, reduced the Chamorro population from 50,000 to 10,000 to less than 5,000.:86 Precipitated by the death of Quipuha, and the murder of Father San Vitores and Pedro Calungsod by local rebel chief Matapang, tensions led to a number of conflicts.
actual: (44, u'1695', 'NUMBER', 10, 10)
predicted question type: NUMBER



all results:
[   (64, u'Northern Mariana Chamorros', 'OTHER', 25, 27),
    (64, u'30 years', 'NUMBER', 21, 22),
    (64, u'Chamorros', 'OTHER', 3, 3),
    (113, u'Okinawa', u'LOCATION', 34, 34),
    (113, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 32, 32),
    (113, u'9,000', 'NUMBER', 24, 26),
    (113, u'Marines', 'OTHER', 21, 21),
    (113, u'8,600', 'NUMBER', 18, 20),
    (113, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 15, 15),
    (113, u'S', 'OTHER', 3, 3),
    (113, u'U', 'OTHER', 1, 1),
    (58, u'Germany', u'LOCATION', 45, 45),
    (58, u'Northern Mariana Islands', u'LOCATION', 40, 42),
    (58, u'Philippines', u'LOCATION', 36, 36),
    (58, u'American', 'OTHER', 29, 29),
    (58, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 21, 21),
    (58, u'A', 'OTHER', 19, 19),
    (58, u'108', 'NUMBER', 17, 17),
    (58, u'Executive Order', 'OTHER', 15, 16),
    (58, u'1898', 'NUMBER', 13, 13)]
question: Who were loyal to Japan?
expected: Northern Mariana Chamorros
expected sentence: Guam's Chamorros believed their northern brethren should have been compassionate towards them, whereas having been occupied for over 30 years, the Northern Mariana Chamorros were loyal to Japan.
actual: (64, u'Chamorros', 'OTHER', 3, 3)
predicted question type: PERSON



all results:
[   (68, u'32nd', 'NUMBER', 43, 43),
    (68, u'549 km2', 'NUMBER', 37, 38),
    (68, u'212', 'NUMBER', 33, 33),
    (68, u'145.0', 'NUMBER', 22, 24),
    (68, u'144.6', 'NUMBER', 16, 18),
    (68, u'13.7', 'NUMBER', 9, 11),
    (68, u'13.2', 'NUMBER', 3, 5),
    (74, u'4', 'NUMBER', 27, 27),
    (74, u'3 ⁄', 'NUMBER', 25, 26),
    (74, u'19 km', 'NUMBER', 20, 21),
    (74, u'6', 'NUMBER', 18, 18),
    (74, u'12 miles', 'NUMBER', 15, 16),
    (74, u'4', 'NUMBER', 13, 13),
    (74, u'50 km', 'NUMBER', 8, 9),
    (74, u'30 miles', 'NUMBER', 5, 6),
    (185, u'9,700 km', 'NUMBER', 20, 23),
    (185, u'6,000 miles', 'NUMBER', 15, 18),
    (162, u'800 m', 'NUMBER', 44, 45),
    (162, u'0.5 miles', 'NUMBER', 39, 42),
    (162, u'25', 'NUMBER', 36, 36)]
question: How many square miles is Guam?
expected: 212
expected sentence: Guam lies between 13.2°N and 13.7°N and between 144.6°E and 145.0°E, and has an area of 212 square miles (549 km2), making it the 32nd largest island of the United States.
actual: (68, u'13.2', 'NUMBER', 3, 5)
predicted question type: NUMBER



all results:
[   (141, u'Antonio B', 'OTHER', 5, 6),
    (141, u'Won Pat International Airport', 'OTHER', 8, 11),
    (141, u'United Airlines', 'OTHER', 18, 19),
    (67, u'S', 'OTHER', 15, 15),
    (67, u'U', 'OTHER', 13, 13),
    (67, u'S', 'OTHER', 9, 9),
    (67, u'U', 'OTHER', 7, 7),
    (67, u'Since Guam', 'OTHER', 2, 3),
    (124, u'Compacts', 'OTHER', 1, 1),
    (124, u'Guam', 'OTHER', 27, 27),
    (141, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 0, 0),
    (67, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 20, 20),
    (67, u'242', 'NUMBER', 1, 1),
    (3, u'Guam', u'LOCATION', 9, 9),
    (3, u'785 people', 'NUMBER', 5, 6),
    (3, u'2015,161', 'NUMBER', 1, 3),
    (124, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 15, 16)]
actual: (141, u'Antonio B', 'OTHER', 5, 6)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
    (180, u'Schools', 'OTHER', 20, 20),
    (180, u'Pacific Islands University', 'OTHER', 0, 2),
    (31, u'Sails', 'OTHER', 15, 15),
    (31, u'Island', 'OTHER', 13, 13),
    (31, u'Magellan', 'OTHER', 5, 5),
    (178, u'Western Association of Schools', 'OTHER', 17, 20),
    (178, u'University of Guam', 'OTHER', 1, 3),
    (178, u'Colleges', 'OTHER', 22, 22),
    (178, u'UOG', 'OTHER', 5, 5),
    (178, u'Guam Community College', 'OTHER', 8, 10),
    (30, u'Islands', 'OTHER', 19, 19),
    (30, u'Magellan', 'OTHER', 10, 10),
    (30, u'Latinas', 'OTHER', 17, 17),
    (30, u'Proas', 'OTHER', 5, 5),
    (91, u'Cat\xe1logo', 'OTHER', 21, 21),
    (91, u'Roman Catholic Christianity', 'OTHER', 11, 13),
    (91, u'Spanish', 'OTHER', 4, 4),
    (91, u'Chamorros', 'OTHER', 1, 1),
    (106, u'Electoral College', 'OTHER', 33, 34)]
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (187, u'Government', 'OTHER', 1, 1),
    (187, u'Guam Memorial Hospital', 'OTHER', 14, 16),
    (30, u'Islands', 'OTHER', 19, 19),
    (30, u'Magellan', 'OTHER', 10, 10),
    (30, u'Latinas', 'OTHER', 17, 17),
    (30, u'Proas', 'OTHER', 5, 5),
    (31, u'Sails', 'OTHER', 15, 15),
    (31, u'Island', 'OTHER', 13, 13),
    (31, u'Magellan', 'OTHER', 5, 5),
    (91, u'Cat\xe1logo', 'OTHER', 21, 21),
    (91, u'Roman Catholic Christianity', 'OTHER', 11, 13),
    (91, u'Spanish', 'OTHER', 4, 4),
    (91, u'Chamorros', 'OTHER', 1, 1),
    (0, u'Territory', 'OTHER', 19, 19),
    (0, u'IPA', 'OTHER', 15, 15),
    (0, u'Gu\xe5h\xe5n', 'OTHER', 12, 12),
    (0, u'Chamorro', 'OTHER', 10, 10),
    (43, u'Spanish', 'OTHER', 32, 32),
    (43, u'Mexican', 'OTHER', 25, 25),
    (43, u'Spanish', 'OTHER', 23, 23)]
actual: (187, u'Government', 'OTHER', 1, 1)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (22, u'Transformer', 'OTHER', 14, 14),
    (22, u'Тransformator', 'OTHER', 7, 7),
    (   22,
        u'Трансформатор',
        'OTHER',
        11,
        11),
    (22, u'Russian', 'OTHER', 9, 9),
    (24, u'Japanese', 'OTHER', 4, 4),
    (24, u'NHK', 'OTHER', 7, 7),
    (41, u'DVB', 'OTHER', 1, 1),
    (41, u'ETSI', 'OTHER', 12, 12),
    (101, u'Hz', 'OTHER', 29, 29),
    (101, u'NTSC', 'OTHER', 22, 22),
    (101, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 19, 19),
    (101, u'Hz', 'OTHER', 16, 16),
    (101, u'SECAM', 'OTHER', 5, 5),
    (101, u'PAL', 'OTHER', 3, 3),
    (101, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 0, 0),
    (18, u'European', 'OTHER', 39, 39),
    (18, u'NTSC', 'OTHER', 26, 26),
    (18, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 14, 14),
    (18, u'PAL', 'OTHER', 43, 43),
    (18, u'SECAM', 'OTHER', 45, 45)]
question: Which country developed the 441-line system?
expected: France
expected sentence: In 1938 France followed with their own 441-line system, variants of which were also used by a number of other countries.
actual: (22, u'Transformer', 'OTHER', 14, 14)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (12, u'Olympics', 'OTHER', 38, 38),
    (12, u'Nippon Hōsō Kyōkai', 'OTHER', 1, 3),
    (36, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 11, 11),
    (33, u'MUSE', 'OTHER', 10, 10),
    (33, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 1, 1),
    (13, u'NTSC', 'OTHER', 18, 18),
    (13, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 6, 6),
    (13, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 24, 24),
    (14, u'Color', 'OTHER', 5, 5),
    (14, u'Hz', 'OTHER', 23, 23),
    (24, u'Japanese', 'OTHER', 4, 4),
    (26, u'BS', 'OTHER', 17, 17),
    (26, u'November', 'OTHER', 22, 22),
    (12, u'1964', 'NUMBER', 33, 33),
    (12, u'five', 'NUMBER', 28, 28),
    (12, u'Tokyo', u'LOCATION', 37, 37),
    (36, u'seven broadcasters', 'NUMBER', 14, 15),
    (33, u'four times', 'NUMBER', 14, 15),
    (14, u'1972', 'NUMBER', 9, 9)]
actual: (12, u'Olympics', 'OTHER', 38, 38)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (17, u'1979', 'NUMBER', 16, 16),
    (17, u'four', 'NUMBER', 2, 2),
    (57, u'1993', 'NUMBER', 16, 16),
    (107, u'1940s', 'NUMBER', 15, 15),
    (107, u'1080i ).', 'NUMBER', 54, 55),
    (107, u'720p resolution', 'NUMBER', 37, 38),
    (49, u'two', 'NUMBER', 31, 31),
    (49, u'1980s', 'NUMBER', 12, 12),
    (49, u'6', 'NUMBER', 3, 3),
    (56, u'720', 'NUMBER', 16, 16),
    (56, u'720p systems', 'NUMBER', 53, 54),
    (56, u'720p', 'NUMBER', 12, 12),
    (56, u'1280 \xd7', 'NUMBER', 51, 52),
    (56, u'750', 'NUMBER', 8, 8),
    (56, u'1080i', 'NUMBER', 49, 49),
    (56, u'1920', 'NUMBER', 47, 47),
    (26, u'1991', 'NUMBER', 12, 12),
    (26, u'1989', 'NUMBER', 5, 5),
    (26, u'9ch', 'NUMBER', 19, 19),
    (26, u'25,1994', 'NUMBER', 23, 25)]
question: How many major HDTV systems were tested by SMPTE in the late 70's?
expected: four
actual: (17, u'1979', 'NUMBER', 16, 16)
predicted question type: NUMBER



all results:
[   (57, u'Thomson', u'PERSON', 49, 49),
    (57, u'Sarnoff', u'PERSON', 47, 47),
    (107, u'Fox', u'PERSON', 30, 30),
    (25, u'Nyquist', u'PERSON', 15, 15),
    (15, u'Charles Ginsburg', u'PERSON', 13, 14),
    (60, u'John Glenn', u'PERSON', 27, 28),
    (17, u'1979', 'NUMBER', 16, 16),
    (17, u'SMPTE', 'OTHER', 8, 8),
    (17, u'SMPTE', 'OTHER', 18, 18),
    (17, u'A Study', 'OTHER', 22, 23),
    (57, u'Massachusetts Institute of Technology', 'OTHER', 54, 57),
    (57, u'Digital HDTV Grand Alliance', 'OTHER', 19, 22),
    (57, u'1993', 'NUMBER', 16, 16),
    (57, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 6, 7),
    (57, u'Zenith', 'OTHER', 51, 51),
    (57, u'Philips', 'OTHER', 45, 45),
    (57, u'General Instrument', 'OTHER', 42, 43),
    (57, u'AT & T Bell Labs', 'OTHER', 36, 40),
    (107, u'CW', 'OTHER', 52, 52)]
actual: (57, u'Thomson', u'PERSON', 49, 49)
predicted question type: PERSON



all results:
[   (19, u'819 lines', 'NUMBER', 9, 10),
    (19, u'1949', 'NUMBER', 1, 1),
    (19, u'737', 'NUMBER', 14, 14),
    (6, u'819 lines', 'NUMBER', 11, 12),
    (6, u'1949', 'NUMBER', 1, 1),
    (67, u'2003', 'NUMBER', 11, 11),
    (4, u'1938', 'NUMBER', 1, 1),
    (4, u'441', 'NUMBER', 7, 7),
    (66, u'1,2004', 'NUMBER', 7, 9),
    (7, u'4', 'NUMBER', 47, 47),
    (7, u'405', 'NUMBER', 38, 38),
    (7, u'4', 'NUMBER', 8, 8),
    (7, u'5', 'NUMBER', 45, 45),
    (7, u'4', 'NUMBER', 52, 52),
    (7, u'3 aspect', 'NUMBER', 10, 11),
    (7, u'3', 'NUMBER', 54, 54),
    (7, u'240', 'NUMBER', 15, 15),
    (18, u'2000s', 'NUMBER', 20, 20),
    (18, u'625', 'NUMBER', 40, 40),
    (18, u'525', 'NUMBER', 23, 23)]
question: In what year did France start transmissions using and 819 line system?
expected: 1949
expected sentence: In 1949, France started its transmissions with an 819 lines system (with 737 active lines).
actual: (19, u'819 lines', 'NUMBER', 9, 10)
predicted question type: NUMBER



all results:
[   (24, u'3 display', 'NUMBER', 19, 20),
    (24, u'1979', 'NUMBER', 1, 1),
    (51, u'1.67', 'NUMBER', 46, 48),
    (51, u'1.78', 'NUMBER', 30, 32),
    (51, u'1.85', 'NUMBER', 53, 55),
    (51, u'9', 'NUMBER', 28, 28),
    (51, u'16', 'NUMBER', 26, 26),
    (14, u'1972', 'NUMBER', 9, 9),
    (14, u'1125 lines', 'NUMBER', 12, 13),
    (14, u'60', 'NUMBER', 22, 22),
    (7, u'4', 'NUMBER', 8, 8),
    (7, u'4', 'NUMBER', 52, 52),
    (7, u'4', 'NUMBER', 47, 47),
    (7, u'240', 'NUMBER', 15, 15),
    (7, u'405', 'NUMBER', 38, 38),
    (27, u'1981', 'NUMBER', 1, 1),
    (22, u'1958', 'NUMBER', 1, 1),
    (22, u'1,125 lines', 'NUMBER', 33, 36),
    (72, u'60 million', 'NUMBER', 56, 58),
    (72, u'2010', 'NUMBER', 59, 59)]
question: In what year did NHK first develop consumer HD television with a 5:3 aspect ratio?
expected: 1979
expected sentence: In 1979, the Japanese state broadcaster NHK first developed consumer high-definition television with a 5:3 display aspect ratio.
actual: (24, u'3 display', 'NUMBER', 19, 20)
predicted question type: NUMBER



all results:
[   (59, u'C', 'OTHER', 56, 56),
    (59, u'July', 'OTHER', 61, 61),
    (59, u'D', 'OTHER', 54, 54),
    (59, u'HD Model Station', 'OTHER', 48, 50),
    (59, u'WHD', 'OTHER', 68, 68),
    (59, u'TV', 'OTHER', 70, 70),
    (59, u'NBC', 'OTHER', 78, 78),
    (59, u'TV', 'OTHER', 35, 35),
    (59, u'WRC', 'OTHER', 83, 83),
    (59, u'WRAL', 'OTHER', 33, 33),
    (59, u'TV', 'OTHER', 85, 85),
    (59, u'HD', 'OTHER', 25, 25),
    (59, u'WRAL', 'OTHER', 23, 23),
    (59, u'July', 'OTHER', 11, 11),
    (101, u'Hz', 'OTHER', 29, 29),
    (101, u'NTSC', 'OTHER', 22, 22),
    (101, u'Hz', 'OTHER', 16, 16),
    (101, u'SECAM', 'OTHER', 5, 5),
    (101, u'PAL', 'OTHER', 3, 3),
    (123, u'VHS', 'OTHER', 16, 16)]
question: Which country had successful public analog HDTV broadcasting?
expected: Japan
expected sentence: Japan remained the only country with successful public broadcasting of analog HDTV, with seven broadcasters sharing a single channel.
actual: (59, u'C', 'OTHER', 56, 56)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (57, u'Thomson', u'PERSON', 49, 49),
    (57, u'Sarnoff', u'PERSON', 47, 47),
    (68, u'Alfacam', u'PERSON', 14, 14),
    (15, u'Charles Ginsburg', u'PERSON', 13, 14),
    (28, u'Ronald Reagan', u'PERSON', 11, 12),
    (41, u'ETSI', 'OTHER', 12, 12),
    (41, u'DVB', 'OTHER', 1, 1),
    (90, u'RGB', 'OTHER', 35, 35),
    (90, u'YUV', 'OTHER', 13, 13),
    (90, u'10', 'NUMBER', 7, 7),
    (32, u'1990s', 'NUMBER', 8, 8),
    (117, u'HTPC', 'OTHER', 86, 86),
    (117, u'HD', 'OTHER', 78, 78),
    (117, u'3', 'NUMBER', 76, 76),
    (117, u'Series', 'OTHER', 75, 75),
    (117, u'TiVo', 'OTHER', 72, 72),
    (117, u'Digital', 'OTHER', 66, 66),
    (117, u'722', 'NUMBER', 62, 62),
    (117, u'VIP', 'OTHER', 61, 61),
    (117, u'622', 'NUMBER', 59, 59)]
actual: (57, u'Sarnoff', u'PERSON', 47, 47)
predicted question type: PERSON



all results:
[   (42, u'TV', 'OTHER', 18, 18),
    (42, u'S', 'OTHER', 8, 8),
    (42, u'TV', 'OTHER', 25, 25),
    (42, u'TV', 'OTHER', 11, 11),
    (45, u'MPEG', 'OTHER', 8, 8),
    (45, u'ATSC', 'OTHER', 1, 1),
    (45, u'H', 'OTHER', 29, 29),
    (45, u'264', 'NUMBER', 31, 31),
    (45, u'MPEG', 'OTHER', 33, 33),
    (45, u'4', 'NUMBER', 35, 35),
    (45, u'AVC', 'OTHER', 36, 36),
    (59, u'HD Model Station', 'OTHER', 48, 50),
    (59, u'Raleigh', u'LOCATION', 17, 17),
    (59, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 7, 8),
    (59, u'NBC', 'OTHER', 78, 78),
    (59, u'WHD', 'OTHER', 68, 68),
    (59, u'31,1996', 'NUMBER', 62, 64),
    (59, u'23,1996', 'NUMBER', 12, 14),
    (59, u'WRC', 'OTHER', 83, 83),
    (59, u'North Carolina', u'LOCATION', 19, 20)]
actual: (42, u'TV', 'OTHER', 18, 18)
predicted question type: PERSON



all results:
[   (47, u'6', 'NUMBER', 25, 25),
    (47, u'1983', 'NUMBER', 1, 1),
    (37, u'1972', 'NUMBER', 1, 1),
    (53, u'9 aspect', 'NUMBER', 23, 24),
    (53, u'16', 'NUMBER', 21, 21),
    (53, u'1080i', 'NUMBER', 35, 35),
    (53, u'1,080', 'NUMBER', 37, 39),
    (53, u'709', 'NUMBER', 17, 17),
    (53, u'2', 'NUMBER', 13, 13),
    (53, u'709', 'NUMBER', 11, 11),
    (53, u'1080p', 'NUMBER', 47, 47),
    (53, u'1,080', 'NUMBER', 49, 51),
    (39, u'709', 'NUMBER', 20, 20),
    (39, u'1993', 'NUMBER', 7, 7),
    (39, u'1', 'NUMBER', 5, 5),
    (36, u'seven broadcasters', 'NUMBER', 14, 15),
    (56, u'720p systems', 'NUMBER', 53, 54),
    (56, u'750', 'NUMBER', 8, 8),
    (56, u'1280 \xd7', 'NUMBER', 51, 52),
    (56, u'720p', 'NUMBER', 12, 12)]
actual: (47, u'6', 'NUMBER', 25, 25)
predicted question type: NUMBER



all results:
[   (67, u'HD1', 'OTHER', 27, 27),
    (67, u'IBC', 'OTHER', 7, 7),
    (67, u'September', 'OTHER', 10, 10),
    (67, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 40, 40),
    (28, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 28, 28),
    (28, u'President', 'OTHER', 10, 10),
    (28, u'MUSE', 'OTHER', 5, 5),
    (66, u'HD1', 'OTHER', 17, 17),
    (66, u'Belgian', 'OTHER', 12, 12),
    (66, u'Euro1080', 'OTHER', 14, 14),
    (66, u'January', 'OTHER', 6, 6),
    (66, u'Concert', 'OTHER', 27, 27),
    (69, u'HD1', 'OTHER', 1, 1),
    (60, u'Space Shuttle Discovery', 'OTHER', 38, 40),
    (60, u'American Advanced Television Systems Committee', 'OTHER', 1, 5),
    (60, u'October', 'OTHER', 16, 16),
    (60, u'ATSC', 'OTHER', 7, 7),
    (60, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 9, 9),
    (84, u'Hz', 'OTHER', 41, 41),
    (16, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 3, 3)]
question: The New Year's Day broadcast officially launched which channel?
expected: HD1
expected sentence: Test transmissions had been active since the IBC exhibition in September 2003, but the New Year's Day broadcast marked the official launch of the HD1 channel, and the official start of direct-to-home HDTV in Europe.
actual: (67, u'IBC', 'OTHER', 7, 7)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (66, u'Concert', 'OTHER', 27, 27),
    (66, u'New Year', 'OTHER', 23, 24),
    (66, u'Euro1080', 'OTHER', 14, 14),
    (66, u'Belgian', 'OTHER', 12, 12),
    (66, u'January', 'OTHER', 6, 6),
    (67, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 40, 40),
    (67, u'Day', 'OTHER', 19, 19),
    (67, u'New Year', 'OTHER', 15, 16),
    (67, u'September', 'OTHER', 10, 10),
    (67, u'IBC', 'OTHER', 7, 7),
    (72, u'Astra', 'OTHER', 85, 85),
    (72, u'HD', 'OTHER', 78, 78),
    (72, u'TV', 'OTHER', 74, 74),
    (72, u'TVs', 'OTHER', 51, 51),
    (72, u'HD', 'OTHER', 49, 49),
    (72, u'Astra', 'OTHER', 44, 44),
    (72, u'HD', 'OTHER', 42, 42),
    (72, u'Satellite Monitor', 'OTHER', 28, 29),
    (72, u'SES', 'OTHER', 24, 24),
    (72, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 20, 20)]
question: Which European company launched HD1?
expected: Euro1080
expected sentence: The first regular broadcasts started on January 1, 2004 when the Belgian company Euro1080 launched the HD1 channel with the traditional Vienna New Year's Concert.
actual: (66, u'January', 'OTHER', 6, 6)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (68, u'European', 'OTHER', 24, 24),
    (68, u'HD', 'OTHER', 29, 29),
    (68, u'Belgian TV', 'OTHER', 10, 11),
    (68, u'HD TVs', 'OTHER', 33, 34),
    (68, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 17, 17),
    (68, u'HD', 'OTHER', 38, 38),
    (68, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 45, 45),
    (101, u'Hz', 'OTHER', 16, 16),
    (101, u'SECAM', 'OTHER', 5, 5),
    (101, u'PAL', 'OTHER', 3, 3),
    (101, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 19, 19),
    (101, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 0, 0),
    (101, u'NTSC', 'OTHER', 22, 22),
    (101, u'Hz', 'OTHER', 29, 29),
    (66, u'Concert', 'OTHER', 27, 27),
    (66, u'New Year', 'OTHER', 23, 24),
    (66, u'HD1', 'OTHER', 17, 17),
    (66, u'Belgian', 'OTHER', 12, 12),
    (66, u'January', 'OTHER', 6, 6),
    (71, u'DVB', 'OTHER', 13, 13)]
actual: (68, u'European', 'OTHER', 24, 24)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (72, u'60 million', 'NUMBER', 56, 58),
    (72, u'20 million households', 'NUMBER', 63, 66),
    (72, u'185 million', 'NUMBER', 47, 49),
    (72, u'200', 'NUMBER', 37, 37),
    (72, u'27 %', 'NUMBER', 67, 68),
    (72, u'16 million', 'NUMBER', 82, 84),
    (56, u'720', 'NUMBER', 16, 16),
    (56, u'720p', 'NUMBER', 12, 12),
    (56, u'750', 'NUMBER', 8, 8),
    (56, u'1920', 'NUMBER', 47, 47),
    (56, u'1080i', 'NUMBER', 49, 49),
    (56, u'1280 \xd7', 'NUMBER', 51, 52),
    (56, u'720p systems', 'NUMBER', 53, 54),
    (105, u'720p', 'NUMBER', 14, 14),
    (105, u'720p', 'NUMBER', 24, 24),
    (105, u'1080i format', 'NUMBER', 16, 17),
    (105, u'720p', 'NUMBER', 48, 48),
    (105, u'1080i', 'NUMBER', 60, 60),
    (105, u'1080p.1080p', 'NUMBER', 62, 64),
    (105, u'24,1080i /', 'NUMBER', 66, 69)]
question: According to the 2010 Satellite Monitor market survey, how many HD capable TV's were sold in Europe?
expected: 185 million
expected sentence: Despite delays in some countries, the number of European HD channels and viewers has risen steadily since the first HDTV broadcasts, with SES's annual Satellite Monitor market survey for 2010 reporting more than 200 commercial channels broadcasting in HD from Astra satellites, 185 million HD capable TVs sold in Europe (£60 million in 2010 alone), and 20 million households (27% of all European digital satellite TV homes) watching HD satellite broadcasts (16 million via Astra satellites).
actual: (72, u'60 million', 'NUMBER', 56, 58)
predicted question type: NUMBER



all results:
[   (73, u'D', 'OTHER', 35, 35),
    (73, u'Digital TV Group', 'OTHER', 29, 31),
    (73, u'T2', 'OTHER', 21, 21),
    (73, u'DVB', 'OTHER', 19, 19),
    (73, u'European', 'OTHER', 9, 9),
    (73, u'December', 'OTHER', 1, 1),
    (73, u'United Kingdom', u'LOCATION', 4, 5),
    (73, u'2009', 'NUMBER', 2, 2),
    (73, u'DTG', 'OTHER', 33, 33)]
question: What does DTG stand for?
expected: Digital TV Group
expected sentence: In December 2009 the United Kingdom became the first European country to deploy high definition content using the new DVB-T2 transmission standard, as specified in the Digital TV Group (DTG) D-book, on digital terrestrial television.
actual: (73, u'December', 'OTHER', 1, 1)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (105, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 3, 3),
    (105, u'Blu', 'OTHER', 85, 85),
    (105, u'Disc', 'OTHER', 88, 88),
    (91, u'RGB', 'OTHER', 18, 18),
    (90, u'RGB', 'OTHER', 35, 35),
    (90, u'YUV', 'OTHER', 13, 13),
    (113, u'BD', 'OTHER', 37, 37),
    (113, u'Blu', 'OTHER', 31, 31),
    (113, u'Smart Televisions', 'OTHER', 28, 29),
    (113, u'AppleTV', 'OTHER', 23, 23),
    (113, u'GoogleTV Roku', 'OTHER', 19, 20),
    (113, u'IPTV', 'OTHER', 16, 16),
    (117, u'DirecTV', 'OTHER', 35, 35),
    (117, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 26, 26),
    (117, u'Digital', 'OTHER', 41, 41),
    (117, u'Sky HD', 'OTHER', 45, 46),
    (117, u'VHS', 'OTHER', 19, 19),
    (117, u'W', 'OTHER', 17, 17),
    (117, u'VHS', 'OTHER', 15, 15),
    (117, u'Data', 'OTHER', 13, 13)]
question: Which format is typically used for internet distribution of HD video?
expected: 720p
expected sentence: Non-cinematic HDTV video recordings intended for broadcast are typically recorded either in 720p or 1080i format as determined by the broadcaster. 720p is commonly used for Internet distribution of high-definition video, because most computer monitors operate in progressive-scan mode. 720p also imposes less strenuous storage and decoding requirements compared to both 1080i and 1080p. 1080p/24, 1080i/30, 1080i/25, and 720p/30 is most often used on Blu-ray Disc.
actual: (105, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 3, 3)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (113, u'BD', 'OTHER', 37, 37),
    (113, u'GoogleTV Roku', 'OTHER', 19, 20),
    (113, u'Smart Televisions', 'OTHER', 28, 29),
    (113, u'IPTV', 'OTHER', 16, 16),
    (113, u'Blu', 'OTHER', 31, 31),
    (117, u'HTPC', 'OTHER', 86, 86),
    (117, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 83, 83),
    (117, u'HD', 'OTHER', 78, 78),
    (117, u'Series', 'OTHER', 75, 75),
    (117, u'TiVo', 'OTHER', 72, 72),
    (117, u'Digital', 'OTHER', 66, 66),
    (117, u'VIP', 'OTHER', 61, 61),
    (117, u'VIP', 'OTHER', 58, 58),
    (117, u'Dish Network', 'OTHER', 54, 55),
    (117, u'Sky HD', 'OTHER', 45, 46),
    (117, u'Digital', 'OTHER', 41, 41),
    (117, u'DirecTV', 'OTHER', 35, 35),
    (117, u'HDTV', 'OTHER', 26, 26),
    (117, u'VHS', 'OTHER', 19, 19),
    (117, u'W', 'OTHER', 17, 17)]
actual: (113, u'GoogleTV Roku', 'OTHER', 19, 20)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (121, u'USB', 'OTHER', 50, 50),
    (121, u'PVR', 'OTHER', 47, 47),
    (121, u'DVD', 'OTHER', 39, 39),
    (121, u'Blu', 'OTHER', 26, 26),
    (121, u'MPEG', 'OTHER', 14, 14),
    (121, u'HD', 'OTHER', 3, 3),
    (73, u'D', 'OTHER', 35, 35),
    (73, u'DTG', 'OTHER', 33, 33),
    (73, u'Digital TV Group', 'OTHER', 29, 31),
    (73, u'T2', 'OTHER', 21, 21),
    (73, u'DVB', 'OTHER', 19, 19),
    (73, u'European', 'OTHER', 9, 9),
    (73, u'December', 'OTHER', 1, 1),
    (111, u'HD', 'OTHER', 9, 9),
    (111, u'TV', 'OTHER', 5, 5),
    (114, u'HD', 'OTHER', 52, 52),
    (114, u'Zune', 'OTHER', 43, 43),
    (114, u'Windows Media Center HTPC', 'OTHER', 34, 37),
    (114, u'Netflix', 'OTHER', 32, 32),
    (114, u'Xbox', 'OTHER', 26, 26)]
question: Content is now protected by what encryption?
expected: 5C
expected sentence: This content is protected by encryption known as 5C.
actual: (121, u'HD', 'OTHER', 3, 3)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (0, u'Commonwealth', 'OTHER', 15, 15),
    (289, u'Massachusetts Port Authority', 'OTHER', 37, 39),
        'OTHER',
        14,
        19),
    (289, u'MWRA', 'OTHER', 33, 33),
    (289, u'Massport', 'OTHER', 41, 41),
    (162, u'Route', 'OTHER', 1, 1),
    (168, u'Santander Bank', 'OTHER', 8, 9),
    (333, u'I', 'OTHER', 6, 6),
    (319, u'Spaulding Rehabilitation Hospital', 'OTHER', 15, 17),
    (319, u'Ear Infirmary', 'OTHER', 12, 13),
    (319, u'Eye', 'OTHER', 10, 10),
    (319, u'Massachusetts General Hospital', 'OTHER', 5, 7),
    (19, u'Cambridge Agreement', 'OTHER', 20, 21),
    (19, u'Massachusetts Bay Colony', 'OTHER', 4, 6),
    (291, u'Federal Reserve Bank of Boston', 'OTHER', 51, 55),
    (291, u'District', 'OTHER', 45, 45),
    (291, u'United States District Court', 'OTHER', 39, 42),
    (   291,
actual: (0, u'Commonwealth', 'OTHER', 15, 15)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (0, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 20, 21),
    (0, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 0, 0),
    (290, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 6, 6),
    (289, u'Bostonians', u'LOCATION', 50, 50),
    (2, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 37, 38),
    (2, u'New England', u'LOCATION', 28, 29),
    (164, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 0, 0),
    (168, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 12, 12),
    (182, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 61, 61),
    (182, u'Fenway', u'LOCATION', 37, 37),
    (182, u'Commonwealth Avenue', u'LOCATION', 22, 23),
    (182, u'Brighton', u'LOCATION', 63, 63),
    (182, u'Newton', u'LOCATION', 65, 65),
    (182, u'Beacon Hill', u'LOCATION', 43, 44),
    (278, u'Jamaica Pond', u'LOCATION', 4, 5),
    (278, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 7, 7),
    (26, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 8, 8),
    (75, u'Atlantic Ocean', u'LOCATION', 4, 5),
    (75, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 16, 17),
    (75, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 7, 7)]
actual: (0, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 20, 21)
predicted question type: LOCATION



all results:
[   (15, u'European', 'OTHER', 4, 4),
    (93, u'C', 'OTHER', 21, 21),
    (93, u'F', 'OTHER', 15, 15),
    (93, u'July', 'OTHER', 4, 4),
    (94, u'C', 'OTHER', 20, 20),
    (94, u'F', 'OTHER', 14, 14),
    (94, u'January', 'OTHER', 4, 4),
    (15, u'England', u'LOCATION', 36, 36),
    (15, u'Lincolnshire', u'LOCATION', 34, 34),
    (15, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 32, 32),
    (15, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 30, 30),
    (15, u'three mountains', 'NUMBER', 16, 17),
    (15, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 0, 0),
    (93, u'23.0', 'NUMBER', 17, 19),
    (93, u'73.4', 'NUMBER', 11, 13),
    (94, u'1.7', 'NUMBER', 16, 18),
    (94, u'29.0', 'NUMBER', 10, 12),
    (15, u'Trimountaine', 'OTHER', 11, 11)]
question: What does Trimountaine mean?
expected: three mountains
actual: (15, u'European', 'OTHER', 4, 4)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (31, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 3, 3),
    (31, u'Boston Brahmins', 'OTHER', 29, 30),
    (31, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 24, 24),
    (211, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 38, 38),
    (211, u'Boston Symphony Orchestra', 'OTHER', 13, 15),
    (211, u'Pops Orchestra', 'OTHER', 39, 40),
    (211, u'Boston Youth Symphony Orchestra', 'OTHER', 21, 24),
    (211, u'Back Bay', u'LOCATION', 6, 7),
    (211, u'Hall', 'OTHER', 1, 1),
    (63, u'Massachusetts General Hospital', 'OTHER', 3, 5),
    (63, u"Brigham and Women ' s Hospital", 'OTHER', 14, 19),
    (63, u'Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center', 'OTHER', 7, 11),
    (28, u'one', 'NUMBER', 8, 8),
    (28, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 6, 6),
    (190, u'Charles River', u'LOCATION', 17, 18),
    (190, u'Harvard University', 'OTHER', 0, 1),
    (190, u'Cambridge', u'LOCATION', 20, 20),
    (190, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 38, 38),
    (256, u'1903', 'NUMBER', 8, 8),
    (256, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 12, 12)]
actual: (31, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 3, 3)
predicted question type: PERSON



all results:
[   (34, u'Fugitive Slave Law', 'OTHER', 6, 8),
    (107, u'F', 'OTHER', 40, 40),
    (107, u'C', 'OTHER', 44, 44),
    (127, u'Hispanic', 'OTHER', 16, 16),
    (127, u'Hispanic', 'OTHER', 28, 28),
    (42, u'Irish', 'OTHER', 20, 20),
    (42, u'Tip O', 'OTHER', 36, 37),
    (42, u'Catholics', 'OTHER', 2, 2),
    (167, u'Fidelity Investments', 'OTHER', 3, 4),
    (188, u'Boston Conservatory and Berklee College of Music', 'OTHER', 4, 10),
    (346, u'Future', 'OTHER', 27, 27),
    (346, u'Five', 'OTHER', 24, 24),
    (346, u'Future Best City', 'OTHER', 33, 35),
    (24, u'Revolution', 'OTHER', 2, 2),
    (100, u'Nor', 'OTHER', 20, 20),
    (134, u'Chinese Americans', 'OTHER', 4, 5),
    (251, u'July', 'OTHER', 37, 37),
    (251, u'Boston the United States Olympic Committee', 'OTHER', 6, 11),
    (251, u'Summer Olympic Games', 'OTHER', 21, 23),
    (132, u'Irish', 'OTHER', 2, 2)]
actual: (34, u'Fugitive Slave Law', 'OTHER', 6, 8)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (66, u'2004', 'NUMBER', 58, 58),
    (66, u'Bank of America', 'OTHER', 54, 56),
    (66, u'Charlotte', u'LOCATION', 51, 51),
    (66, u'The New York Times', 'OTHER', 26, 29),
    (66, u'The Boston Globe', 'OTHER', 22, 24),
    (66, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 0, 0),
    (167, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 25, 26),
    (167, u'one', 'NUMBER', 17, 17),
    (167, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 16, 16),
    (167, u'1980s', 'NUMBER', 12, 12),
    (167, u'Fidelity Investments', 'OTHER', 3, 4),
    (167, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 0, 0),
    (46, u'Chinatown', u'LOCATION', 25, 25),
    (46, u'Financial District', 'OTHER', 21, 22),
    (46, u'West End', u'LOCATION', 17, 18),
    (46, u'South End', u'LOCATION', 13, 14),
    (83, u'South Boston', u'LOCATION', 37, 38),
    (83, u'Government Center', 'OTHER', 33, 34),
    (83, u'Financial District', 'OTHER', 30, 31),
    (83, u'Greek Revival', 'OTHER', 16, 17)]
actual: (66, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 0, 0)
predicted question type: PERSON



all results:
[   (81, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 0, 0),
    (164, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 0, 0),
    (289, u'Bostonians', u'LOCATION', 50, 50),
    (323, u'Massachusetts', u'LOCATION', 10, 10),
    (1, u'Suffolk County', u'LOCATION', 9, 10),
    (1, u'Massachusetts', u'LOCATION', 12, 12),
    (1, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 0, 0),
    (12, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 0, 0),
    (83, u'South Boston', u'LOCATION', 37, 38),
    (285, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 0, 0),
    (89, u'South Boston', u'LOCATION', 99, 100),
    (89, u'East Boston', u'LOCATION', 103, 104),
    (89, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 0, 0),
    (79, u'Milton', u'LOCATION', 21, 21),
    (79, u'Neponset River', u'LOCATION', 1, 2),
    (79, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 7, 7),
    (140, u'East Boston', u'LOCATION', 5, 6),
    (320, u'Brighton', u'LOCATION', 9, 9),
    (320, u'Brighton', u'LOCATION', 16, 16),
    (322, u'Jamaica Plain', u'LOCATION', 9, 10)]
actual: (81, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 0, 0)
predicted question type: LOCATION



all results:
[   (89, u'K\xf6ppen Dfa', 'OTHER', 51, 52),
    (89, u'January', 'OTHER', 25, 25),
    (89, u'C', 'OTHER', 16, 16),
    (89, u'Downtown', 'OTHER', 97, 97),
    (89, u'F', 'OTHER', 20, 20),
    (89, u'K\xf6ppen Cfa', 'OTHER', 42, 43),
    (78, u'The Graves', 'OTHER', 73, 74),
    (78, u'Shag Rocks', 'OTHER', 67, 68),
    (78, u'Nixes Mate', 'OTHER', 57, 58),
    (141, u'Puerto Rican', 'OTHER', 6, 7),
    (141, u'Colombian', 'OTHER', 51, 51),
    (141, u'Mexican', 'OTHER', 66, 66),
    (141, u'Guatemalan', 'OTHER', 82, 82),
    (127, u'Hispanic', 'OTHER', 16, 16),
    (127, u'Hispanic', 'OTHER', 28, 28),
    (35, u'Town', 'OTHER', 16, 16),
    (35, u'March', 'OTHER', 29, 29),
    (39, u'Irish', 'OTHER', 15, 15),
    (39, u'Polish Jews', 'OTHER', 29, 30)]
question: Most of the city lies in which USDA plant hardiness zone?
expected: 6b
expected sentence: Boston has a continental climate with some maritime influence, and using the −3 °C (27 °F) coldest month (January) isotherm, the city lies within the transition zone from a humid subtropical climate (Köppen Cfa) to a humid continental climate (Köppen Dfa), although the suburbs north and west of the city are significantly colder in winter and solidly fall under the latter categorization; the city lies at the transition between USDA plant hardiness zones 6b (most of the city) and 7a (Downtown, South Boston, and East Boston neighborhoods).
actual: (89, u'K\xf6ppen Dfa', 'OTHER', 51, 52)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (89, u'USDA', 'OTHER', 83, 83),
    (89, u'K\xf6ppen Dfa', 'OTHER', 51, 52),
    (89, u'January', 'OTHER', 25, 25),
    (89, u'C', 'OTHER', 16, 16),
    (89, u'Downtown', 'OTHER', 97, 97),
    (89, u'F', 'OTHER', 20, 20),
    (89, u'K\xf6ppen Cfa', 'OTHER', 42, 43),
    (94, u'January', 'OTHER', 4, 4),
    (94, u'F', 'OTHER', 14, 14),
    (94, u'C', 'OTHER', 20, 20),
    (93, u'July', 'OTHER', 4, 4),
    (93, u'F', 'OTHER', 15, 15),
    (93, u'C', 'OTHER', 21, 21),
    (96, u'C', 'OTHER', 33, 33),
    (96, u'February', 'OTHER', 16, 16),
    (96, u'F', 'OTHER', 29, 29),
    (96, u'F', 'OTHER', 7, 7),
    (96, u'C', 'OTHER', 11, 11),
    (328, u'Boston University School of Medicine', 'OTHER', 18, 22),
    (   328,
        u'Boston University Hospital and Boston City Hospital',
        'OTHER',
        42,
        48)]
question: What is the coldest month in Boston?
expected: January
expected sentence: Boston has a continental climate with some maritime influence, and using the −3 °C (27 °F) coldest month (January) isotherm, the city lies within the transition zone from a humid subtropical climate (Köppen Cfa) to a humid continental climate (Köppen Dfa), although the suburbs north and west of the city are significantly colder in winter and solidly fall under the latter categorization; the city lies at the transition between USDA plant hardiness zones 6b (most of the city) and 7a (Downtown, South Boston, and East Boston neighborhoods).
actual: (89, u'K\xf6ppen Dfa', 'OTHER', 51, 52)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (101, u'111 cm', 'NUMBER', 24, 25),
    (101, u'1,110 mm', 'NUMBER', 8, 11),
    (101, u'43.8 inches', 'NUMBER', 3, 6),
    (101, u'43.8 inches', 'NUMBER', 19, 22),
    (121, u'2.26', 'NUMBER', 5, 7),
    (121, u'3.08', 'NUMBER', 14, 16),
    (111, u'2,600 hours', 'NUMBER', 16, 19),
    (104, u'81.0', 'NUMBER', 47, 49),
    (104, u'9.3', 'NUMBER', 24, 26),
    (104, u'2011', 'NUMBER', 19, 19),
    (104, u'2.06 m', 'NUMBER', 52, 55),
    (104, u'23.6 cm', 'NUMBER', 29, 32),
    (104, u'12', 'NUMBER', 21, 21),
    (284, u'10,000 residents', 'NUMBER', 52, 55),
    (198, u'100,000 ).', 'NUMBER', 47, 50),
    (198, u'5.26', 'NUMBER', 43, 45),
    (198, u'1999', 'NUMBER', 36, 36),
    (198, u'one', 'NUMBER', 29, 29),
    (198, u'100,000 people', 'NUMBER', 19, 22),
    (198, u'26.5', 'NUMBER', 15, 17)]
question: What is the average snowfall per year in the City of Boston?
expected: 43.8 inches
expected sentence: The city averages 43.8 inches (1,110 mm) of precipitation a year, with 43.8 inches (111 cm) of snowfall per season.
actual: (101, u'1,110 mm', 'NUMBER', 8, 11)
predicted question type: NUMBER



all results:
[   (141, u'Puerto Rican', 'OTHER', 6, 7),
    (141, u'Colombian', 'OTHER', 51, 51),
    (141, u'Mexican', 'OTHER', 66, 66),
    (141, u'Guatemalan', 'OTHER', 82, 82),
    (23, u'Siege', 'OTHER', 37, 37),
    (23, u'Boston Tea Party', 'OTHER', 15, 17),
    (23, u'Boston Massacre', 'OTHER', 11, 12),
    (23, u'American Revolution', 'OTHER', 7, 8),
    (6, u'Siege', 'OTHER', 32, 32),
    (6, u'Bunker Hill', 'OTHER', 27, 28),
    (6, u'Battle', 'OTHER', 25, 25),
    (6, u'Boston Tea Party', 'OTHER', 20, 22),
    (6, u'Boston Massacre', 'OTHER', 16, 17),
    (6, u'American Revolution', 'OTHER', 10, 11),
    (219, u'North End', 'OTHER', 43, 44),
    (219, u'Boston Arts Festival', 'OTHER', 28, 30),
    (219, u'Early Music Festival', 'OTHER', 22, 24),
    (219, u'Eve', 'OTHER', 18, 18),
    (219, u'Catholic', 'OTHER', 46, 46),
    (219, u'Italian', 'OTHER', 38, 38)]
question: What can the population of Boston rech during special events?
expected: 2 million
expected sentence: Some 1.2 million persons may be within Boston's boundaries during work hours, and as many as 2 million during special events.
actual: (141, u'Puerto Rican', 'OTHER', 6, 7)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (127, u'49.5 %', 'NUMBER', 32, 35),
    (127, u'1950s', 'NUMBER', 2, 2),
    (127, u'2000', 'NUMBER', 24, 24),
    (123, u'46,540', 'NUMBER', 19, 21),
    (123, u'52,544 versus', 'NUMBER', 14, 17),
    (130, u'2010', 'NUMBER', 3, 3),
    (141, u'0.7 %', 'NUMBER', 88, 91),
    (141, u'1.0 %', 'NUMBER', 72, 75),
    (141, u'1.1 %', 'NUMBER', 57, 60),
    (141, u'1.8 %', 'NUMBER', 43, 46),
    (141, u'4.2 %', 'NUMBER', 28, 31),
    (141, u'4.9 %', 'NUMBER', 13, 16),
    (141, u'30,506', 'NUMBER', 9, 11),
    (141, u'4,451', 'NUMBER', 84, 86),
    (141, u'5,961', 'NUMBER', 68, 70),
    (141, u'6,649', 'NUMBER', 53, 55),
    (141, u'10,850', 'NUMBER', 39, 41),
    (141, u'25,648', 'NUMBER', 24, 26),
    (129, u'2006', 'NUMBER', 1, 1),
    (177, u'3,300 minority', 'NUMBER', 14, 17)]
actual: (127, u'1950s', 'NUMBER', 2, 2)
predicted question type: NUMBER



all results:
[   (175, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 22, 23),
    (175, u'US', u'LOCATION', 16, 16),
    (175, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 18, 18),
    (141, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 2, 2),
    (141, u'Dominican', u'LOCATION', 22, 22),
    (141, u'Salvadoran', u'LOCATION', 37, 37),
    (37, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 4, 4),
    (133, u'Caribbean', u'LOCATION', 5, 5),
    (196, u'United States Attorney', u'LOCATION', 39, 41),
    (196, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 0, 0),
    (2, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 37, 38),
    (2, u'New England', u'LOCATION', 28, 29),
    (182, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 61, 61),
    (182, u'Fenway', u'LOCATION', 37, 37),
    (182, u'Brighton', u'LOCATION', 63, 63),
    (182, u'Newton', u'LOCATION', 65, 65),
    (182, u'Commonwealth Avenue', u'LOCATION', 22, 23),
    (182, u'Beacon Hill', u'LOCATION', 43, 44),
    (278, u'Jamaica Pond', u'LOCATION', 4, 5),
    (278, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 7, 7)]
actual: (175, u'US', u'LOCATION', 16, 16)
predicted question type: LOCATION



all results:
[   (138, u'227,000', 'NUMBER', 18, 20),
    (138, u'25,000 Jews', 'NUMBER', 10, 13),
    (138, u'22', 'NUMBER', 36, 36),
    (139, u'one', 'NUMBER', 10, 10),
    (147, u'160 churches', 'NUMBER', 47, 48),
    (147, u'58,000 adherents', 'NUMBER', 42, 45),
    (147, u'2010', 'NUMBER', 2, 2),
    (147, u'339 churches', 'NUMBER', 33, 34),
    (147, u'two million members', 'NUMBER', 29, 32),
    (120, u'18 living', 'NUMBER', 19, 20),
    (120, u'25.5 %', 'NUMBER', 24, 27),
    (120, u'20.4 %', 'NUMBER', 9, 12),
    (120, u'252,699 households', 'NUMBER', 2, 5),
    (120, u'16.3 %', 'NUMBER', 34, 37),
    (120, u'54.0 %', 'NUMBER', 48, 51),
    (120, u'37.1 %', 'NUMBER', 57, 60),
    (120, u'9.0 %', 'NUMBER', 70, 73),
    (120, u'65 years', 'NUMBER', 80, 81),
    (69, u'129th', 'NUMBER', 24, 24),
    (69, u'2011 survey', 'NUMBER', 34, 35)]
question: How many Jewish people live in the Boston Metro area?
expected sentence: The city has a sizable Jewish population with an estimated 25,000 Jews within the city and 227,000 within the Boston metro area; the number of congregations in Boston is estimated at 22.
actual: (138, u'25,000 Jews', 'NUMBER', 10, 13)
predicted question type: NUMBER



all results:
[   (163, u'2014', 'NUMBER', 47, 47),
    (163, u'8.3 billion', 'NUMBER', 23, 26),
    (163, u'1.4 million', 'NUMBER', 38, 41),
    (163, u'21.2 million', 'NUMBER', 13, 16),
    (9, u'20 million visitors', 'NUMBER', 13, 16),
    (69, u'2011 survey', 'NUMBER', 34, 35),
    (69, u'214 cities', 'NUMBER', 37, 38),
    (69, u'129th', 'NUMBER', 24, 24),
    (69, u'one', 'NUMBER', 8, 8),
    (70, u'36th worldwide', 'NUMBER', 14, 15),
    (70, u'221', 'NUMBER', 26, 26),
    (250, u'2011 ).', 'NUMBER', 57, 58),
    (250, u'2008 ),', 'NUMBER', 52, 53),
    (250, u'2013 ),', 'NUMBER', 48, 49),
    (250, u'2004,2007', 'NUMBER', 43, 45),
    (250, u'2014 ),', 'NUMBER', 38, 39),
    (250, u'2004', 'NUMBER', 35, 35),
    (250, u'2001,2003', 'NUMBER', 31, 33),
    (250, u'2001', 'NUMBER', 27, 27),
    (250, u'nine championships', 'NUMBER', 24, 25)]
question: How many tourists visited Boston in 2011?
expected: 21.2 million
expected sentence: Tourism also composes a large part of Boston's economy, with 21.2 million domestic and international visitors spending $8.3 billion in 2011; excluding visitors from Canada and Mexico, over 1.4 million international tourists visited Boston in 2014, with those from China and the United Kingdom leading the list.
actual: (163, u'8.3 billion', 'NUMBER', 23, 26)
predicted question type: NUMBER



all results:
[   (163, u'21.2 million', 'NUMBER', 13, 16),
    (163, u'2014', 'NUMBER', 47, 47),
    (163, u'1.4 million', 'NUMBER', 38, 41),
    (163, u'2011', 'NUMBER', 28, 28),
    (163, u'8.3 billion', 'NUMBER', 23, 26),
    (9, u'20 million visitors', 'NUMBER', 13, 16),
    (346, u'1 %', 'NUMBER', 49, 50),
    (346, u'2000', 'NUMBER', 52, 52),
    (346, u'2008', 'NUMBER', 1, 1),
    (346, u'2.1 %', 'NUMBER', 54, 57),
    (346, u'2009', 'NUMBER', 59, 59),
    (143, u'25,000 +,', 'NUMBER', 32, 35),
    (143, u'22,000 +.', 'NUMBER', 39, 42),
    (143, u'31,000 +,', 'NUMBER', 27, 30),
    (143, u'40,000 +,', 'NUMBER', 22, 25),
    (143, u'95,000 +,', 'NUMBER', 17, 20),
    (143, u'175,000 +,', 'NUMBER', 12, 15),
    (167, u'one', 'NUMBER', 17, 17),
    (167, u'1980s', 'NUMBER', 12, 12),
    (154, u'30', 'NUMBER', 10, 10)]
question: What year did the number of Tourists from china and the UK top the list?
expected: 2014
expected sentence: Tourism also composes a large part of Boston's economy, with 21.2 million domestic and international visitors spending $8.3 billion in 2011; excluding visitors from Canada and Mexico, over 1.4 million international tourists visited Boston in 2014, with those from China and the United Kingdom leading the list.
actual: (163, u'21.2 million', 'NUMBER', 13, 16)
predicted question type: NUMBER



all results:
[   (174, u'145 schools', 'NUMBER', 10, 11),
    (174, u'57,000 students', 'NUMBER', 5, 8),
    (175, u'1635', 'NUMBER', 6, 6),
    (10, u'1897 ).', 'NUMBER', 25, 26),
    (10, u'1635 ),', 'NUMBER', 18, 19),
    (177, u'3,300 minority', 'NUMBER', 14, 17),
    (84, u'two', 'NUMBER', 29, 29),
    (114, u'2 million', 'NUMBER', 21, 23),
    (114, u'1.2 million persons', 'NUMBER', 1, 5),
    (195, u'1990s', 'NUMBER', 18, 18),
    (174, u'Boston Latin School', 'OTHER', 33, 35),
    (174, u'Bryant School of Math & Science', 'OTHER', 25, 30),
    (174, u'O', 'OTHER', 23, 23),
    (174, u'John D', u'PERSON', 20, 21),
    (174, u'Boston Latin Academy', 'OTHER', 16, 18),
    (174, u'Boston Public Schools', 'OTHER', 1, 3),
    (175, u'US', u'LOCATION', 16, 16),
    (175, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 22, 23),
    (175, u'Boston Latin School', 'OTHER', 1, 3),
    (187, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 71, 72)]
question: How many schools are in Boston?
expected: 145 schools
expected sentence: The Boston Public Schools enrolls 57,000 students attending 145 schools, including the renowned Boston Latin Academy, John D. O'Bryant School of Math & Science, and Boston Latin School.
actual: (174, u'57,000 students', 'NUMBER', 5, 8)
predicted question type: NUMBER



all results:
[   (186, u'New England School of Law', 'OTHER', 48, 52),
    (186, u'Wentworth Institute of Technology', 'OTHER', 43, 46),
    (   186,
    (186, u'Wheelock College', 'OTHER', 40, 41),
    (186, u'Fisher College', 'OTHER', 17, 18),
    (186, u'Emerson College', 'OTHER', 67, 68),
    (186, u'Simmons College', 'OTHER', 34, 35),
    (186, u'Wellesley College', 'OTHER', 37, 38),
    (186, u'Emmanuel College', 'OTHER', 14, 15),
    (186, u'Boston Architectural College', 'OTHER', 10, 12),
    (186, u'Bentley University', 'OTHER', 7, 8),
    (186, u'Babson College', 'OTHER', 4, 5),
    (258, u'Braves', 'OTHER', 20, 20),
    (258, u'Beaneaters', 'OTHER', 12, 12),
    (182, u'South End', 'OTHER', 30, 31),
    (182, u'Northeastern University', 'OTHER', 33, 34),
    (182, u'Boston University', 'OTHER', 5, 6),
    (182, u'Boston College', 'OTHER', 55, 56),
    (182, u'Suffolk University', 'OTHER', 40, 41)]
actual: (186, u'Wentworth Institute of Technology', 'OTHER', 43, 46)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (187, u'Design', 'OTHER', 46, 46),
    (187, u'New England School of Art', 'OTHER', 40, 44),
    (187, u'New England Institute of Art', 'OTHER', 34, 38),
    (187, u'Suffolk University', 'OTHER', 48, 49),
    (187, u'Metropolitan Boston', 'OTHER', 0, 1),
    (186, u'Emerson College', 'OTHER', 67, 68),
    (186, u'New England School of Law', 'OTHER', 48, 52),
    (186, u'Wentworth Institute of Technology', 'OTHER', 43, 46),
    (   186,
    (186, u'Wheelock College', 'OTHER', 40, 41),
    (186, u'Simmons College', 'OTHER', 34, 35),
    (186, u'Fisher College', 'OTHER', 17, 18),
    (186, u'Wellesley College', 'OTHER', 37, 38),
    (186, u'Emmanuel College', 'OTHER', 14, 15),
    (186, u'Boston Architectural College', 'OTHER', 10, 12)]
actual: (187, u'Design', 'OTHER', 18, 18)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (187, u'New England School of Art', 'OTHER', 40, 44),
    (187, u'New England Institute of Art', 'OTHER', 34, 38),
    (187, u'Suffolk University', 'OTHER', 48, 49),
    (187, u'Metropolitan Boston', 'OTHER', 0, 1),
    (258, u'Braves', 'OTHER', 20, 20),
    (258, u'Beaneaters', 'OTHER', 12, 12),
    (225, u'Contemporary Art', 'OTHER', 3, 4),
    (225, u'Institute', 'OTHER', 1, 1),
    (225, u'Seaport District', 'OTHER', 19, 20),
    (224, u'Museum of Fine Arts', 'OTHER', 12, 15),
    (277, u'Emerald Necklace', 'OTHER', 13, 14),
    (212, u'Boston Symphony Hall', 'OTHER', 6, 8),
    (212, u'The Guardian', 'OTHER', 3, 4),
    (212, u'Symphony Hall', 'OTHER', 25, 26),
    (212, u'British', 'OTHER', 1, 1),
    (265, u'New England Patriots', 'OTHER', 11, 13)]
actual: (187, u'Lesley University College of Art', 'OTHER', 12, 16)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (210, u'American', 'OTHER', 17, 17),
    (210, u'Big Five', 'OTHER', 9, 10),
    (210, u'Gramophone', 'OTHER', 25, 25),
    (211, u'Pops Orchestra', 'OTHER', 39, 40),
    (211, u'Boston Youth Symphony Orchestra', 'OTHER', 21, 24),
    (211, u'Hall', 'OTHER', 1, 1),
    (212, u'The Guardian', 'OTHER', 3, 4),
    (212, u'British', 'OTHER', 1, 1),
    (212, u'Boston Symphony Hall', 'OTHER', 6, 8),
    (212, u'Symphony Hall', 'OTHER', 25, 26),
    (215, u'Handel', 'OTHER', 33, 33),
    (215, u'Baroque', 'OTHER', 25, 25),
    (215, u'Boston Lyric Opera Company', 'OTHER', 11, 14),
    (215, u'Haydn Society', 'OTHER', 35, 36),
    (215, u'Boston Baroque', 'OTHER', 19, 20),
    (217, u'Boston Modern Orchestra Project', 'OTHER', 3, 6),
    (217, u'Boston Musica Viva', 'OTHER', 8, 10),
    (346, u'Future', 'OTHER', 27, 27),
    (346, u'Five', 'OTHER', 24, 24),
    (346, u'Future Best City', 'OTHER', 33, 35)]
question: What classical music magazine called the Boston Symphony orchestra one of the worlds best orchestras?
expected: Gramophone
expected sentence: The Boston Symphony Orchestra is one of the "Big Five," a group of the greatest American orchestras, and the classical music magazine Gramophone called it one of the "world's best" orchestras.
actual: (210, u'Big Five', 'OTHER', 9, 10)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (96, u'14,2016', 'NUMBER', 17, 19),
    (96, u'18', 'NUMBER', 9, 9),
    (96, u'0', 'NUMBER', 5, 5),
    (96, u'9', 'NUMBER', 27, 27),
    (96, u'23', 'NUMBER', 31, 31),
    (96, u'1957', 'NUMBER', 39, 39),
    (273, u'42.2 km', 'NUMBER', 22, 25),
    (273, u'26.2', 'NUMBER', 16, 18),
    (273, u'One', 'NUMBER', 0, 0),
    (114, u'2 million', 'NUMBER', 21, 23),
    (114, u'1.2 million persons', 'NUMBER', 1, 5),
    (104, u'2.06 m', 'NUMBER', 52, 55),
    (104, u'81.0', 'NUMBER', 47, 49),
    (104, u'23.6 cm', 'NUMBER', 29, 32),
    (104, u'9.3', 'NUMBER', 24, 26),
    (104, u'12', 'NUMBER', 21, 21),
    (104, u'2011', 'NUMBER', 19, 19),
    (123, u'46,540', 'NUMBER', 19, 21),
    (123, u'52,544 versus', 'NUMBER', 14, 17),
    (2, u'24th', 'NUMBER', 32, 32)]
actual: (96, u'14,2016', 'NUMBER', 17, 19)
predicted question type: NUMBER



all results:
[   (187, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 71, 72),
    (187, u'New England Conservatory', u'LOCATION', 61, 63),
    (160, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 20, 21),
    (273, u'Boston Marathon', u'LOCATION', 12, 13),
    (215, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 46, 47),
    (215, u'US', u'LOCATION', 29, 29),
    (215, u'Opera Boston', u'LOCATION', 16, 17),
    (328, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 58, 59),
    (328, u'South End', u'LOCATION', 7, 8),
    (23, u'Lexington', u'LOCATION', 29, 29),
    (23, u'Concord', u'LOCATION', 31, 31),
    (15, u'England', u'LOCATION', 36, 36),
    (15, u'Lincolnshire', u'LOCATION', 34, 34),
    (49, u'South Boston', u'LOCATION', 7, 8),
    (49, u'East Boston', u'LOCATION', 12, 13),
    (49, u'Roxbury', u'LOCATION', 17, 17),
    (49, u'Dorchester', u'LOCATION', 21, 21),
    (49, u'Mattapan', u'LOCATION', 26, 26),
    (49, u'South Boston', u'LOCATION', 31, 32),
    (49, u'Brighton', u'LOCATION', 37, 37)]
actual: (187, u'New England Conservatory', u'LOCATION', 61, 63)
predicted question type: LOCATION



all results:
[   (230, u'Beacon Hill', u'LOCATION', 6, 7),
    (168, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 12, 12),
    (170, u'Houghton Mifflin Harcourt', u'LOCATION', 8, 10),
    (170, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 0, 0),
    (300, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 7, 7),
    (173, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 23, 23),
    (173, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 33, 33),
    (173, u'Fairfield', u'LOCATION', 26, 26),
    (173, u'Connecticut', u'LOCATION', 28, 28),
    (231, u'Mother Church', 'OTHER', 10, 11),
    (231, u'Christian Scientists', 'OTHER', 1, 2),
    (231, u'Back Bay', 'OTHER', 6, 7),
    (231, u'1894 ).', 'NUMBER', 13, 14),
    (230, u'Unitarian Universalism', 'OTHER', 0, 1),
    (168, u'Santander Bank', 'OTHER', 8, 9),
    (170, u'Bedford', 'OTHER', 19, 19),
    (170, u'St', 'OTHER', 21, 21),
    (170, u'Martin', u'PERSON', 23, 23),
    (170, u'Press', 'OTHER', 26, 26),
    (170, u'Beacon Press', 'OTHER', 28, 29)]
actual: (230, u'Beacon Hill', u'LOCATION', 6, 7)
predicted question type: LOCATION



all results:
[   (235, u'2004 –', 'NUMBER', 15, 16),
    (235, u'4 days', 'NUMBER', 22, 23),
    (250, u'2013 ),', 'NUMBER', 48, 49),
    (250, u'2004,2007', 'NUMBER', 43, 45),
    (250, u'2008 ),', 'NUMBER', 52, 53),
    (250, u'2014 ),', 'NUMBER', 38, 39),
    (250, u'2001,2003', 'NUMBER', 31, 33),
    (250, u'2011 ).', 'NUMBER', 57, 58),
    (250, u'2001', 'NUMBER', 27, 27),
    (250, u'nine championships', 'NUMBER', 24, 25),
    (49, u'1874 ),', 'NUMBER', 63, 64),
    (49, u'1912 ).', 'NUMBER', 69, 70),
    (49, u'1874', 'NUMBER', 59, 59),
    (49, u'1868 ),', 'NUMBER', 19, 20),
    (49, u'1804', 'NUMBER', 10, 10),
    (49, u'1870', 'NUMBER', 35, 35),
    (49, u'1874', 'NUMBER', 45, 45),
    (49, u'1836', 'NUMBER', 15, 15),
    (266, u'2014 seasons', 'NUMBER', 15, 16),
    (266, u'2001,2003', 'NUMBER', 8, 10)]
question: How many days between 2004 and 2013 was the air unhealthy?
expected: 4 days
expected sentence: Air quality in Boston is generally very good: during the ten-year period 2004–2013, there were only 4 days in which the air was unhealthy for the general public, according to the EPA.
actual: (235, u'2004 –', 'NUMBER', 15, 16)
predicted question type: NUMBER



all results:
[   (   260,
        'OTHER',
        46,
        52),
    (260, u'National Hockey League', 'OTHER', 41, 43),
    (260, u'Boston Bruins', 'OTHER', 37, 38),
    (260, u'TD Garden', 'OTHER', 1, 2),
    (260, u'North Station', 'OTHER', 24, 25),
    (334, u'Big Dig', 'OTHER', 29, 30),
    (334, u'O', 'OTHER', 23, 23),
    (334, u'Central Artery', 'OTHER', 5, 6),
    (291, u'Federal Reserve Bank of Boston', 'OTHER', 51, 55),
    (291, u'District', 'OTHER', 45, 45),
    (291, u'United States District Court', 'OTHER', 39, 42),
    (   291,
        'OTHER',
        28,
        36),
    (291, u'Neill Federal Building', 'OTHER', 23, 25),
    (291, u'Kennedy Federal Office Building', 'OTHER', 12, 15),
    (291, u'O', 'OTHER', 21, 21),
    (241, u'Mayor', 'OTHER', 7, 7),
    (239, u'Building Energy Reporting', 'OTHER', 4, 6),
    (239, u'Disclosure Ordinance', 'OTHER', 8, 9),
    (225, u'Seaport District', 'OTHER', 19, 20)]
actual: (260, u'TD Garden', 'OTHER', 1, 2)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (265, u'Boston Patriots', 'OTHER', 25, 26),
    (265, u'National Football League', 'OTHER', 16, 18),
    (258, u'Braves', 'OTHER', 20, 20),
    (258, u'Beaneaters', 'OTHER', 12, 12),
    (82, u'Back Bay', 'OTHER', 77, 78),
    (82, u'Trimountain', 'OTHER', 57, 57),
    (82, u'Tremont Street', 'OTHER', 61, 62),
    (250, u'TitleTown', 'OTHER', 10, 10),
    (250, u'Red Sox', 'OTHER', 40, 41),
    (250, u'Celtics', 'OTHER', 50, 50),
    (250, u'Bruins', 'OTHER', 55, 55),
    (262, u'National Hockey League', 'OTHER', 9, 11),
    (262, u'Bruins', 'OTHER', 1, 1),
    (262, u'American', 'OTHER', 5, 5),
    (262, u'Original Six', 'OTHER', 14, 15),
    (273, u'Day', 'OTHER', 42, 42),
    (273, u'April', 'OTHER', 44, 44),
    (187, u'New England School of Art', 'OTHER', 40, 44),
    (187, u'New England Institute of Art', 'OTHER', 34, 38),
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (251, u'2024', 'NUMBER', 20, 20),
    (251, u'27,2015', 'NUMBER', 38, 40),
    (48, u'2.4 km2', 'NUMBER', 16, 19),
    (48, u'600 acres', 'NUMBER', 13, 14),
    (275, u'October', 'OTHER', 14, 14),
    (190, u'Charles River', u'LOCATION', 17, 18),
    (190, u'Harvard University', 'OTHER', 0, 1),
    (190, u'Cambridge', u'LOCATION', 20, 20),
    (190, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 38, 38),
    (213, u'New England Conservatory', 'OTHER', 6, 8),
    (213, u'Jordan Hall', u'LOCATION', 11, 12),
    (251, u'Boston the United States Olympic Committee', 'OTHER', 6, 11),
    (251, u'Summer Olympic Games', 'OTHER', 21, 23),
    (251, u'July', 'OTHER', 37, 37),
    (77, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 17, 17),
    (77, u'Cambridge', u'LOCATION', 11, 11),
    (77, u'Charles River', u'LOCATION', 1, 2),
    (77, u'Watertown', u'LOCATION', 6, 6),
    (77, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 4, 4),
    (77, u'Charlestown', u'LOCATION', 21, 21)]
actual: (251, u'2024', 'NUMBER', 20, 20)
predicted question type: NUMBER



all results:
[   (174, u'John D', u'PERSON', 20, 21),
    (318, u'Dana', u'PERSON', 45, 45),
    (288, u'The School Committee', 'OTHER', 0, 2),
    (323, u'Massachusetts', u'LOCATION', 10, 10),
    (323, u'Boston Public Health Commission', 'OTHER', 1, 4),
    (175, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 22, 23),
    (175, u'US', u'LOCATION', 16, 16),
    (175, u'Boston Latin School', 'OTHER', 1, 3),
    (175, u'1635', 'NUMBER', 6, 6),
    (174, u'Boston Latin Academy', 'OTHER', 16, 18),
    (174, u'145 schools', 'NUMBER', 10, 11),
    (174, u'57,000 students', 'NUMBER', 5, 8),
    (174, u'O', 'OTHER', 23, 23),
    (174, u'Bryant School of Math & Science', 'OTHER', 25, 30),
    (174, u'Boston Latin School', 'OTHER', 33, 35),
    (187, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 71, 72),
    (187, u'New England Conservatory', u'LOCATION', 61, 63),
actual: (174, u'John D', u'PERSON', 20, 21)
predicted question type: PERSON



all results:
[   (289, u'Massachusetts Port Authority', 'OTHER', 37, 39),
        'OTHER',
        14,
        19),
    (289, u'Massport', 'OTHER', 41, 41),
    (289, u'Bostonians', u'LOCATION', 50, 50),
    (289, u'MWRA', 'OTHER', 33, 33)]
question: What is the MWRA?
expected: Massachusetts Water Resources Authority
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
        'OTHER',
        14,
        19),
    (289, u'Boston Public Health Commission', 'OTHER', 22, 25),
    (289, u'MWRA', 'OTHER', 33, 33),
    (289, u'Massport', 'OTHER', 41, 41),
    (258, u'Braves', 'OTHER', 20, 20),
    (258, u'Beaneaters', 'OTHER', 12, 12),
    (329, u'Massport', 'OTHER', 15, 15),
    (336, u'T', 'OTHER', 18, 18),
    (336, u'MBTA', 'OTHER', 12, 12),
    (52, u'Boston Redevelopment Authority', 'OTHER', 13, 15),
    (52, u'BRA', 'OTHER', 17, 17),
    (265, u'Boston Patriots', 'OTHER', 25, 26),
    (265, u'National Football League', 'OTHER', 16, 18),
    (265, u'New England Patriots', 'OTHER', 11, 13),
    (35, u'City', 'OTHER', 43, 43),
    (35, u'City', 'OTHER', 23, 23),
    (35, u'Town', 'OTHER', 16, 16),
    (35, u'March', 'OTHER', 29, 29)]
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (293, u'1998', 'NUMBER', 19, 19),
    (293, u'three', 'NUMBER', 2, 2),
    (287, u'four citywide', 'NUMBER', 17, 18),
    (287, u'nine district', 'NUMBER', 12, 13),
    (287, u'two years', 'NUMBER', 7, 8),
    (296, u'2012', 'NUMBER', 19, 19),
    (297, u'2013', 'NUMBER', 20, 20),
    (104, u'2.06 m', 'NUMBER', 52, 55),
    (104, u'81.0', 'NUMBER', 47, 49),
    (104, u'23.6 cm', 'NUMBER', 29, 32),
    (104, u'9.3', 'NUMBER', 24, 26),
    (104, u'12', 'NUMBER', 21, 21),
    (104, u'2011', 'NUMBER', 19, 19),
    (123, u'46,540', 'NUMBER', 19, 21),
    (123, u'52,544 versus', 'NUMBER', 14, 17),
    (9, u'20 million visitors', 'NUMBER', 13, 16),
    (16, u'7,1630', 'NUMBER', 5, 7),
    (21, u'four', 'NUMBER', 10, 10),
    (21, u'130 years', 'NUMBER', 3, 4),
    (286, u'2014', 'NUMBER', 6, 6)]
question: What year was Capuano elected?
expected: 1998
expected sentence: The northern three-fourths of the city is in the 7th district, represented by Mike Capuano since 1998.
actual: (293, u'three', 'NUMBER', 2, 2)
predicted question type: NUMBER



all results:
[   (308, u'CBS Radio WBZ', 'OTHER', 16, 18),
    (308, u'WEEI', 'OTHER', 13, 13),
    (308, u'WRKO', 'OTHER', 7, 7),
    (310, u'WGBH', 'OTHER', 17, 17),
    (310, u'WBUR', 'OTHER', 15, 15),
    (310, u'NPR', 'OTHER', 13, 13),
    (310, u'FM', 'OTHER', 4, 4),
    (311, u'WMLN', 'OTHER', 54, 54),
    (311, u'Northeastern University', 'OTHER', 50, 51),
    (311, u'FM', 'OTHER', 56, 56),
    (311, u'Boston University', 'OTHER', 40, 41),
    (311, u'WRBB', 'OTHER', 48, 48),
    (311, u'Curry College', 'OTHER', 58, 59),
    (311, u'WERS', 'OTHER', 6, 6),
    (311, u'WTBU', 'OTHER', 38, 38),
    (311, u'Brandeis University', 'OTHER', 35, 36),
    (311, u'WHRB', 'OTHER', 10, 10),
    (311, u'WBRS', 'OTHER', 33, 33),
    (311, u'Harvard', 'OTHER', 12, 12),
    (311, u'Tufts University', 'OTHER', 30, 31)]
actual: (308, u'CBS Radio WBZ', 'OTHER', 16, 18)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (310, u'FM', 'OTHER', 4, 4),
    (310, u'NPR', 'OTHER', 13, 13),
    (314, u'PBS', 'OTHER', 16, 16),
    (314, u'TV', 'OTHER', 10, 10),
    (314, u'WGBX', 'OTHER', 22, 22),
    (314, u'PBS', 'OTHER', 6, 6),
    (308, u'CBS Radio WBZ', 'OTHER', 16, 18),
    (308, u'WEEI', 'OTHER', 13, 13),
    (308, u'WRKO', 'OTHER', 7, 7),
    (308, u'AM', 'OTHER', 2, 2),
    (311, u'WMLN', 'OTHER', 54, 54),
    (311, u'Northeastern University', 'OTHER', 50, 51),
    (311, u'FM', 'OTHER', 56, 56),
    (311, u'Boston University', 'OTHER', 40, 41),
    (311, u'WRBB', 'OTHER', 48, 48),
    (311, u'Curry College', 'OTHER', 58, 59),
    (311, u'WERS', 'OTHER', 6, 6),
    (311, u'WTBU', 'OTHER', 38, 38),
    (311, u'Brandeis University', 'OTHER', 35, 36),
    (311, u'WHRB', 'OTHER', 10, 10)]
question: WBUR and WGBH are exaples of what type of radio station?
expected: NPR
expected sentence: A variety of commercial FM radio formats serve the area, as do NPR stations WBUR and WGBH.
actual: (310, u'FM', 'OTHER', 4, 4)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
    (194, u'Children', 'OTHER', 56, 56),
    (194, u'Floating Hospital', 'OTHER', 53, 54),
    (194, u'Tufts University', 'OTHER', 0, 1),
    (15, u'Trimountaine', 'OTHER', 11, 11),
    (15, u'European', 'OTHER', 4, 4),
    (16, u'Puritan', 'OTHER', 16, 16),
    (16, u'Old Style', 'OTHER', 9, 10),
    (16, u'September', 'OTHER', 4, 4),
    (   318,
        'OTHER',
        61,
        67),
    (318, u'Joslin Diabetes Center', 'OTHER', 55, 57),
    (318, u'Harvard Medical School', 'OTHER', 51, 53),
    (318, u'Farber Cancer Institute', 'OTHER', 47, 49),
    (318, u'Children', 'OTHER', 39, 39),
    (318, u'Hospital', 'OTHER', 37, 37),
    (318, u'Women', 'OTHER', 34, 34),
    (318, u'Brigham', 'OTHER', 32, 32),
    (318, u'Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center', 'OTHER', 26, 30),
    (318, u'Academic Area', 'OTHER', 4, 5),
    (318, u'Longwood Medical', 'OTHER', 1, 2)]
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (327, u'New England Medical Center', 'OTHER', 7, 10),
    (194, u'Floating Hospital', 'OTHER', 53, 54),
    (194, u'Children', 'OTHER', 56, 56),
    (194, u'Tufts University', 'OTHER', 0, 1),
    (   318,
        'OTHER',
        61,
        67),
    (318, u'Longwood Medical', 'OTHER', 1, 2),
    (318, u'Joslin Diabetes Center', 'OTHER', 55, 57),
    (318, u'Academic Area', 'OTHER', 4, 5),
    (318, u'Harvard Medical School', 'OTHER', 51, 53),
    (318, u'Farber Cancer Institute', 'OTHER', 47, 49),
    (318, u'Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center', 'OTHER', 26, 30),
    (318, u'Children', 'OTHER', 39, 39),
    (318, u'Hospital', 'OTHER', 37, 37),
    (318, u'Brigham', 'OTHER', 32, 32),
    (318, u'Women', 'OTHER', 34, 34),
    (311, u'Curry College', 'OTHER', 58, 59),
    (311, u'FM', 'OTHER', 56, 56),
    (311, u'WMLN', 'OTHER', 54, 54),
    (311, u'Northeastern University', 'OTHER', 50, 51)]
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (315, u'Telefutura', u'PERSON', 22, 22),
    (329, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 18, 18),
    (329, u'Massport', 'OTHER', 15, 15),
    (329, u'Massachusetts Port Authority', 'OTHER', 11, 13),
    (329, u'East Boston', u'LOCATION', 5, 6),
    (330, u'Norwood Memorial Airport', u'LOCATION', 19, 21),
    (330, u'Hanscom Field', u'LOCATION', 12, 13),
    (73, u'5.8 m', 'NUMBER', 18, 21),
    (73, u'19 ft', 'NUMBER', 15, 16),
    (73, u'Logan International Airport', u'LOCATION', 10, 12),
    (165, u'Western Hemisphere', u'LOCATION', 24, 25),
    (165, u"United States ' East Coast", u'LOCATION', 8, 12),
    (331, u'East Boston', u'LOCATION', 35, 36),
    (331, u'Charlestown', u'LOCATION', 33, 33),
    (331, u'South Boston', u'LOCATION', 26, 27),
    (331, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 10, 10),
    (331, u'Port', 'OTHER', 8, 8),
    (331, u'Massport', 'OTHER', 0, 0),
    (175, u'United States', u'LOCATION', 22, 23)]
actual: (315, u'Telefutura', u'PERSON', 22, 22)
predicted question type: PERSON



all results:
[   (329, u'Massport', 'OTHER', 15, 15),
    (329, u'Massachusetts Port Authority', 'OTHER', 11, 13),
    (194, u'Tufts University', 'OTHER', 0, 1),
    (194, u'Tufts Medical Center', 'OTHER', 28, 30),
    (194, u'Floating Hospital', 'OTHER', 53, 54),
    (194, u'Children', 'OTHER', 56, 56),
    (100, u'Nor', 'OTHER', 20, 20),
    (40, u'Italians', 'OTHER', 21, 21),
    (40, u'Irish', 'OTHER', 27, 27),
    (40, u'Russian Jews', 'OTHER', 35, 36),
    (40, u'West End', 'OTHER', 40, 41),
    (107, u'C', 'OTHER', 44, 44),
    (107, u'F', 'OTHER', 40, 40),
    (340, u'Downeaster', 'OTHER', 5, 5),
    (340, u'T', 'OTHER', 33, 33),
    (340, u'Amtrak', 'OTHER', 2, 2),
    (21, u'French', 'OTHER', 21, 21),
    (21, u'British', 'OTHER', 18, 18),
    (21, u'Indian Wars', 'OTHER', 13, 14),
    (21, u'French', 'OTHER', 11, 11)]
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (329, u'Massport', 'OTHER', 15, 15),
    (329, u'Massachusetts Port Authority', 'OTHER', 11, 13),
    (137, u'South Asians', 'OTHER', 12, 13),
    (137, u'Indian', 'OTHER', 20, 20),
    (150, u'South Church', 'OTHER', 1, 2),
    (153, u'Boston Tea Party', 'OTHER', 16, 18),
    (153, u'Old South Meeting House', 'OTHER', 9, 12),
    (40, u'Italians', 'OTHER', 21, 21),
    (40, u'Irish', 'OTHER', 27, 27),
    (40, u'Russian Jews', 'OTHER', 35, 36),
    (40, u'West End', 'OTHER', 40, 41),
    (172, u'Boston Convention and Exhibition Center', 'OTHER', 26, 30),
    (172, u'Seaport World Trade Center', 'OTHER', 21, 24),
    (172, u'Hynes Convention Center', 'OTHER', 11, 13),
    (46, u'Financial District', 'OTHER', 21, 22),
    (182, u'Boston College', 'OTHER', 55, 56),
    (182, u'Suffolk University', 'OTHER', 40, 41),
    (182, u'Northeastern University', 'OTHER', 33, 34),
    (182, u'South End', 'OTHER', 30, 31),
    (182, u'Boston University', 'OTHER', 5, 6)]
question: What airport is south of Logan Airport?
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
    (336, u'T', 'OTHER', 18, 18),
    (336, u'MBTA', 'OTHER', 12, 12),
    (258, u'Braves', 'OTHER', 20, 20),
    (258, u'Beaneaters', 'OTHER', 12, 12),
    (10, u'Boston Latin School', 'OTHER', 14, 16),
    (340, u'T', 'OTHER', 33, 33),
    (340, u'Downeaster', 'OTHER', 5, 5),
    (340, u'Amtrak', 'OTHER', 2, 2),
    (35, u'City', 'OTHER', 43, 43),
    (35, u'City', 'OTHER', 23, 23),
    (35, u'Town', 'OTHER', 16, 16),
    (35, u'March', 'OTHER', 29, 29),
    (82, u'Back Bay', 'OTHER', 77, 78),
    (82, u'Trimountain', 'OTHER', 57, 57),
    (82, u'Tremont Street', 'OTHER', 61, 62),
    (265, u'Boston Patriots', 'OTHER', 25, 26),
    (265, u'National Football League', 'OTHER', 16, 18),
    (265, u'New England Patriots', 'OTHER', 11, 13),
    (345, u'Bicycling magazine', 'OTHER', 5, 6)]
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
    (336, u'T', 'OTHER', 18, 18),
    (314, u'PBS', 'OTHER', 6, 6),
    (314, u'WGBH', 'OTHER', 8, 8),
    (314, u'TV', 'OTHER', 10, 10),
    (314, u'PBS', 'OTHER', 16, 16),
    (314, u'WGBX', 'OTHER', 22, 22),
    (256, u'Pilgrims', 'OTHER', 13, 13),
    (273, u'Patriots', 'OTHER', 40, 40),
    (273, u'Day', 'OTHER', 42, 42),
    (273, u'April', 'OTHER', 44, 44),
    (18, u'BC', 'OTHER', 12, 12),
    (193, u'Massachusetts Institute of Technology', 'OTHER', 1, 4),
    (193, u'Boston Tech', 'OTHER', 18, 19),
    (193, u'MIT', 'OTHER', 6, 6),
    (201, u'English', 'OTHER', 25, 25),
    (201, u'Eastern New England', 'OTHER', 18, 20),
    (88, u'Central Artery', 'OTHER', 12, 13),
    (88, u'Central Artery', 'OTHER', 35, 36),
    (88, u'Big Dig', 'OTHER', 23, 24)]
question: The MBTA is also known as the what?
expected: T
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (336, u'T', 'OTHER', 18, 18),
    (336, u'MBTA', 'OTHER', 12, 12),
    (10, u'Boston Latin School', 'OTHER', 14, 16),
    (340, u'T', 'OTHER', 33, 33),
    (340, u'Downeaster', 'OTHER', 5, 5),
    (340, u'Amtrak', 'OTHER', 2, 2),
    (78, u'The Graves', 'OTHER', 73, 74),
    (78, u'Shag Rocks', 'OTHER', 67, 68),
    (78, u'Nixes Mate', 'OTHER', 57, 58),
    (193, u'Boston Tech', 'OTHER', 18, 19),
    (193, u'MIT', 'OTHER', 6, 6),
    (193, u'Massachusetts Institute of Technology', 'OTHER', 1, 4),
    (24, u'Revolution', 'OTHER', 2, 2),
    (221, u'Pops', 'OTHER', 11, 11),
    (221, u'Harborfest', 'OTHER', 6, 6),
    (100, u'Nor', 'OTHER', 20, 20),
    (283, u'The Trust for Public Land', 'OTHER', 6, 10),
    (283, u'ParkScore', 'OTHER', 3, 3)]
question: How long is bostons subway system?
expected: 65.5 miles
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (338, u'Back Bay', u'LOCATION', 25, 26),
    (338, u'South Station', u'LOCATION', 10, 11),
    (339, u'Washington', u'LOCATION', 11, 11),
    (339, u'New York City', u'LOCATION', 7, 9),
    (339, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 33, 33),
    (249, u'Philadelphia', u'LOCATION', 19, 19),
    (249, u'New York', u'LOCATION', 16, 17),
    (249, u'Los Angeles', u'LOCATION', 13, 14),
    (249, u'Detroit', u'LOCATION', 11, 11),
    (162, u'Greater Boston', u'LOCATION', 5, 6),
    (316, u'Newton', u'LOCATION', 15, 15),
    (316, u'Needham', u'LOCATION', 13, 13),
    (134, u'Chinatown', u'LOCATION', 34, 34),
    (134, u'Manhattan', u'LOCATION', 36, 36),
    (134, u'Chinese', u'LOCATION', 26, 26),
    (134, u'Chinatown', u'LOCATION', 22, 22),
    (134, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 10, 10),
    (71, u'Boston Marathon', u'LOCATION', 19, 20),
    (336, u'Americas', u'LOCATION', 29, 29),
    (336, u'Boston', u'LOCATION', 0, 0)]
actual: (338, u'Back Bay', u'LOCATION', 25, 26)
predicted question type: LOCATION



all results:
[   (344, u'80', 'NUMBER', 24, 24),
    (344, u'2015', 'NUMBER', 2, 2),
    (344, u'75', 'NUMBER', 30, 30),
    (344, u'70', 'NUMBER', 37, 37),
    (343, u'2011', 'NUMBER', 1, 1),
    (283, u'50', 'NUMBER', 31, 31),
    (283, u'2013', 'NUMBER', 2, 2),
    (113, u'million residents', 'NUMBER', 18, 19),
    (70, u'2011', 'NUMBER', 21, 21),
    (70, u'36th worldwide', 'NUMBER', 14, 15),
    (70, u'221', 'NUMBER', 26, 26),
    (82, u'three', 'NUMBER', 51, 51),
    (82, u'two', 'NUMBER', 2, 2),
    (139, u'one', 'NUMBER', 10, 10),
    (284, u'10,000 residents', 'NUMBER', 52, 55),
    (215, u'one', 'NUMBER', 38, 38),
    (69, u'129th', 'NUMBER', 24, 24),
    (69, u'2011 survey', 'NUMBER', 34, 35),
    (69, u'one', 'NUMBER', 8, 8),
    (69, u'214 cities', 'NUMBER', 37, 38)]
actual: (344, u'80', 'NUMBER', 24, 24)
predicted question type: NUMBER



all results:
[   (344, u'Transit Score', 'OTHER', 27, 28),
    (344, u'Bike Score', 'OTHER', 34, 35),
    (341, u'The Walking City', 'OTHER', 2, 4),
    (153, u'Boston Tea Party', 'OTHER', 16, 18),
    (153, u'Old South Meeting House', 'OTHER', 9, 12),
    (131, u'Hispanic White', 'OTHER', 24, 25),
    (131, u'Non', 'OTHER', 22, 22),
    (131, u'Census', 'OTHER', 16, 16),
    (131, u'Latino', 'OTHER', 9, 9),
    (302, u'Latino', 'OTHER', 5, 5),
    (328, u'Boston University School of Medicine', 'OTHER', 18, 22),
    (   328,
        u'Boston University Hospital and Boston City Hospital',
        'OTHER',
        42,
        48),
    (328, u'Boston Medical Center', 'OTHER', 0, 2),
    (23, u'Siege', 'OTHER', 37, 37),
    (23, u'Boston Tea Party', 'OTHER', 15, 17),
    (23, u'Boston Massacre', 'OTHER', 11, 12),
    (23, u'American Revolution', 'OTHER', 7, 8),
    (35, u'City', 'OTHER', 43, 43),
    (35, u'City', 'OTHER', 23, 23),
    (35, u'Town', 'OTHER', 16, 16)]
actual: (344, u'Transit Score', 'OTHER', 27, 28)
predicted question type: OTHER



all results:
[   (163, u'US', u'LOCATION', 45, 45),
    (31, u'1920s', 'NUMBER', 3, 3),
    (163, u'National Infrastructure Protection Center', 'OTHER', 12, 15),
    (163, u'Internet', 'OTHER', 27, 27),
    (163, u'CITAC', 'OTHER', 8, 8),
    (163, u'Infrastructure Threat Assessment Center', 'OTHER', 3, 6),
    (163, u'NIPC', 'OTHER', 17, 17),
    (163, u'Investigations', 'OTHER', 1, 1),
    (124, u'Wikipedia', 'OTHER', 26, 26),
    (124, u'Caltech', 'OTHER', 7, 7),
    (124, u'Virgil Griffith', u'PERSON', 3, 4),
    (124, u'2007', 'NUMBER', 2, 2),
    (124, u'August', 'OTHER', 1, 1),
    (140, u'FBI Laboratory', 'OTHER', 14, 15),
    (140, u'1932', 'NUMBER', 21, 21),
    (155, u'Top Hoodlum Program', 'OTHER', 16, 18),
    (155, u'FBI', 'OTHER', 13, 13),
    (155, u'25,1953', 'NUMBER', 8, 10),
    (155, u'August', 'OTHER', 7, 7)]
question: Where was the UCR created?
expected: 1920s
expected sentence: Created in the 1920s, the UCR system has not proven to be as uniform as its name implies.
actual: (163, u'US', u'LOCATION', 45, 45)
predicted question type: LOCATION


